Oh, is‐‐is your mom not home?
Nah, she's never home.
You guys wanna go in first?
Cool.
‐ Is it okay to just‐‐
Put Daddy...
I'm gonna take my jacket off.
‐ What?
‐ I'm gonna take my jacket off.
‐ Okay.
So what should we do?
‐ Whatever.
Okay.
‐ Do you have
any snacks, babe?
Yeah, they're in the freezer
over there.
‐ Over...
Over there. Through the door.
‐ Look here, um‐‐
‐ What chord was that?
- Which one?
- See you.
Just kidding.
JK.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ Totally.
Is this what I look like?
‐ You look amazing.
I am so hungry, though. Like‐‐
‐ Oh, my God.
Wait, look at this freezer.
- Oh, my God!
‐ I'm so‐‐
Wait, are those marshmallows?
- Okay.
- Here.
Oh, my God.
I'm so hungry.
You don't want
to go home, right?
Like, you're not worried
at all?
‐ Mm‐mm. I'm not worried.
Unless you want to‐‐
Do you want to go home
or do you want to stay?
‐ I want to hang out
with our boyfriends.
‐ Okay, yeah.
I don't want to go home.
‐ You're, like, gonna get
your first kiss.
‐ No, I'm not, stop.
Oh, stop!
I don't know.
Is my breath okay?
‐ No, it smells amazing.
How's mine?
I'm sorry, it's not good.
‐ Oh, Maya.
‐ Oh, my God, I'm so sorry.
‐ No.
Here we go.
This song's awesome, man.
Heck yeah.
Let me do it.
Cool. Cool. Cool.
‐ Don't touch my butt.
‐ I didn't.
‐ Wait, would you play
that chord again?
This one right here?
‐ Yeah.
Very good. Cool. Cool.
‐ Could you cut out
the drumming?
We're trying to hit this.
You're throwing me off.
‐ I think that your drumming
sounds good.
Yeah, it's just not
matchin' up with our rhythm.
‐ Steve, her dad's
a professional drummer.
So...
‐ Oh, stop.
‐ He is, though.
You shouldn't be humble.
‐ I'm not.
‐ Excellent! Get up.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Get up, get up, go!
One, two, three.
Cool, cool, cool.
Excellent! Cool.
Sorry.
- Are you being bad?
- Sorry.
‐ You want to check out
my watch?
‐ Yeah.
- Ooh!
- Stop.
‐ You look good. Sorry.
I'm cold.
Thanks, Steve.
‐ Yeah.
‐ What kind is it?
‐ Eh, some kind of army.
It's got the army paint on it.
What are you doing?
I'm just‐‐'cause I'm cold.
We're both cold.
Okay.
‐ You want to go
to my room?
‐ Okay.
‐ Sorry, can we just do
over the shirt?
‐ Huh?
‐ Can we just do over it?
Do you like it
without my braces?
‐ I like it.
Less cuts.
‐ Who's that?
That's Gillian Anderson.
‐ No, below that.
- Oh.
- Is that, like,
your ex‐girlfriend or whatever?
- I'm not mad.
- No, no.
That's my friend.
I don't think about her.
Did you bring your meds?
‐ Um, no, they don't
really work for me.
Sorry. Is that okay?
‐ I guess.
‐ Is this your first time?
‐ Yeah. Is it yours?
‐ No. I've done it a lot.
Like, a couple times.
‐ Yeah.
‐ You mean, a BJ right?
You've had
your first kiss before.
‐ Y‐‐uh. Yeah, obviously.
Like, I've had
a bunch of first kisses.
‐ Cool.
‐ I'm ready.
‐ Oh, sorry.
‐ That's all right.
Let me just‐‐
‐ Keep going.
‐ Okay.
‐ Wait, wait, wait, wait.
‐ Come on.
No.
You think Maya's
a good drummer, right?
‐ I mean, I guess.
‐ Well, You didn't have
her back back there,
and you didn't have, like,
her dad's back,
'cause you only had
Derrick's back.
And it's, like,
who's back do you have?
‐ I love you.
‐ Don't change the subject.
‐ Say it back.
Say it.
‐ I love you too.
Come on, let's take it off.
‐ Get it‐‐
‐ Ahh.
Actually, get this.
Okay.
Do you want to‐‐you could‐‐
‐ Whoa.
What's wrong with your balls?
‐ What do you mean?
‐ Why don't you have
two balls?
‐ What?
Oh, there are two,
it's just they're inside.
It's not like there's a‐‐
‐ Oh, so it's like
the line is‐‐
‐ The line? What line?
‐ The line‐‐it's like
it has its own carrying case.
‐ Yeah. I guess.
Do you want to stop
talking about it?
‐ Yeah. Sorry.
Yeah.
- Okay.
- So I'm gonna start now.
Uh...
‐ What's wrong?
‐ I finished.
‐ I didn't cum.
‐ Oh.
‐ Yeah, that's not‐‐
‐ Yeah?
‐ That's an important part,
right?
‐ Okay, I'm gonna do it.
Okay.
‐ Ah, ah! Teeth, teeth!
‐ Ah, sorry.
‐ Yeah, they're‐‐
They're just kind of, like,
dragging.
‐ Okay.
‐ Like that?
‐ Mm.
Like that?
Mm‐hmm.
Mm.
Thanks.
Do you want to kiss?
I'm gonna go wash my hands.
Oh.
‐ But, I'm gonna be‐‐
Maya?
Wait. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm still‐‐
‐ Maya?
- Ew. Ew, ew, ew, ew.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
‐ Did you just get
your first kiss?
Mine was so disgusting.
Like, I got mine with Brendan,
you know I hated it.
And now, like, Steve is, like‐‐
We have it perfectly down.
So kissing's just like that.
Maya, are you okay?
‐ I just gave him
a blow job.
‐ You got your kiss
and you got a blow job.
‐ I didn't do‐‐I just‐‐
‐ Oh.
‐ I just, like‐‐
‐ Amazing.
‐ Yeah. Is it?
Yeah.
But, what was it like?
Did you like it?
Did he like it?
‐ Um, I don't know.
I, like, think he did,
'cause he just, like‐‐
it was, like, weird,
and then he, like, came.
‐ Oh, my God,
are you serious?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Wow. So cool.
‐ I know.
And you were, like‐‐
You were, like,
"Wow, yeah. You're amazing."
‐ I don't think I want
to do a blow job again, though.
‐ Oh, yeah. Yeah.
‐ I probably am not gonna ever.
‐ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
'Cause it was, like, gross
'cause of the, like‐‐
like, the‐‐
‐ Can we just, like, go home?
‐ Oh, yeah.
- Yeah, we can go home.
- Okay.
‐ Steve, can you drive us home?
‐ Shh!
‐ Let's‐‐let's call Shuji.
Let's call Shuji.
‐ Okay.
‐ Okay!
‐ Steve?
Steve! Steven?
Is everything okay?
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ Yeah.
‐ It's fine.
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ All right.
‐ That's him.
‐ Who's that?
‐ It's my brother.
Hi, Shuji.
I don't want to know
what happened.
Okay, I'm sorry.
You guys take the bike, okay?
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Um, let's just‐‐yeah.
- I got it.
- Okay.
Here, I got you. I got it.
‐ I love you.
‐ Love you too.
‐ Do you have that?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Go.
‐ Peace.
Just do Saturday,
then you can just come
and get her.
And then she can sleep in
Friday and‐‐
no.
No!
I'll just leave her stuff out
by the front door.
Otherwise, you pick her up
Saturday.
Like, let her sleep in, though.
You know, till 2:00.
Hi, hon.
‐ Hey.
Or you pick her up from school
and then you get her stuff,
and then you go.
Um. Okay.
Whatever.
Um, how was Maya's?
You didn't sleep over?
I was just talking to your dad
about you going over
to his this weekend.
Anna's home.
Okay. He wants to talk to you.
‐ Hey, Dad.
‐ How's it going, goof?
You still mad at us?
‐ Um, I just, like,
have some bad news actually,
'cause, um,
a golden retriever
killed Daddy.
And it's my fault.
Don't say it's your fault.
Sweetie, I'm sorry.
What‐‐what happened?
Did the dog steal him?
Um, I kind of put it
on the dog's head.
And that's why it's my fault.
- Sorry.
- Well.
Just, you know,
maybe don't do that again.
All right?
You gotta learn from it.
But the dog was wrong, too,
right?
‐ Yeah, the dog was wrong too.
Yeah.
‐ And also, like...
I love Steve.
‐ Aw.
‐ Really?
‐ Um, mom.
‐ What?
But I also don't know
about him.
‐ Well, what'd your mom say?
‐ Um.
‐ Here.
Put her on speaker phone.
Kathy?
She loves him.
‐ I didn't know.
She didn't tell me.
‐ But I don't know
'cause he doesn't, like,
always listen to my feelings,
and I don't know
about his best friend.
He just doesn't take me
seriously.
‐ Well, I don't like that.
But I also want to marry him.
It's not funny.
‐ I'm sorry.
‐ Don't laugh, Dad.
‐ I'm not laughing.
Just fix it.
‐ Oh, sweetie.
We can't fix everything,
you know that.
But we can listen, okay?
‐ Okay.
Dad?
What are you doing?
‐ Vacuuming.
Oh, hey, I got the plastic
off the oven.
‐ Proud of you, Dad.
Derrick!
Yeah, my snake's been acting
real sweet lately.
‐ Really?
‐ Yeah.
‐ This is private.
‐ She's always taking
her tongue out...
‐ Tell him.
- Tell him.
- And licking me.
I know she's just smelling,
but‐‐
‐ When are you gonna tell him?
- Um, wait.
- Huh?
‐ Okay, it's been 21 minutes
of us talking on the phone.
I feel like that's
our longest yet, babe.
Derrick:
Yeah. Oh, hold up.
I gotta grab‐‐I gotta go grab
the snake something...
‐ Oh, okay‐‐
Then I gotta
tell you something.
‐ Okay.
Okay, what? He's on hold.
‐ Okay, so you're gonna say,
"If you still want
to go out with me,
I can't give you another BJ."
‐ I want to go out
with him.
I just don't want
to give him a BJ again.
‐ And medicine 'cause
my doctor prescribed it.
‐ Shh!
Anna, I already told him
that part yesterday.
‐ Okay!
‐ Okay.
Wait, nah. Open your mouth.
‐ What?
‐ Your tooth.
What's wrong with my tooth?
‐ Oh, my God!
What happened?
‐ No, I just got my braces off!
‐ It looks crazy.
No!
Anna.
No, no, no.
This is why I got braces!
Are you kidding me?
‐ I mean, honestly,
I like you better that way.
‐ With a snaggle?
I'm gonna have to get
my braces back on.
You still there?
‐ Hi, yeah.
Turn on the radio
to HOT 106.7.
‐ What‐‐okay, um.
Anna. Anna!
He just said put the radio on.
Put it on‐‐on 106.7.
‐ Did he get you
concert tickets?
‐ I don't know!
‐ Did he get us
concert tickets?
Got it.
‐ Okay, it's on, it's on.
I freaking love this song.
- You listening?
- Yeah.
I'm listening.
Good.
Every time you hear this song,
think about how
I'm breaking up with you.
'Cause that's
what I'm doing right now.
Man it's a hot one
Like seven inches
from the midday sun
Well, I hear you whisper
and the words melt everyone
But you stay so cool
And if you said
this life ain't good enough
I would give my world
to lift you up
I could change my life
To better suit your mood
'Cause you're so smooth
And it's just like the ocean
under the moon
It's the same as the emotion
that I get from you
You the kind of loving
that can be so smooth, yeah
Give me your heart,
make it real
Or else forget about it
It's just like the ocean
under the moon
And it's the same as the
emotion that I get from you
You got the kind of loving
that...
What's wrong with her?
Give me your heart...
‐ Mai.
‐  Make it real
or else forget‐‐
‐ What's wrong with you?
They want to know.
‐ Nothing.
It's just my high school
boyfriend said,
"Every time you hear this song,
I want you to think
"about me breaking up with you
'cause that's what
I'm doing right now."
So now, I keep listening
to this song
over and over again
and keep thinking
about how he broke up with me.
So it's just a cycle
of listening to this song
until I can get
the him breaking up with me
out of my head,
so I just gotta keep listening
to this song till it's done.
‐ You know
what this guy sounds like?
He sounds like a straight‐up...
Lo‐ser.
Look at me.
Hello there!
‐ It's, like, not even
how you do it.
‐ Lo...ser!
Loser!
Yeah, you're‐‐she's much
better at it than me.
‐ I'm not.
So this guy is your boyfriend's
best friend?
‐ Yeah. Why?
You know the saying, right?
"You are what you eat."
And Steve is eating
Derrick's asshole, so to speak.
So if you just‐‐
if you draw the connection‐‐
So you're saying
they're both shitty?
‐ I mean, kind of.
Okay, genius,
thank you so much.
You don't know him.
Steve isn't Derrick, like‐‐
‐ Well, picked real winners.
Maya. Maya!
Do you want to, like,
egg this fucker's house
after school?
‐ Okay.
‐ Yeah?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Okay?
Let's do it. Yeah.
Yeah!
What's up, player?
- So you're not coming?
- That was trash.
I mean, he only did
the most jacked up thing
to my best friend.
Like, he's your friend.
And he's screwing over
my friend.
I mean, they just don't jive.
She didn't respect his music.
I don't know.
‐ Oh, my God.
That is not an excuse.
He's a psycho.
‐ It wasn't cool.
‐ Yeah, it wasn't.
‐ What else do you want
me to say?
‐ Well, you're‐‐
it wasn't cool.
It was dishonorable
what he did.
But it'd be dishonorable
for a best friend to‐‐
‐ Okay, so you're not coming?
‐ I'm not gonna egg
my best friend's house, Anna.
‐ Okay, you chose sides.
‐ "I'm not in this world
to live up
"to your expectations,
and you're not in this world
to live up to mine."
‐ Not everything is a saying.
Like, it's kind of a cop out.
And you chose sides,
and it's not mine,
so I'm not choosing yours.
I don't want to go out
with you anymore.
‐ Anna...
You've made your choice.
I respect it.
And I went to the bathroom
and I was‐‐and as I was walking
into the stall,
it was just like a needle.
Nah, he's not coming?
‐ No.
‐ What happened?
‐ Um, we just broke up.
‐ What?
Oh, my God.
- Are you okay?
- Sorry, Anna. That sucks.
Sorry, that's sucks.
What happened?
‐ Nothing.
Let's go egg this bitch.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Okay?
‐ Okay.
‐ Let's just, like‐‐
‐ Do it.
‐ All right.
‐ Let's go!
Yeah!
Okay, stop!
‐ Do it.
‐ Okay, okay!
Shh!
Come on, come on, come on.
Okay.
Wait, what is this?
‐ Ew, oh, my God.
‐ Is this baby squid?
Are you kidding me, Maya?
Ew!
‐ It was all my mom had.
- That's what smells.
- What?
- It's stinky!
- But why?
‐ It's fine.
‐ It's jiggling.
‐ Wait, what?
‐ Don't touch me with that.
‐ Oh, shit.
Oh, my God,
I touched its tentacle.
Oh, no! No!
Dude, actually this is bad.
Look at all the ink.
Dude, do it.
‐ Ew!
‐ Shut up,
‐ That's gonna get
all over Derrick's window.
- You do it.
- You do it!
- Just throw it!
‐ Go, go!
Oh, my God.
- Oh!
- Yeah, eat squid!
- Okay.
- Ew, ew!
Run!
- Stop.
- Hey, scatter everyone.
Scatter! Go, go, go!
Oh, shit, my backpack!
- Go, go, go!
- Hey!
Yeah, wait up!
- Bitch!
- Fuck you!
- Hey!
Oh, my God.
Shh, shh, shh.
Shh, shh, shh. Can I sit here?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God! Go, go, go!
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, shit!
‐ Shh! Shh!
‐ Is she still there?
‐ Fuck you!
‐ Shut up!
- Fuck you!
- Shh.
Bitch.
‐ How long should we wait?
‐ I don't know.
How long should we wait?
‐ I don't know,
that's why I asked you.
‐ Okay.
Sorry, I'm just thinking
about Steve.
He's just, like, not at all
who I thought he was.
And, like‐‐
‐ Dude, you deserve
way better than that scrub.
Trust me.
‐ I don't feel like that
right now.
‐ You have a little bit
of grass in your hair.
‐ Thank you.
‐ Anytime.
‐ Sometimes Steve did that.
He would take‐‐
‐ You want to see
something cool?
‐ Yeah.
‐ All right, check this out.
‐ You have grass
on your butt.
Ready?
Oh, my God. Look at your knees.
Shit.
My mom's gonna kill me.
This looks so stupid.
- Where did everyone go?
- I don't know.
I hope they didn't get caught.
Yeah.
How long do you think
we should stay back here?
‐ At least, like,
30 minutes or so.
30 minutes?
- Something like that.
- No.
‐ I don't know.
‐ That's too long.
What?
‐ You know you're pretty,
right?
‐ No, I'm not, stupid.
Don't say that.
I'm butt ugly. It's fine.
No, you're not.
You're not butt ugly at all.
‐ Are you joking?
Not today.
Can I see your Discman?
‐ Why?
‐ I don't know.
I just want to try something.
‐ Okay, just be careful
with it.
Okay. Need help?
So whenever you hear
this song...
I want you to think of this.
If it's okay.
‐ All right. Okay.
It's okay.
‐ It's okay?
‐ Yeah.
‐ All right.
And if you said
this life ain't good enough
I would give my world
to lift you up
I could change my live
to better suit your mood
Because you're so smooth
And it's just like the ocean
under the moon
It's the same as the emotion
that I get from you
You got the kind of loving
that can be so smooth, yeah
Give me your heart,
make it real
Or else forget about it
So cute.
Look at my cheeks,
they're so fat.
- Look at your face.
- You're like...
Oh, no, you're so little.
You were so cute.
‐ You're so cute.
‐ Oh, my God, look.
There I am.
- So stupid.
- Oh, little baby Maya.
Oh, my God.
I wonder what we'll be like
in the future.
‐ I know.
All I know is, I want my hair
to be, like, super, super long.
‐ Yeah?
‐ Like, to my ass.
‐ You will.
Yeah.
I can't believe
it's gonna be, like,
eighth grade, and then high
school, and then college.
And, like...
‐ Yeah, it's crazy.
‐ Do you think that
there's ever a time
that we won't be friends?
‐ Nah.
Why would you say that?
‐ No, I'm just saying,
'cause things happen, like‐‐
‐ Like what things?
‐ Like, what if after college,
you get a little bit depressed,
and I'm a little irresponsible,
and we're both
just so super dependent
on each other,
and I can't take it anymore.
And we don't laugh
like we used to?
‐ Or, like, the things
that we didn't think
would bother us
about each other.
Or our parents.
Or the way we see the world
starts to eat at us,
and we just get, like,
really cynical.
And really just, like,
wake up one day
and we're not friends.
Or...
‐ We share a dorm...
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ After school.
‐ Yes.
‐ Okay?
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ And I cook you
all of your lunches.
‐ Oh, yeah.
And I cook breakfast,
- dinners, and snacks.
- Yeah.
'Cause you're the only one
who knows how I like
my onions to be cooked.
‐ I knew you were gonna
say onions.
Sautéed.
‐ Sautéed! That's it.
‐ I know.
‐ Literally.
And, like, after work,
when we're older,
we're probably gonna, like,
walk together, like, every day.
‐ Yeah, and we're gonna
have a double wedding.
‐ Yeah.
And then we'll probably get
divorced at the same time.
‐ 'Cause they got in the way
of us.
‐ Yeah, and then
we'll probably have kids,
like, a couple years apart,
so that you can help me
raise mine.
'Cause I'm gonna have
issues with it.
‐ And we can live
on the same property, right?
‐ Yeah.
And then when you get sick,
I'm gonna take you
to the doctor every day
because it's a block away,
okay?
I'm gonna take you.
I will.
‐ We're just gonna protect
each other from everything.
‐ You promise?
‐ And then there are
gonna be clouds
that are, like,
a little lower in the sky,
like, just around our house.
‐ Yeah.
‐ And they're gonna be
really, really soft
so we can just, like,
hang out in them
and do, like, whatever,
you know?
‐ Yeah.
‐ And then, like,
I'm gonna, like,
have the angels come down
every Friday,
and they're gonna be, like,
"Hey, do you guys, like,
want anything?"
And we're gonna be, like, "No."
'Cause we have each other.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ Oh, my God, look!
That's when we met.