It's weird D isn't here yet.
He's coming. He is!
I brought him
my Thursday pill, look.
Hi. How are you?
I'm your neighbor
from down the street.
How are you?
‐ Good. Is this
the wrapping paper project?
Because I'm cooking something.
I get all my gift wrapping at
the Christmas Tree shop, so...
‐ This is for
the Walk for Cancer.
‐ Yeah and it's through
my Unitarian Church
in Conchamaguet.
Um, we're just
selling luminaries.
So if I can just have
another moment of your time.
"You can choose a message
for your survivor
"or beloved deceased
you want to remember.
"We'll write it
for you on a bag."
‐ No, no, I'm sorry.
No, thank you.
‐ Bitch.
Oh, my God.
‐ What are you doing?
‐ I didn't think she heard.
‐ The door was so open.
‐ Geez.
‐ Ha!
‐ We know you're there.
You've, like, done it
three times.
‐ I keep forgetting.
‐ So stupid.
‐ Stop. Don't do that.
‐ Did‐‐
Did D answer yet?
'Cause he said he was
going to be here at three.
Steve.
‐ Steve.
I'm still waiting for his page.
‐ Okay.
‐ If you think a thing
is impossible,
you will make it impossible.
Babe, stop.
Shwank! Got your beeper!
I got it!
‐ You look nice today.
‐ No, I don't.
Can't even get
this thing to work.
I'm doing something
good for the world.
How?
My, God.
D's not coming, you guys.
You guys!
Cool. Third wheel.
Hey, you guys. D's not coming.
Boo, I don't care.
‐ Maya, my back.
‐ Sorry.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ It just, like, sucks.
He's not coming.
‐ Okay, I'm sorry.
You didn't get mad
at Steve when
he jumped on your back,
but you did when I did.
Well, that's because
he didn't put pressure on it.
- You know I have a bad back.
- I'm sorry.
So am I.
Oh, my God.
Hi, how are you?
Would you like to buy
a luminary for
the Walk for Cancer, please?
I like your hair.
‐ You're very cute.
Are you fifth graders?
‐ Um, "so you can choose
a message for your survivor
"or beloved deceased
that you want to remember.
"And we'll write it
for you on the bag.
"The‐‐"
‐ "The message
"is a celebration of
a loved one touched by cancer.
"And on the night of the walk,
each bag becomes a luminary
"lit within by a candle
and that light.
‐ "Reminiscent‐‐
‐ "Reminiscent of
"your loved one's"‐‐my turn.
"Loved one's fighting spirit,
which we celebrate today."
What'd he say?
‐ What?
‐ What did he say?
‐ He's talking to his mom.
It's just this person
spelled Kevin,
Kevine with an E‐‐look.
‐ Are you talking to me or him?
Hi, sorry, Steve.
I was just talking to Maya.
Yeah.
Oh, my God, Steven.
We've been talking on the phone
for, like, so long.
It's been three hours.
‐ Anna, do you like my shirt?
Isn't it good? Is it okay?
Oh, my God.
Sorry, I was talking
to Maya again.
Um‐‐
‐ I think it looks good.
‐ What'd your mom say now?
‐ Personally.
Do you want to see yours?
Oh, my God. Awe.
You know the Walk for Cancer's
tomorrow.
And you and Derrick are coming,
like, what time?
Yeah, tomorrow.
No, we sold enough bags
for all of us to go.
Can you and Derrick reschedule
bowling for another night?
What?
‐ I'm not. Are you mad?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry. No. I don't know.
Do you swear to God?
No, but you do sound mad at me.
Okay, I love you.
Love you so much, bye.
Are you still on?
‐ Is he mad?
‐ Um, he can't come
because they have plans.
Why can't they
just cancel on each other?
‐ Maya, they have plans,
and they promised each other
they were going to do it,
so they can't cancel.
‐ Okay, sorry, but then
maybe it's better
that it's just you and me
and not Steve
'cause it's been
you guys hanging out a lot.
Sorry.
‐ Sorry.
Maya, maybe you should
call Derrick because, like,
if he wants to come,
then he might want to
change his plans and see you,
and then Steve will come too.
‐ I don't want to.
‐ Maya, no, please.
‐ No, Anna, I don't
want to call him.
Why?
‐ Because he's, like,
been really busy and stuff.
‐ What is he doing?
‐ I don't know.
He's not calling me back,
so I don't...
‐ Please, he loves you.
‐ I, like,
don't even know his number.
Oh, my God, yes.
He loves you so much.
‐ Shh!
‐ Oh, my God. Hey, it's Maya.
Maya.
‐ He loves you.
‐ No, I'm calling you
from Anna's phone.
I didn't block my number.
Oh, 'cause you have caller ID.
No, yeah,
it's just Anna's phone.
‐ Ask about the bowling.
‐ Um, are you guys
gonna be coming to
the Walk for Cancer tomorrow?
D?
What'd he say?
Are they gonna come?
‐ Oh, he hung up.
They can't come. Whatever.
It'll be better anyway
without them.
It can just be you and me.
Anna, it's fine.
Anna, me and you time
and people with cancer.
It'll be fun.
Hello, everyone.
Very happy to be here
with all of you today.
Let's do this, you guys.
Our team sold
the second most luminaries.
So let's share our names
and why we're here.
Uh, we'll start with the people
who sold the most bags.
Jay.
‐ Um, I'm Jay.
This is my partner, Roger.
Um, I'm a tent master.
So, I, uh‐‐
I actually lost my mom
to cancer this year.
Yeah.
It's about three months ago.
I just haven't really known‐‐
‐ Do you think we're
gonna have to walk
the whole time because
I don't want to.
I've dragged Roger
here with me.
- No, you didn't. No.
- I did, I did.
‐ Oh, my God, what is wrong?
You're being really crazy
right now.
And I just want to kind of...
What?
Honor him today as we walk.
‐ I have this pit in my stomach
because I think that
Steve's gonna break up with me.
‐ No way.
‐ Girls. Girls. Please.
‐ Sorry.
‐ Anyway, I just want
to honor him today
as we walk.
Now, I'm Roger, by the way.
‐ Hi, Roger.
‐ I have a question.
Are we gonna walk
the whole 24 hours?
'Cause I don't think
that's possible.
‐ Okay, we're gonna need
a talking stick
because people
keep interrupting.
‐ I raised my hand.
‐ This team is going to walk
in shifts, okay?
So no, it won't be
the whole time.
‐ Oh.
The walk is starting now.
Please make your way
to the track, thank you.
‐ I haven't gotten to say
anything yet.
‐ Girls, girls,
why don't you start us off?
- Okay?
- Okay, Minister Eve.
- Okay.
- Okay, Frances.
We can keep‐‐while they're
going.
- I don't know.
- Go ahead, Francis.
My father died
about a year ago.
‐ Like, still don't get when
we're supposed
to sleep and stuff.
And, like, how many miles
we're supposed to walk.
‐ Yeah, I can't‐‐I can't
even do a mile run.
So I don't know.
‐ Yeah, it's 'cause it turns
into the mile walk every time.
Anna, are you
in a better mood now?
‐ No, that just was funny.
‐ Yeah, that's 'cause
I'm here and it's not Steve.
I'm the one who's, like,
making you happy.
Anna, stop.
Oh, my God, okay, I thought
this was the Walk for Cancer?
‐ Maya‐‐
‐ I just‐‐I take it back.
That was mean. That was mean.
No, I didn't mean it.
'Cause you were
trying to laugh at me.
Anna, stop.
‐ Maya, no.
Don't say that.
‐ Are you gonna piss yourself?
Anna, stop. Get up. Get up.
This is your mom, Anna.
You have to get up right now.
Anna.
I'm dying. I'm dying of water.
Please help me.
‐ That's not funny.
Oh, my God.
Oh, you heard the joke?
- I heard it too.
- I'm so sorry.
Oh, my God.
Sorry.
Is someone gonna say something?
'Cause it's just like,
what's going on?
‐ Ha ha.
‐ I'm Sean.
‐ Brett.
‐ Sorry, I said that
as you said your name.
‐ Stop it, Anna.
‐ I'm Maya.
‐ What‐‐yeah, I'm Anna.
‐ Where you guys from?
‐ Um, the town over, Trailview.
Skills.
‐ You go with anyone?
‐ Um, yeah, but our boyfriends
are, like, dead today.
‐ What are you guys doing here?
‐ We like to do good.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Yeah, us too.
‐ Um‐‐
‐ Um, come in our tent?
‐ No, we do have boyfriends.
Sorry, my voice just cracked.
We do, though.
‐ Are you wearing a ring?
‐ We're just not at that point.
‐ It‐‐it's just a tent.
‐ Like‐‐
‐ We're not engaged, like‐‐
‐ "Like, like..."
‐ Okay. We'll go to your tent.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ They are so hot.
‐ I know. I don't want
to talk about it.
I want to hook up
with the guy from‐‐
this wouldn't happen
if Derrick and Steve were here.
Let's go,
let's pick up that pace
a little bit back there.
We're walking
for a cure here today.
Wait, it's actually stuck.
‐ Your town is cool.
‐ Yeah.
It's stupid, too, though.
Yeah.
Um, I've never seen this
material on a track before.
It's really‐‐it's really nice.
What?
Are you‐‐is your neck okay?
‐ Oh, my God, Anna.
‐ Maya, stop.
‐ Come here, I want
to whisper something to you.
‐ Just say it out loud.
‐ Stop. I can't, seriously.
‐ Okay.
Brett thinks you're cute.
‐ What'd you just say, Sean?
‐ Nothing.
I was just telling Ann here
that you think she's cute.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ I mean, I do, though.
‐ He almost got
class president this year.
And he's fucking funny.
‐ Nah, nah, nah.
‐ You should kiss him.
‐ What?
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ Kiss him. Why not?
‐ I can't 'cause
I have a boyfriend.
I told you that.
‐ We went over this.
‐ I'm not a cheater.
‐ She said they're,
like, buried or...
‐ No, I was, like, kidding.
They're not dead.
They're just, like‐‐
they're in high school, so.
‐ They are probably
cheating on you.
- What?
- Honestly.
With some high school girls.
Well‐‐
‐ Just kiss him.
You shouldn't let boyfriends
rule your life.
‐ Yeah,
you should be independent.
‐ We are independent.
We're independent women.
Right?
‐ Yeah.
‐ We just can't.
I just can't, so.
‐ What? That‐‐that's mean.
He has cancer.
‐ No, he doesn't.
‐ What? Yes, he does.
I swear to God he does.
That's fucked up.
‐ Cool.
‐ You guys, that's, like,
really fucked up
to joke about that.
Like, that's not cool.
‐ Yeah, he knows
it's not a joke.
It's his life.
‐ You guys, it's not funny.
‐ See? He does.
‐ That could've been a haircut.
‐ Ask him yourself.
‐ Do you?
‐ Do‐‐do you have cancer?
‐ Yeah.
‐ If you're not lying,
I'm sorry.
‐ Sorry, if you're not lying.
‐ So you gonna kiss him?
‐ Should we keep walking?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Wait, wait.
Just give my man
a kiss on the cheek.
‐ Oh, okay.
‐ Okay.
If it's on the cheek, yeah.
‐ Okay. Oh, my God.
You guys are, like, so crazy.
One.
Two, three.
‐ Ooh, three‐way kiss
is this kid's first kiss.
Player over here.
I'll see you guys out there.
‐ See ya.
‐ Peace.
Bye.
Oh, my God, the tent.
If anyone sees my wife,
can you please tell her that
I'm looking for her?
I'm out here in the field.
The 50‐yard line.
- Okay, that was crazy.
- Yeah.
‐ He was lying, right?
‐ I felt bad, but I don't know.
I think so, yeah.
‐ No, I know, I felt bad too.
But I'm kind of like, everyone
gets a haircut like that.
Like, it's called a buzzcut.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Supercuts or whatever.
‐ My God, that would be
so messed up.
You think he just‐‐yeah.
I feel sick, though.
I don't know why.
Assholes, come here.
Us?
‐ You two. Come here.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ Stop.
Did you tell my little brother
he doesn't have cancer?
What?
‐ Did you tell my brother
he doesn't have cancer?
‐ Um‐‐no‐‐
‐ I'm so pissed right now.
‐ We‐‐we didn't. Um‐‐right?
‐ No, we didn't.
‐ Cool.
So you go in a tent with them,
act all flirty,
tell Brett that
he doesn't have cancer,
and laugh when
he shows you his hair?
‐ No, no, we didn't laugh.
We were, like, um‐‐
‐ Oh, my God, okay.
‐ We were, like, um‐‐
‐ Don't say God. You're anti.
‐ So this is
just a misunderstanding
'cause what happened is,
we were on the track.
Um, sorry. Um‐‐
‐ Spit it out.
‐ Sean asked us
to go in his tent.
‐ Yeah, 'cause
he wanted us to, like‐‐
‐ Yeah and he was, like‐‐
‐ Kiss him or whatever.
To kiss him. He has cancer.
And so I was like,
"Oh, are you lying?
Or are you just
trying to get play? Or‐‐"
‐ We didn't know if it was play
or lying or, like...
‐ He's not lying about that.
‐ We didn't know. Sorry.
‐ Just stay the fuck away
from my brother.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Anna, Anna, do you think
these people are sick?
‐ Sorry.
‐ Team Radical Love,
right, guys?
Keep up the good work,
guys.
Thanks, guys.
Your burning love
For tonight
Hello?
- Brett?
- Sean?
Is that his sister?
Surprise, bitches.
- Oh, my God.
- What's up?
- Hi.
- Okay.
‐ Jesus.
Yo.
‐ What's up?
‐ Did your hair get longer?
It's hot.
‐ Thanks.
‐ What's up?
Hey, what's up?
I thought you'd be happy
that we came here.
‐ No, I'm not upset. I'm just‐‐
Um, I'm just really tired.
We were, like, sleeping, so‐‐
It's, like, 6:00.
‐ Okay, but it was
kind of dark out.
‐ Yeah, and we almost got,
like, beat up.
‐ Do we need to take someone?
‐ No.
Um, what happened to bowling?
‐ Where are your meds?
‐ Well, I took my Friday pill
'cause I didn't think
you were coming, like...
‐ Lame.
‐ Also, these guys
tried to hook up with us, D.
‐ What?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Not my girl. Not mine.
No, I didn't do it.
I swear, I didn't.
I just, like, on the cheek
'cause he has cancer.
‐ Did you kiss him too?
‐ Yeah, just on the cheek
really quick.
Just 'cause he's sick.
‐ Yeah, like, he might not
ever get a real one, so.
‐ Oh, yeah.
What?
‐ You're not talking that much.
Are you‐‐what's up?
Did you want us to leave?
‐ Steve, I just told you
what was going on.
And, like, also,
sorry, but can you be sensitive
'cause it's
the Walk for Cancer,
and my grandmother
just died of cancer?
‐ Yeah.
‐ I didn't know
you cared that much.
‐ Wasn't it emphysema?
‐ Uh, yeah, it's cancer.
‐ No, that's not cancer.
‐ Whatever.
‐ Stop being, like,
insensitive.
‐ Are you two
on your periods or something?
‐ She doesn't get that yet.
‐ I'm going to sleep too.
‐ What?
How old are you?
‐ 13!
‐ Ew, dude, that kind of
grosses me out.
She doesn't get her period yet.
What are you, dude?
- A pedophile?
- I'm not.
You're, like, a pedophile, man.
Why don't you just
date a sixth grader, bro?
‐ Steve‐‐
‐ Okay, man. Shut up.
‐ I have my period.
‐ Like, right now?
What? That's gross.
‐ I don't have it right now.
I'm just saying I have it.
I'm not, like,
a freaking pedophile.
‐ Good 'cause that
would be gross.
I don't want to know when you
have your period, like, ever.
I want you to stay hot.
‐ Okay.
‐ You should grow
your hair longer.
Lucy Liu.
‐ Okay.
You want some?
‐ What is it?
Vodka.
‐ Um‐‐
I, like, had a lot already.
Chug, chug.
‐ No, thanks.
You guys are being annoying.
I'm over it.
‐ Hey, are you okay?
‐ Yeah. Just‐‐just tired.
‐ Yeah, I am too.
Drunk.
‐ Okay, then
let's go to sleep, like.
‐ Okay, but girls in the middle
so Steve and I no gay, dude.
‐ Shh, there's people
like that on our team.
‐ I just don't want
our butts to touch.
You're missing out.
Be sensitive, like...
Are you okay that they're here?
Yeah.
Are you okay?
Do you want them to go?
Okay.
‐ Are you sure you're okay?
I'm sorry we didn't
come in earlier.
I love you.
‐ I love you too.
‐ Your knee is in my back.
That's my dick.
Thank you. Thank you.
‐ Oh, my God.
They fucking ditched us.
‐ What time is it?
Hey, everybody.
My name is Carl, and I'm sorry
that you all had to listen
to my voice today
on the megaphone.
It's hard to describe
cancer itself
because it was always
just about
these special words they had.
You know, mass.
Be strong. Survivor.
Have goals.
Remission.
All of these key words, but...
the thing that I get to connect
with a lot of you about
today is the, uh,
the departure.
That the people we love go on
before they're even gone.
A mother, a father.
They go on this trip,
and we don't get
to go on it with them.
This trip takes them
somewhere else.
It's like for some of them,
the pain is so great
that the only relief is
to take a bunch of drugs.
Just the day before, their
sickness was just a concept
because we couldn't see
this ride coming.
And then the next day,
it's not a concept anymore
because it‐‐it's a whole
different ride suddenly.
And, uh‐‐but I think
what we all do,
the friend, the daughter,
the father,
the survivor,
I think the strength
that's needed to attend
this‐‐this, uh,
this mountain of a ride
with no definite end point,
no known destination,
is for the fearless
and the brave.
And tonight, right now,
we're all here together
on this same ride,
and it's an honor for me
to connect with all of you
and to be here now.
Tonight, I know
that I'm not alone.
It's not that kind of luminary.
‐ It's not that kind‐‐
‐ Sorry.
It doesn't float.
‐ I thought it was gonna
float up.
Like the ones that float.
So I'm here,
a guy who doesn't
really do things like this.
I'm really glad
that I'm here with you.
‐ Me too. Just you.
I'm very fortunate because
I'm in remission today.
Can we have a moment
of silence, please?
Thank you all so much.
Sit there and
count your fingers
What else can you do
Old girl, you're through
Sit there and count
Your little fingers
Unlucky little girl
Blue
No use old girl
You might as well surrender
Your hope is
getting slender
Why won't somebody send
A tender blue boy
To cheer up
little girl blue
‐ Sorry you lost your mom.
‐ What?
‐ I'm sorry, um‐‐
I'm sorry you lost your mom.
Love you.
‐ I love you.