Jonathan... where have you been?
Bethany, I have to talk to you.
I asked you to come meet me,
because I got you a milkshake,
and now it is warm.
You suck that down now.
I told you, Beth,
no more milkshakes.
Why, you love my strawberry milkshake?
Get right into my face,
and I wanna tell you...
- That you wanna suck my shake?
- No.
- That I can't do this anymore.
- What?
I have a wife and kids at home.
And I got a husband
and two bitch kids,
and I don't care! I miss you!
Hold on.
Can you do that later?
- Ugh!
- OK.
How dare you do this to me, bitch?
If you call me that one more time,
I swear to God I'm gonna hit you.
No, we're too good together.
Don't go to that love.
What is going on here?
You know what, Frank,
I've had it up to here. OK?
- 'Na...
- Yeah?
Can we, like, never not do this?
Duh.
No, it's me, like,
I wanna Sylvanian till we're, like, old.
I wanna do it always.
Like, every Friday night.
I thought you loved me.
I did, and I don't anymore.
Why do they change so quick?
♪ High ♪
♪ I am high ♪
♪ That view I show to you is just a lie ♪
♪ You take what you want ♪
♪ You give what you take ♪
♪ High, high, high ♪
I tell you. Barb has been skimping
on the beans lately.
She's lagging.
- Uh, Mai...
- Anna.
Can you get something out of my backpack?
Ah, it's, like, so annoying, Anna.
Well, fine, don't get it.
I'll get it then.
- No.
- I'll get my hands all over my...
No.
Are you serious?
Hell to the 'Na! No! Are you serious?
Oh, my God!
This is Sylvanian Family Hamburger Wagon!
And like, I've been literally looking
for this forever!
I know.
We should definitely do this tonight.
Oh, my God, yes!
Beth, we've talked about this.
I've talked about it endlessly to you.
We are eating in public tonight.
I don't care.
I want French fries in my mouth
while you suck on them, too.
Why do you have dolls?
We don't. These this...
These that?
- That's not a doll.
- That, no.
- That's investment from eBay.
- Yeah.
Looks like a doll.
You're playing with them tonight,
and everyone knows it. OK?
OK, Gabe. Like What? What are you,
the smartest man on the living Earth?
Yes, we are playing with them,
'cause they're collector items,
so why do you care?
Collectors' item means that you just
kinda put 'em on display.
OK.
Lady, you're 13.
And?
And you're still playing with dolls.
Um, I saw you with a G.I. Joe last week.
They're ripped, OK?
OK, but you're admitting
that you play with them?
I have G.I. Joes,
but I don't play with them.
- Oh, my God!
I'm Sam.
I don't think I play with G.I. Joes.
♪ I don't play with dolls ♪
Shut up!
♪ My name is Sam ♪
- ♪ I play with dolls, dolls ♪
- ♪ I play with G.I. Joes ♪
- ♪ My name is Sam! ♪
- ♪ Sam! Sam! ♪
♪ Sam! I play with dolls, dolls
I play with dolls ♪
Shut up!
Shut up! Hey, everybody!
Oh, my God, what's in that box,
Maya and Anna?
- Are you guys playing with dolls?
- Stop it.
Maya and Anna have a box full of dolls
that they're playing with tonight.
- They do. Oh, my God!
- Yeah, yeah, they are.
Oh, my God, stop!
- Let's go.
- And Maya, what's in there?
Asshole.
- Bye!
You wanna do Sylvanian still tonight or...
I mean, yeah, I bought it.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm really, like, do it
every Friday night since we were six.
- I like one...
- You're such a slut.
So what's the plan?
Uh, my brother was gonna pick up
some herb for us for tonight.
Ooh! Who's got it? Charney?
Yeah. Oh, my God! Relax, slut.
Also Kyle was talking about, like,
maybe hanging tonight.
Only if he brings his older brothers.
I like love Kyle Field.
I thought you loved Brett Field.
No, I like him,
and I like every other Field bro, too.
Wait, who is that?
Do you guys have a lighter?
I left it in my desk.
Totally chill, no worries.
- Found it!
- Oh, give me.
- Ah, shh.
- Shit. Can you guys get that?
- Shit, run, run, run!
- What's going on here?
I still see feet.
Sorry, we're just eating our lunch.
In here?
Everything OK?
That's not ours, we swear on our life.
Yeah, it's not ours.
Um, lessons get learned through choices.
And that's why I'm going to have you
throw that away instead of me. OK?
Thank you.
Your brother's picking us up?
Oh, my gosh, he's like so hot.
Yeah.
Ooh, shut the fuck up, slut!
Oh, my gosh, chillax, Miranda.
Hey, ladies, I just want to apologize...
Shut the fuck up, slut!
- OK.
- Leave.
There you are, girls. OK. Let's go.
Mom, what are you doing? As you remember,
at school, never get out of the car.
And why are wearing that tank top?
Are you kidding,
like with your breasts out?
Be a bad, bad boy.
- Hey...
- You're a bad, bad, bad boy!
My parents aren't home,
and I just need someone to watch me.
I don't know where they went.
Excuse me, sir.
Maya, they're trying to...
he's trying to talk to you guys.
No, I know. He's just busy right now.
Hold on.
All right, this is super fun, like...
I'll just fricking play by myself.
It was, like, your idea to play this,
so like...
Sorry. I thought you, like,
still wanted to. I don't know.
Let's just, like, so something else.
I don't know.
OK, fine.
- Alex!
- 'Sup!
You've been, like, ignoring me
for three days.
We are married. You can't do that anymore.
It's not like middle school.
I'm sorry, babe.
No, sorry is not enough, like...
OK, they need to like, make up now?
Babe, we were just getting into it.
What are you doing?
- I don't know. I'm just like...
- Bored?
Maybe.
- Yeah.
- Again, like...
- Let's just do something else.
- OK, fine.
I'm trying to like...
Don't hog it all
chubs butt, like, I want it.
- Give it to me like...
- OK, slut.
Wait. Who're you calling?
Shh.
- Hello.
- Sam?
Speaking...
- Hey...
- Wait. Who is this?
It's Miranda Harris.
OK...
Hello?
I was wondering if you had any salami,
'cause I'm trying to make a sandwich.
- Sandwich?
- Hello?
Sorry about that. I just had to...
use the bathroom quickly,
but I just wanted to tell you that...
I have a feeling
that you like Maya Ishii-Peters,
- and I just...
- Shh. Stop it! 'Na!
- You're a bitch!
- You are.
Oh, my God, I have an idea!
♪ When you look at me... ♪
I'm hot!
- So much sluttier.
- Hey, Kyle.
I, like, wanna get married to you...
- 'Na...
- and I can't have sex before I do.
I like Kyle.
Kyle, I can't wait to fuck you,
'cause I'm in no hurry for marriage.
Ah, you just fully copied me like...
Wait.
We should, like, totally smoke this.
It'd be so chill.
Yeah, it'd be chill.
I'm just not, like, 100% sure
that I'm ready to be a smoker.
No, no, of course. Like...
I'm not gonna do without you,
'cause we do everything together.
- Together, yeah.
- Yeah.
Like, maybe we should,
get like a lighter.
To, like, play better, you know.
- Hey, Dad.
- Hey, Curt.
Hey, you guys, you look festive.
Curt, we're playing like, dress-up.
Yeah. We're just gonna go for a walk.
- Oh, that's cool.
- Cool.
- OK.
- You need money or anything or...
- Um, yes, please.
- Yeah.
- OK.
- That'd be great.
- Thanks, Curt.
- You guys have fun, though.
- Yeah.
- Thanks, Dad.
- I love you.
- See you, guys.
- Thanks, Curt.
- Bye.
- See ya.
- OK, bye.
Uh, where are your lighters?
Oh.
So, I think I want, like, four of them.
Or is that too many?
- What's up!
- I'm gonna...
- Here with your mom?
- I'm just gonna, like, check to see
if they work.
We're here alone, bitch. JK.
But we're really here alone.
Should I do, like, three, or do I do four?
- Anna?
- What?
Anna, do I do three or do I do four?
Just however many people
get usually.
- So... two?
- Two.
- Yeah, two. We'll just, like, do two.
- We'll just do two.
- Whatever, you know. Thank you.
- Thank you.
Wait, partner.
Oh, my God.
Put it away. Put it away. Put it away.
Go. Go. Go.
This way. This way.
- He like, literally thought we were...
- Wait. Which one do you think...
No, wait.
Oh, my God! 'Na!
- Look. Oh, my God!
- What?
That's Miranda's brother's car.
Oh!
What?
Wait.
Should we spy on them?
Oh, my God, you're so creepy, you stalker.
- I'm not a stalker!
- What are you doing?
They're having a sleepover.
Let's just, like, ding dong and ditch.
Oh, my God, you wanna ding dong and stay.
No.
OK, fine, let's just go back
to your house then.
- OK.
After you...
My God! I knew it. You wanna stay.
- Ah!
- No, I don't.
- Yes, you do.
- No, you do. You wanna do it.
- No, you do it.
- You do it.
- Stop! You do it.
- Stop!
- Maya...
- Anna...
Don't. Don't.
Stop! Anna, stop!
Go!
- Go!
- Who is that?
Maya?
Yo.
Anna?
She's in the bush.
Um... yo, what are you doing?
We were um... like,
just about to smoke.
Oh, cool. Us, too. Let's smoke.
Do you wanna smoke?
Yeah?
Oh, my God!
When are the boys coming?
Nine. Like... relax, biatch.
Like the Fields or...
There's five of us and five of them.
It's perfect.
Isn't one of them, like, eight?
Yeah, but he's fucking hot.
I wish we had herb.
Who's got the beer?
Oh.
Do you guys drink?
I need to pee.
So I'm freaking the eff out.
Who cares? People drink.
Like, it's just beer.
Who cares?
The Field brothers are so hot.
Wait. Wait.
Which one's the hottest one?
- I like...
- It's like...
- I like Kyle.
- No. Scottie.
It's Kyle.
Are you drinking?
Yeah, like, just one sip.
Without me. Cool.
Anna, you take a sip.
Sip! Sip! Sip!
Sip, Anna, sip. Sip, Anna, sip.
- Holy shit!
- Yeah!
Wow!
- Yeah.
- Holy shit!
You guys ever done computer cleaner?
Yeah, actually, I have... or my dad has.
He uses it for computer,
'cause it gets in all the crevices.
- Yeah.
- We are inhaling not cleaning.
- Yeah!
- I know!
- Do you?
- Yeah, I do.
I'll do it if you do it.
- OK.
Me, too. If you do it.
- 'Na?
- Mm-hmm.
Do it then.
- OK.
- Go.
- Give me space.
- OK.
- In your mouth.
- OK. Just inhale.
- Inhale.
OK, ready?
Inhale! Inhale!
- Let's do it.
- Inhale! Inhale!
Inhale! Inhale!
When does it...
Oh, my God! Maya?
Is this normal? Maya? Maya?
- Maya?
- Ah, cool.
- Whoa!
- Oh, my God!
Oh, my God!
How long were we out for?
Ten seconds.
We lost our minds, you guys.
That was crazy!
Just you. We didn't do it.
- Wait, what?
- You looked so scary.
I thought you were a corpse.
Wait. You didn't do it, 'Na?
Sorry. I... I... I... I was gonna...
It's just, like,
I'm worried about my brain.
You promised.
- You are fi... you are fine.
- So messed up.
Guys, it's nine o'clock.
- Where are the boys?
- Wait. It's nine?
Can I use your phone?
Yeah. My brother's room.
See? Now you try.
Hey.
'Sup!
Can I...
May I use your phone, please?
Right in front of you... the boat.
Oh.
- Hello?
- Hey, Mama.
- Is everything OK?
- Yeah. We're just...
We are about to go to bed,
so I just wanted to say good night.
- OK, I hear something.
- Yeah.
Um, it's just... it's a movie Anna rented.
We're just... yeah.
It's Home Alone.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Be polite.
Oyasumi.
Fun, real fun.
Thank you. Good-bye.
♪ Check it out now ♪
♪ Uh... ♪
♪ No doubt now ♪
♪ Yo, check it out now ♪
My mom's not home, so...
Cool.
♪ Biggest thing in my itty bitty world ♪
♪ Called her up
And she made me feel right ♪
Uh... Stevie.
♪ Sittin' back with this mic in my hand ♪
♪ Spittin' hot shit tryin' to see grand ♪
♪ Imprinted on my mind every minute ♪
Charney I guess.
Sick.
♪ Uh, you're such a vivrant thing ♪
♪ Vivrant thing, a vivrant thing ♪
♪ And even though we both fly ♪
♪ Give each other space... ♪
You.
Yes!
♪ Actin' like grown-ups ♪
♪ Don't even try to hide
'Cause the spot blown up ♪
♪ Girlfriend tellin' you... ♪
The... the tall one.
♪ I say 'I dunno' but you say 'Gladly' ♪
Do you need help with that?
Got it.
Wait.
What do you want?
Um, all the good spots are taken.
Well, we can't do
everything together, so...
You ever play Crash Bandicoot?
What?
- You gonna do it?
- OK.
Wait. Mm-hmm.
OK.
This is what I look like without it.
We've just done everything together
since, like, '93.
And then all of a sudden, it's, like,
everything can just change
in, like, a flip or an instant.
I know exactly what you mean.
My grandmother... died last year.
Then you probably know exactly how I feel.
I mean, I... I think so.
Dragon.
I don't know how long
you've known your grandma.
I've known Maya...
literally forever.
Maybe it's more or less like,
when my magic cards got stolen.
I thought we were on the same page,
but like...
You lost me.
Wait, look...
I'm a scarecrow.
What?
Like, if you don't wanna hook up,
that's fine. I mean, like...
I just thought, you know,
we're in like, you know...
Oh, just fricking start with a kiss.
You're gonna come in right now?
Uh-huh.
Onto my lips?
Hoot! Hoot!
I'm an owl now.
I'm...
Someone's coming.
Is that your mom?
What the hell is going on?
- Hurry.
- Take this.
- Me?
- Go. Go.
What's happening?
Shh. She's coming.
Hi, Mom.
- Hi, Ms. Harris.
Hi. How's your girls' night?
- Good.
- Pretty good.
Um, just playing cards.
What's this?
Whose beer is this?
- Did you drink this beer?
- No.
- Don't lie to me.
- I'm not.
- Is that my coat?
- Ye-Yeah.
Come here. Come here.
- No.
- Let me smell your breath.
OK.
I'm gonna need to call your mom.
Oh, my God, my mom.
'Na...
Maya, what are you doing? Go to bed.
Just having water.
You like, yelled at me for an hour.
Give me a break.
- OK, just drink it and go to bed. OK?
- OK.
- Anna!
- Maya!
Go away! I'm mad at you.
I want you to. That's why we need to talk.
Open the door.
Keep your voice down. No!
- Open the... what the fuck are you doing?
- No.
- Don't.
- No!
- OK.
Whatever.
Gone.
Be quiet.
I got it.
Stop rolling your eyes, Anna.
I'm sorry. I don't realize when I do it.
Ugh!
- You just hit...
- OK. Well, I didn't mean to.
Sorry.
Well, I'm just glad that you're OK, so...
Well, I'm not literally OK,
because you left me to get in trouble
by myself.
You're the one that said,
"We can't do everything together,"
when you were in the closet with that boy.
I only said that,
because I did you-know-what...
and you didn't do it with me.
- Are you serious?
- Shh! My mom!
Oh, my God! I'm being shush...
My mom is literally, like, right outside.
So can you please be quiet?
- Shh!
- Are you kidding me?
You just said "are" so loud.
Stop, Anna.
When I came out of the bathroom,
you were already like...
Are you serious?
Yeah, I'm serious.
Yeah, you serious?
Like, seriously, Anna,
you were the one that was like
Are you kidding? You did it before me.
Like, we were supposed
to have our first, like...
together.
And now that moment's gone forever.
What happened in the closet with that boy?
You mean, like, nothing. I swear.
Like, he wanted to hook up with me,
but I was like... no.
Did you... with your guy?
No, he's, like, eight.
Yeah, but he's fucking hot.
Yeah.
I know that you're bored in pretend.
'Na, like...
Come on. You were bored, too,
like, don't even pretend.
I know you're just, like, over me.
'Na, I'm, like, obviously never over you.
Like, come here.
No, I know you are.
I'm not. I swear.
Come on.
Just, like, put them on.
You bitch!
Slut!
I guess I'm sleeping over.
Oh, my God!
Should we flush it?
We could, like... still have
our first together if you want.
OK, I will... if you will I guess.
I don't know. I'm, like, still drunk.
Yeah, like, big decisions should be made
when we're, like, sober.
But I promise, like, when we do do it...
like, we'll do it together.
Wait. I wanna...
- Where you gonna...
- Up here.
- Shh!
Hmm.
Hoot! Hoot! I'm an owl now.