Oh, my god. She's gonna love this.
You are so funny.
Okay, shh. I'm doing it.
Maya, pick up the phone!
Okay, I got it!
It's for you.
‐ hello?
‐ hey.
Hi.
‐ are you super excited for tonight?
‐ oh, yeah. Yeah, I'm really excited.
‐ sleepover part‐ay, girl.
‐ oh, I know. At Maura's.
‐ yeah.
Um, can I ask you, like,
a quick question?
How much do you love Maura?
‐ what do you mean?
‐ like, on a scale from one to ten.
- ‐ um...
- ‐
‐
‐ can I be honest? I think I‐‐
uh... I mean...
I think I pick... Four‐‐
‐ it's Maura and Anna on the phone.
We're just calling‐‐ ‐
oh, my god, you guys!
‐ we're calling‐‐
‐ oh, my god, Maura.
You're on the phone?
‐ Maya?
Truth. Were you gonna say four?
‐ what? That's crazy! No.
I was literally in the
middle of saying...
"For sure ten."
- Like, I love you ten.
- See? Obviously.
I told you she was gonna say ten.
She was saying "for sure ten."
‐ yeah, obviously, I love you ten.
I love you "for sure ten."
You guys are not ready for tonight.
‐ no, I'm packed already.
‐ no, like, I mean it's
gonna be off the hook.
Oh. Okay.
‐ love you, besties. See you soon.
Love you, fool. ‐ bye. Love you guys.
- Love you.
‐ Maya, are you sure you want
to go to this sleepover?
‐ yeah, I'm freaking packing, am I not?
Do you not see a bag?
‐
I don't wanna worry about
picking you up tonight.
You're not gonna have
to, 'cause I'm going
to my other best friend
in the world's house.
Stop.
You don't even know who
I am anymore clearly,
if you're asking.
‐ I'll be with her, Mrs. ishii‐peters.
All night. I'll make sure she's good.
‐ okay.
‐ what?
‐ were you gonna say four on the phone?
‐ no.
No, it's just...
Sometimes, you guys,
like, leave me out,
which is fine, it's just‐‐
that phone call was kinda crazy.
‐ mai, I'm sorry, but I just
wish you weren't so sensitive.
‐ well, I'm actually not
that sensitive, I‐‐
‐ just because we were just playing
and I thought you'd think it's funny.
‐ I actually think it's the
funniest thing in the world.
‐ I thought you'd think it's the
‐ I do. I think it's hilarious.
‐ You do.
And Maura said tonight's
gonna be off the chain, so‐‐
‐ yeah, I agree. It's
gonna be really fun.
I'm excited. ‐ no, me too.
‐ get in the bag.
‐ okay.
‐
'sup, Brandt?
Wanna hang tonight?
I'm bizzy.
Coo.
Watchu doin'?
‐ royal rumble
pay‐per‐view with my boys!
Where you at, Dustin,
Alex, tj, Kyle, and Evan?
What's up, Gabe and jafeer?
Just printing pics of weasels.
Wanna come over watch wrestling?
You must be done sucking Brandt's dick.
Har, har.
Match at 7:00. Mom's getting pizza.
Sure, bro. I'll bring a beer.
Jafeer?
‐ "when the people you love are gone,
you are alone."
Keanu Reeves.
♪ Uh, today's the day ♪
So what are the plans
for the party tonight?
‐ so, like, obviously, we're
gonna do truth or dare,
'cause you can't, like,
not do truth or dare.
Obviously. And whoever's
the most honest
gets a beanie baby.
‐ oh, hey.
Hey. ‐ thanks for having me.
Course. ‐ oh, my god.
Is that double stuffed crust?
Yeah.
‐ amazing. I'm gonna do it.
‐ like, has it ever been proven?
‐ hey. ‐ hey.
‐ well, it's never been
proven, but, like,
I've heard all sorts of stories‐‐
Anna.
‐ where's your mom? ‐ what?
Is there more powerade?
To, like, chant her name and, like‐‐
I'm gonna have to read
the instructions again.
You either, like, spin around‐‐ ‐ guys.
Or, like, you look in the mirror.
‐ I haven't seen Maya in a long time.
Can't find her anywhere.
‐ okay.
♪ We're riding in a rollercoaster ♪
‐ what the fuck?
‐
‐ lt's the‐‐
it's the rhi‐‐
it's ace ventura coming
out of the rhino's butt.
‐ ugh, you guys are so weird sometimes.
‐ sorry.
‐ way to be late to my party, guys.
♪ Riding in a rollercoaster ♪
Anyway, I've heard all
sorts of stories...
- Just for a second.
- I'm hosting out here.
We'll be out.
Um, is something wrong?
‐ are you mad at us?
Like, you can be honest.
‐ my god, stop.
You guys are just really
annoying sometimes.
When you laugh together. ‐ okay.
- ‐ sorry.
- Sorry.
‐ you're right.
‐ whatever. It's more Gina.
She's so annoying.
Oh. ‐ oh, Gina.
‐ she's so annoying.
‐ I don't even know if she,
like, wants to be here, but‐‐
‐ no, she'd be crazy
to not wanna be here.
‐ so, like, you swear then.
You're not mad at us.
‐ my god, mai, not at all.
But, like, ask me one
more time and I'll, like,
actually be mad at you.
‐ okay.
‐ Come on, guys.
Number ones?
‐ oh, yeah, number ones.
- Maya?
- Maya.
What's wrong, mai?
- ‐ what?
- What's wrong?
You good?
‐ yeah, I'm fine.
I just have to go to the bathroom.
‐ okay, do you want me
to stay‐‐or us to stay?
‐ mm‐mm. ‐ yeah, you okay?
‐ no, no, no, it's okay.
It's a number two actually, so‐‐
‐ Listening.
Plunk, plunk.
- ‐ oh, okay.
- Like, plop.
‐ well, it's not gonna plop.
It's gonna be really smooth and quiet.
Sure. ‐ love you.
- Bye.
- Don't take forever.
Bye.
‐ you guys?
You guys.
Maura, Becca, and Gina:
Crack an egg on your head,
let the yolk drip down,
let the yolk drip down.
Crack an egg on your head,
let the yolk drip down,
let the yolk drip down‐‐
let the yolk drip down.
Crack an egg on your head,
let the yolk drip down,
let the yolk drip down.
Crack an egg on your head,
let the yolk drip down,
let the yolk drip down.
‐ hey.
Crack an egg on your head...
‐ hey, Maya.
‐ couldn't find you guys.
‐ what happened? You fall in the potty?
No, I just didn't see where you went.
‐ we're here. ‐ yeah.
Okay, so here's the thing, you guys.
No one is going to sleep tonight.
Ooh.
- Wait, what?
- Oh, my god.
‐ my swim meet's at 8:00,
so there's, like, no way.
‐ no one cares. We're staying up.
‐ well, I just get really
tired at 10:00, but‐‐
‐ I'm down.
Yeah! Hell yeah!
‐
‐ jk.
How are we gonna stay up?
‐ drink up, children.
Ew.
‐ wait, na, you're gonna
stay up all night?
‐ are we staying‐‐I thought
we were staying up all night.
‐ no, I just didn't know
that you wanted to do‐‐no.
- ‐ okay.
- I want to.
‐ yeah, that's the only reason I‐‐
- ‐ I said it.
- I'm doing it.
There we go. Heck yeah! Come on!
‐ oh, my god, Anna, you're
gonna be up all night.
- Yes!
Yeah! ‐ that's a huge sip.
Guys. ‐ we're gonna be so hyper.
You guys. Guys.
♪ Back to back, belly to belly ♪
‐ oh, my gosh.
‐ Maya, really, really do it.
Like you're really a stripper.
Oh, my god.
‐ so, like, um... ‐ she's so funny.
‐ are you Maura's new
best friend, or...
‐ oh, me and Maya are. Are you?
‐ um, no. My mom makes
me come here, so‐‐
- ‐ oh.
- Whoo!
‐
‐ gross!
Don't mind if I do.
‐ okay, is that enough time?
- I'm done. I did it.
- Okay, good job.
‐ that was really
embarrassing, you guys.
Next. ‐ okay.
Okay, next.
Okay. Um... Becca.
Okay, truth or dare?
‐ truth for sure.
‐ what's a deep dark secret
you've never told anyone?
‐ okay, I've never told anyone this...
Okay.
‐ but Heather cheated on
Alex with her cousin.
They hooked up.
‐ he so doesn't deserve that.
- Her first‐‐her first cousin?
- That's disgusting.
‐ wait, that's, like,
disgusting, you guys.
That's incest. ‐ yeah.
‐ that's really bad.
‐ but you guys can't tell anyone this.
Swear. On your life. ‐ no way.
‐ swear. Swear. ‐ oh, I swear.
‐ pinky swear. ‐ don't tell anyone.
Swear?
Swear.
‐ I'll, like, never forget this night.
‐ I love you guys. ‐ love you guys.
Love you.
I love you too.
Ew, no. No, that's so gross.
‐ no, Anna will make it really funny.
‐ wait, what will I make funny?
I wanna do something. I'll do it funny.
‐ yes, she will!
‐ okay, I didn't pick it,
so don't get mad at me.
‐ I'm not gonna get mad.
Okay.
Anna's dare is...
To go lick the bathroom floor.
‐ oh, my god.
‐ that's disgusting.
‐
But you have to do it.
‐ no, I'm not doing that.
That's disgusting.
‐ what? That's not fair.
We all did something and
you're not going to?
‐ yeah, but mine's worse.
‐ I know, but it's gonna be funny
if you do it, na.
Just do it. Do it. ‐ yeah.
‐ oh, my god. ‐ there, I did it.
Oh, that's disgusting.
‐ that doesn't count. ‐ Maura, truth.
You haven't done a truth yet.
‐ that's true. You
have not done a truth.
Okay.
‐ how far have you gone with a guy?
‐
Definitely not as far as you or Anna.
- What?
- ‐
‐ okay.
Truth, Maya.
What really happened with Brandt?
Were you really desperate?
‐ I don't know. Can I say, na?
‐ tell them what...
‐ okay, this stays in this group.
‐ yeah. ‐ 'cause this,
like, can't leave.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Okay, so what really happened is...
Brandt asked to finger me,
and I was like, "can I bring Anna?"
'Cause I was scared,
and then we went into the closet
and he just, like, felt us up.
Just, like, up and down and‐‐
‐ and circles?
‐ yeah.
‐ rumors are, like, so messed up.
I know.
‐ someone once said I have alopecia,
but my hair is, like, so full.
‐ oh, my god. ‐ rumors are crazy.
You have the most beautiful hair.
‐ I know! It's so weird.
‐ it's so not true
'cause your hair is so full. ‐ right?
I love you. ‐ okay, but, like, Maya.
Maya.
I heard you were, like, totally
obsessed with Brandt though.
And, like, you put hair in his locker
and, like, he almost
transferred schools
for a second 'cause you
scared him so bad.
‐ Gina: Stalker.
‐ that's not true! That's crazy.
That's weird. ‐
‐ I don't like him.
I don't like assholes, you guys.
‐ I mean, girls do like assholes.
You can just admit it.
‐ no, but Maya doesn't like assholes.
She‐‐she had a crush on Sam zablowski.
He's not an asshole. ‐ what?
Zablowski? ‐ you and Sam?
‐ Anna! I don't like Sam.
I just liked him for, like‐‐ ‐ not now!
Not now!
‐ I had a crush on him for, like, a day
and then I stopped.
God. ‐ that's right. You stopped.
‐ oh, my god, we should call him.
‐ I don't like him. Fine, call him.
I don't care. ‐ what's
his number then, Maya?
‐ I don't memorize it
'cause I don't like him.
‐ don't call him 'cause
she doesn't like him.
Wait, we should.
Does anyone know his number?
‐ I want in. ‐ I don't like
him so I don't care. Call.
‐ who knows his number? ‐ I want in.
‐ who knows his number?
Does anyone know his number?
Becca, Becca? ‐ Anna might.
I don't know.
Do you know? ‐ do I know? I don't...
‐ hello?
Hi.
It's Becca and Maura.
‐ Maura?
Sam...
How much do you like Maya
on a scale of one to ten?
‐ Maya ishii‐peters? Yeah.
‐ I don't know. Why?
‐ what?
‐ they're just prank calling me.
They wanna know if I like Maya, or...
‐ whatever.
Peace.
Girls.
Secret blood.
‐ come on, you guys, stop.
Let me out. That's not funny.
‐ not until you do bloody Mary.
‐ stop it, you guys. Come on.
Let me out. ‐ do it!
‐ Maya, they'll let you out
when you do bloody Mary.
Yeah.
You guys, stop!
Let me out!
- ‐ do it!
- It's not funny.
Stop it. Come on, you guys.
‐ no, do it! ‐ fine.
Bloody Mary, bloody Mary, bloody Mary.
Let me out! ‐ we can't hear you.
‐ bloody Mary, bloody Mary,
bloody Mary, bloody Mary, bloody Mary!
Let me out!
‐ was that funny, Maya?
Did you see bloody Mary?
‐ yes.
‐ are you actually mad, Maya?
- It was just a joke.
- Yeah.
‐ no. ‐ are you okay? What's wrong?
‐ Anna, I'm good. Anna, stop.
‐ oh, no. ‐ no, stop.
I thought it was funny. It's good.
That was really funny, you guys.
- ‐ are you sure?
- Yes.
Anna, stop asking me.
I'm fine.
What's her problem?
Honestly, I don't know.
‐ are you okay?
‐ yeah, no. I said it's really funny.
I liked it.
‐ I'm talking about Anna.
Like, I love her, like,
so much. ‐ yeah.
But she has the biggest mouth.
I can't believe she told
everyone about Sam.
‐ I mean, honestly, like‐‐ Maura: Yeah.
‐ I agree.
Like, physically, she has a huge mouth.
She can stick anything in it. ‐ what?
‐ like, even her entire fist.
‐ has she done that?
‐ yeah, but shh.
‐ ask Anna to do that right now.
‐ what? Did you say my name?
Yeah. ‐ nothing.
‐ Anna, truth.
Can you stick your entire
fist in your mouth?
Maya said you could. ‐ Maya!
‐ in a funny way, though, I said.
Like, you do it as a joke.
‐ wait, Anna, actually do it.
Do it, do it, do it...
‐ she doesn't have to.
You don't have to.
- Do it.
- Do it, do it.
Seriously, that's disgusting.
‐ oh, my god! Ew!
‐ ugh, there's, like,
saliva all over that.
‐ I know. ‐ oh, my god, you guys.
Gina's already asleep.
‐ she's so tired.
- ‐ it's so early.
- ‐ Gina!
Gina! Arise!
‐ oh, my gosh, you guys, seriously!
I have to sleep.
‐ it wasn't me. It was Maura.
‐ Gina, Gina, Gina, Gina.
Gina, Gina, Gina, Gina. ‐ Maya, stop!
My meet's in, like, four hours. ‐ Gina!
‐ wake up for an hour for my meet.
I'm sorry! ‐ okay, okay, okay.
Shut up. Shut up. Everybody shut up.
Listen. Here's the deal.
Next person who falls asleep is out.
‐ not it. ‐ not it.
‐ not it! ‐ not it.
‐
‐ mm.
‐ she's out.
Sharpie her.
Do it.
‐ shh.
‐
‐ what's the farthest you've gone?
‐ haven't found the lucky lady.
You?
‐ uh, I just got a handy last summer.
‐ you never told me that.
‐ burned my dick off.
Lotion, my friend.
‐ hmm. Good to know.
‐
‐ what is going‐‐maya!
‐ Sorry!
‐ what are you doing? ‐
‐ what are you‐‐ my sleeping bag's wet.
What the hell?
‐ don't be so sensitive.
We're doing it to everyone.
‐ I'm not sensitive.
You're the most sensitive person here.
‐ oh, my god. Sorry.
You were leaving me out all night.
You left me in a bag. Maybe
that's why I'm sensitive.
‐ that wasn't on purpose. Oh, my god.
Are you kidding? ‐ oh, my god.
‐ you leave me out all the time.
And you got my bag wet.
‐ sorry.
That was Maura's idea, not mine.
Sorry. ‐ oh, was it Maura's idea?
Yeah! ‐ where is she?
‐ you literally are obsessed with her.
‐ are you kidding? Wow.
‐ oh, my god, whatever.
Oh, my god, Maura.
‐ she's asleep.
‐ she's out.
‐ She's out.
‐ Maya, shh.
‐
Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
‐ she sleeps with her eyes open.
‐ ew.
My god.
So weird.
‐ do you love Maura more than me?
Be honest.
‐ Maya.
Obviously not.
She's here.
You're here, but above the heavens.
‐ I mean, for me, she's
below the ground
and you're, like, up here.
‐ that's what I'm saying. Same.
Under. ‐ swear?
‐ swear.
I love you.
- ‐ yeah, let's go to bed.
- In your bag?
‐ yeah.
‐ are you sure‐‐ are you
sure you don't mind?
‐ yeah, no, I'm good.
Hey, Anna.
‐ yeah?
‐ the last ones out, aren't we?
‐ yeah.
Do you want me to rub your back?
‐ no, it tickles.
Oh, my back, okay, yeah.
Can you do the long scratches?
‐
You guys!
Wake up!
‐ oh, my god.
Somebody clogged the toilet
and it's brand‐new and super expensive.
‐ what?
Somebody clogged the toilet
and it's brand‐new and super expensive.
- Who was it?
- God.
‐ she's right.
There's a weird pad in there,
so whoever left it has their period.
‐ not it. Not it.
‐ definitely not it.
‐ I bet it's Maya.
‐ What?
‐ I mean, you did go in there last.
‐ it wasn't Maya
'cause we don't have our periods yet.
‐ yeah. We don't.
‐ I mean, Maya, if it was
you, it's totally fine.
We just need to know so we can fix it.
‐ okay, but it's not me
'cause I don't have it,
but what if it was like, Santa came
and, like, literally bled on a pad
and, like, put it in the toilet.
‐ nah, I'm pretty sure it was you.
‐ I don't have my period! Stop.
- ‐ it obviously was though!
- Oh, my god.
Maura, you're being crazy actually.
Stop. ‐ you guys, she
wants her privacy.
‐ guys, stop.
You're being crazy! Stop!
‐ uh, Maura? Your foot's bleeding.
‐ what?
Wait, what?
- Oh, my god!
- Ew!
Ew! Ew! Ew!
‐ ew!
Ew!
‐ is that what you do for a pad?
That's disgusting!
Oh, my god, what is that?
‐ stop.
‐ stop!
Okay, you guys are being really mean!
Stop!
Oh, my god! Stop it!
‐ what?
‐ my blood.
‐ fucking knew it.
Why would you lie to Anna?
That's so fucked up.
‐ I'm not.
‐ come here.
‐ it's gonna be okay, Anna.
It's okay.
‐ Anna, I'm sorry.
‐ I didn't‐‐
I'm so sorry.
That's so fucked up.
We're here for you.
- ‐ we're your friends.
- We love you, Anna.
Hello? ‐ hey, mom.
Maya?
‐ yeah, I'm sorry for calling so late.
What‐‐what's wrong?
‐ nothing. Can you
just come pick me up?
Please?
What's going on?
‐ nothing. I just wanna come home.
Everyone thinks I'm a liar.
‐ no, you're not a liar.
You know, privacy's
different than secret.
‐ no, I know,
but Anna asked and I lied to her
and I feel like...
I don't know, I, like,
clogged Maura's toilet
and everyone thinks I'm disgusting now.
‐ oh, you‐‐listen to me, Maya.
Girls or women are like salad bowls.
You know?
You put everything in one bowl.
Um, like this one here?
This is your...
‐
What? It's not funny.
It's‐‐it's beautiful.
No, I hate it. ‐ it's
a little cute wonder.
And... Ooh, who's that?
What's in here?
Ooh, this is Anna.
You cherish it and keep it.
And you only get to keep
what's most important to you.
Okay?
Because there's not much
room in the salad bowl.
Okay?
What's that?
- ‐ taking things off.
- Ah.
You have a lot of junk
in your bowl, huh?
Oh, what's that?
- ‐ Anna.
- Anna?
Ooh, it's nice.
Okay.
‐ stop taking it off my head.
You wanna keep it there? ‐ yeah.
You wanna keep Anna? ‐ yeah.
Ah, that's good.
‐ even if she hates me.
‐ I'm sure she doesn't.
She will come back.
‐ okay.
‐ yeah.
So let's just cherish it.
Let's keep it. Okay?
‐ mm‐hmm. ‐ hmm?
You're gonna be okay.
‐ okay. ‐ all right?
‐
Hmm?
‐ um, sorry, but I just‐‐
can I have $20?
'Cause, um, Bernard spent
it all on alcohol again.
‐ again? What a cunt.
‐ thanks.
It's kinda weird that
Maya's not here, no?
‐ I mean, like, it'd be
weirder if she was here.
Like, I don't know how
you forgive someone
after lying to you like that.
‐ yeah.
‐ Maya moved to Arizona.
‐ mm.
Yeah.
Bernard.
You just always lie to me.
‐ don't cry. Don't cry.
You want milk, baby?
Milk.
‐
Oh, my god.
Tonia.
Hey.
- ‐ hey. You got your milk?
- Yeah.
Uh, can I have my wallet back now?
‐ oh, yeah. Thanks. I
just borrowed the...
Yeah.
‐ your baby needs you.
Shh. ‐ mm‐hmm.
Mom.
Mom, could you, like, come up here?
‐ Maura...
You said that she was, like, a doctor.
But she's in a body spray ad.
‐ um, can I just have this back?
‐ well, I'm just using it.
‐ Anna. ‐ what?
Right? I mean, you lied. ‐ can I just‐‐
‐ you can just say it. ‐ can I just‐‐
can I just‐‐ give it back please.
‐ no. ‐ Anna.
It's mine.
Mom! Mommy?
Anna.
- Anna, it's mine.
- No.
It's mine! ‐ no.
‐ give it back. ‐ no, you give it back!
‐ no. Mom!
Hey, it's mine.
I'm just gonna‐‐ just let me‐‐ stop.
- Stop.
- Give it back!
- ‐ Maura.
- It's mine!
- Come on! It's mine!
- Maura, no.
- It's mine! Anna!
- No, no, no!
Anna! ‐ just go.
Just‐‐ Maura: No! Mom!
- Mom, no!
- Shh.
It's okay. Calm down.
‐ no! Anna!
Give it‐‐anna!
No, mom, it's mine!
‐ come on. ‐ mom, no!
- Sweetheart, calm.
- Mom.
Just calm.
Calm. Just breathe.
Anna!
That's why I said four
about her, on the phone.
I knew she was not right.
You always know before me.
Like, I'm too trusting.
- I'm too trusting.
- My mom knew too.
And Gina. ‐ I know.
None of them are her real friends.
‐ I knew it. I freaking knew it!
‐ no. Duh. She's a liar.
‐ no, I know, but I am too.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you
about my period, but...
I guess you don't like
me either right now.
‐ honestly, it's something about me.
Like, I just attract liars.
Something that says, like,
you can't trust me.
‐ Anna, it's not always about you.
It's my freaking period!
Like, it was a big
deal and I was like‐‐
I thought it was small
and it would go away,
but it, like‐‐it didn't.
Just comes once a month.
‐ no, you're right.
That's really intense.
‐ it is.
‐ I'm sorry, and I'm
really so happy for you.
My best friend's a woman.
‐ no, I don't wanna be.
‐ why?
‐ I don't know, I guess I'm
just, like, a salad bowl
like every other woman.
‐ mm.
Mm‐hmm, mm‐hmm.
‐ yeah.
Like mushy carrots, you know?
‐ just promise no more secrets.
‐ never. ‐ okay?
- ‐ I swear.
- Swear.
‐ swear. ‐ swear.
Except I did throw away
one of your library books
'cause I spilled sprite on it.
‐ Maya, that could affect my credit.
‐ I know. Sorry.
And also, when you're not around,
I go through your underwear drawer
and try on every pair
with flowers on them.
‐ over or under yours?
‐ under. ‐
‐ also, I drew that goatee on your face
and there's still a
little bit on there.
‐ you did that? ‐ yeah.
I also joined wrestling
because of Brandt,
not 'cause I wanted to
be a strong wrestler.
Also when my mom buys potatoes,
I put them in my shirt
and I walk around like this with boobs.
Also I have a book of crushes
and one of them is your dad.
‐ ew, Maya! ‐ I just‐‐
also I sometimes touch
myself down there
in a way that I told you about,
but in a different
way, not for comfort.
I have a secret screen name
where I talk to old men,
and I'm talking to one right now.
I also shave my mustache sometimes.
- Shuji's my half brother.
- What?
But we're basically full.
That's probably it.
‐ I got a pencil mark
on your bed cover once.
It was about this big,
and I didn't tell you.
‐ Anna! ‐ that has been killing me.
‐ why would you do
that and not tell me?
‐ I feel so much better.
‐ ugh, that's, like, kind of annoying.
♪ Unbounded by languor or longitude ♪