[calming music]
♪ ♪
YUKI:
Maya?
Maya.
‐ Hmm.
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ How's Anna?
‐ Okay.
YUKI: How is she dealing
with her parents?
‐ Okay.
You normally talk more.
What's wrong?
‐ Everyone hates me at school.
♪ ♪
I don't wanna talk about it.
‐ You care always about
what the others are thinking.
Who cares
what the others think?
Neh?
‐ Okay.
♪ ♪
‐ So we're just‐‐we're waiting.
The court has to decide
who's gonna get the house.
[sighs]
Fingers crossed.
Let's hope that, uh, the judge
does the right thing.
Is that too much information?
Oh.
You have a lot of heart energy
in there.
Anna?
You need to open up.
ANNA:
Okay, sorry.
♪ ♪
KATHY:
Hey.
How 'bout‐‐
how 'bout we do, um...
a mother‐daughter day?
We get our nails done,
and we go shopping.
‐ Can I please be excused?
‐ Yeah.
♪ ♪
‐ Please put the incense out.
It's weird.
♪ ♪
[students chatting]
[bell rings]
ANNA:
Tweedledee and Tweedledum.
Wonder what those idiots
are talking about.
‐ [laughs]
ANNA: Kinda miss 'em.
MAYA: Yeah.
STUDENT: Due Friday.
‐ Oh, shite.
Superlatives.
‐ Oh, my God.
Not now.
[sighs]
‐ Shit, Best Duo?
Connie's tits.
[laughter]
‐ Shut up.
She's right beside you.
HEATHER: That was, like,
the worst joke.
‐ It's just a joke, chill.
‐ What's up, Brandt?
‐ What's up?
BRANDT: What's up, bro?
‐ Dustin, Best Couple?
Me and your mom.
[laughter]
ALL: Oh!
‐ For real, though.
‐ 'Scuse you.
‐ Brandt, what about you
and BSB for Best Couple?
‐ Shit.
HEATHER: Okay, okay.
What about Miss Lackey
when she gets her braces off?
‐ Yeah.
For sure.
Man, that's fucked up.
ALEX: Biggest gossip.
HEATHER: Oh, definitely Ian.
CONNIE: Definitely.
HEATHER: Yes.
BRANDT:
Yeah, Connie's mom, bro.
DUSTIN: Oh!
CONNIE: Shut up!
Shut up!
‐ Yo, she got a MILF!
[laughter]
‐ She definitely has a MILF.
‐ No, stop.
‐ 'Sup?
‐ Is that your new table?
‐ Nah, that's just‐‐
Brandt was just saying
that he's gonna vote
for Connie M.'s tits
for Best Duo
and then Ian for Class Gossip.
‐ Why would that go to Ian?
‐ I don't know.
They said he was gay, so...
[indistinct chatter]
GABE:
So are you, like, resigning
as editorial manager
of Weasels?
‐ You guys still doing that?
‐ [scoffs]
Damn.
‐ What?
‐ You're kinda different.
DUSTIN:
What?
Jafeer, come on.
Don't be so fucking sensitive.
[reflective music]
♪ ♪
‐ [speaking indistinctly]
ANNA:
Ugh, I hate this question.
Like, what is success,
you know?
So stupid.
‐ Okay, well, obviously,
you and me
for Best Best Friends.
[laughing]
Obviously.
‐ Hey, quick question.
I'm struggling here.
‐ Oh, sure.
‐ Would you wanna be put down
as "psycho bitch"
or "puss‐nasty"?
[quickly]
Big smelly bush say what?
‐ What?
‐ [laughs]
‐ Oh, "big smelly bush"?
How 'bout you get Smallest Dick
Most Likely to Have
the Saggiest Balls
In His Dad's Mouth?
Fool.
Bye!
‐ Hey.
‐ Hi.
‐ Oh, my God!
‐ Oh, Ring Pops.
‐ Maura.
‐ Hi.
MAURA:
Hi!
That's funny,
I put that one too.
That one's wrong.
That should be Spencer.
‐ Oh, I know.
‐ Yeah.
That's what‐‐
‐ Maya said Spencer.
‐ I said Spencer earlier.
‐ [laughs]
ANNA:
I love your pants.
I love them.
‐ Thanks.
They're 7 Jeans.
I hate knockoffs.
‐ I hate knockoffs too.
‐ Me too.
‐ I wish that they had
a category for Best Pants.
It's, like, so annoying
that they don't.
‐ I know.
‐ I'm gonna write it in.
‐ For who?
‐ For her.
‐ Oh, obviously.
‐ [laughs]
Thanks.
Wanna come over to my house
after school?
[refined music]
ANNA:
Oh, my God.
MAURA:
You should take this one.
It would be perfect on you.
ANNA: Oh, yeah.
MAYA:
Wait, are these car keys real?
ANNA:
This is incredible.
‐ Take what you want.
It's all for pretend.
ANNA: Where'd you get
that cell phone?
MAYA: Oh, my God.
ANNA: Is this real diamonds?
MAURA:
I think so.
ANNA: [gasps]
I love this.
‐ So, I'm Alison Canning,
and my husband is a banker,
and this is my son Danny.
‐ [laughing]
Okay.
And I'm Isabel,
and this is my daughter Kate,
and her father's been missing.
‐ Oh, no.
‐ Okay, and I'm Bonnie,
and this is Robert,
and I have to go to Blockbuster
because my other son,
Ascrit, is there
and he's just been there alone
for hours,
so I gotta pick him up.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ Now, yeah.
‐ Maya.
‐ I know.
‐ Guys, let's eat lunch
at Cazzio's.
BOTH: Okay.
‐ What's Cazzio's?
‐ Uh, it's, like, a restaurant.
MAYA: Cazzio's!
‐ Maya and I play pretend too,
but not everybody does.
BOTH: Yeah.
MAURA: Hang on.
MAYA: Okay.
‐ Mom, turn the AC on.
I'm hot.
All right.
ANNA: That's an intercom?
MAURA: Yeah.
‐ That's cool.
‐ You guys.
‐ Hmm?
‐ Um...I'm just having
the hardest time with Bernard.
‐ [gasps]
No.
MAURA:
Aww.
‐ Listen, do you want me
to get Wade to talk to him?
Because honestly, like,
I need a break from him
'cause he just keeps wanting
to have so much sex
all the time.
‐ Oh, my gosh.
‐ It's, like, so much,
you guys.
‐ It's, like, the same
with my husband.
‐ Mine too.
‐ Mine's more, though.
A lot.
‐ Mm.
ANNA: Mm.
MAURA: Mm.
MAYA:
Mm.
‐ Are you guys hungry?
‐ No, I've got
my chicken cacciatore.
[both laugh]
‐ No, I mean,
like, in real life.
Like, actually hungry.
‐ Yeah.
[hip‐hop music]
♪ ♪
‐ I know.
[both laugh]
MAYA: It's kinda crazy
that we've just met,
like, ten minutes ago
and now we're just
in your house
like it's been forever.
‐ So random.
MAURA: So random.
ANNA: So random.
‐ [laughs]
‐ Fools.
‐ Yeah, fools.
‐ Fool.
Fool.
‐ So who's even in
your group of friends?
Like...
‐ Yeah.
‐ I kinda have, like, a lot.
‐ That makes sense.
‐ Like who?
Like, who's in your group?
‐ Well, I have this ultimate,
ultimate best friend,
but she's in Arizona,
but, like, she's a doctor.
‐ Shut up!
MAURA:
Yeah, and she's, like, our age.
She's, like, the youngest
in the country.
‐ You're lying.
MAURA: No, I'm not!
‐ How is she a doctor?
ANNA: Is she a genius?
‐ Yeah.
‐ That's, like, crazy.
MAURA: Right?
‐ Can I, like, see a picture?
‐ Yeah.
ANNA: That is incredible.
MAYA:
[laughs]
MAURA: That's her.
‐ Oh...
ANNA: Oh, my God.
MAYA: My God.
MAURA: That's Tanya.
MAYA: She's so pretty.
‐ I know, right?
ANNA: Beautiful.
MAYA: Oh, my God.
‐ She has, like,
three mansions too.
MAYA: Wow.
‐ How'd she get those?
LEANNE:
Hi, girls.
ANNA: Oh, hey!
MAYA: Hi.
‐ Hey.
I'm Leanne.
I'm Maura's mom.
‐ Oh, hi.
I'm Anna.
‐ Anna.
So nice to meet you.
ANNA: Nice to meet you.
‐ I'm Maya.
‐ Hi, Maya.
So glad you're here.
Can I get you girls a drink?
I have...
Powerade, ginger ale,
Capri Sun‐‐
MAYA:
Yes.
Powerade, please?
‐ Of course.
How many?
‐ Three.
‐ Maya.
‐ What?
‐ No.
MAYA: It's fine.
‐ Anna?
‐ Okay, yeah.
‐ Come on.
‐ Yes, please.
‐ Did you hear what she said?
‐ Of course.
ANNA: Three.
‐ Anna.
‐ [whispering]
What?
‐ You just said‐‐
LEANNE: Okay.
MAYA: Yeah.
‐ Okay, sorry.
Here we go.
‐ Thank you.
MAYA: Thank you.
‐ Mom, leave.
‐ I will.
I just wanna see
if your friends would like
something to eat.
Frozen pizza, chicken nuggets,
mozzarella sticks...
‐ Mom.
LEANNE: Or I can make you guys
a quesadilla.
Honey, quesadilla.
‐ I don't want
a fucking quesadilla, you cunt.
‐ Sweetie, um...
you're being such a bad fairy.
‐ Shwoo!
‐ Okay.
Okay!
Um, I will, uh,
get out of your way,
but please help yourself
to whatever.
I buy in bulk, so...
ANNA:
Oh, thank you.
‐ Thank you.
‐ I'm so sorry about that.
She just really misses Tonia.
‐ Oh, no.
Who's Tonia?
‐ My best friend.
‐ The doctor.
MAURA: Yeah.
‐ That she just showed us.
ANNA: Yes.
‐ From Arizona.
‐ Yes.
MAURA: Yeah.
‐ Like...
‐ [laughs]
Doy.
‐ Wait.
Are those jawbreakers?
MAURA:
Yeah, fool.
You want some?
[Alexia's "Happy"]
ALEXIA:
♪ Happy ♪
♪ Sha‐la‐la ♪
♪ It's so nice to be happy ♪
♪ Everybody should be happy ♪
♪ Sha‐la‐la ♪
♪ It's so nice to be happy ♪
‐ Hey, fool.
MAYA: [laughs]
‐ What you looking at, fool?
[laughter]
[laughing]
Oh, my gosh, Maya!
‐ [moaning]
‐ Hey, fools.
[laughs]
ALEXIA:
♪ Everybody should be happy ♪
[shady music]
♪ ♪
‐ Oh, hey.
Do you know
who you're gonna vote for
for Best Best Friends?
‐ Um, I don't know.
I haven't thought about it.
‐ Well, me, Maya, and Anna
have been best friends
since we were, like, two,
and I think
it'd be pretty fucked up
to not vote for what's real.
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ You want a Ring Pop?
‐ Um, sure.
MAURA:
Just think about it.
♪ ♪
Oh, hey.
Do you know
who you're gonna vote for
for Best Best Friends?
♪ ♪
‐ Hi!
MAURA:
Hi!
Oh, are you Anna's mom?
Oh, my God, you are so pretty!
Where are you guys going?
Can I come?
‐ [gasps]
Yes. Please?
‐ Uh, you're very sweet,
but not today.
I have the massage table.
Car's full.
‐ Oh, that's totally fine.
I can just sit on their laps!
KATHY: No.
‐ Yes, she can sit on our laps.
Please? Oh, my God.
‐ Anna, Anna, no.
‐ Mom!
‐ I'm attached to them.
‐ Yeah.
KATHY: No.
Anna, no.
‐ Mom, stop being such a fool.
KATHY: Anna Kone!
BOTH: Ooh.
‐ Who's a fool now, fool?
‐ Yeah, fool.
‐ Fool.
‐ I'm a fool, fool?
MAYA: Yeah, you're a fool.
MAYA: You're a fool.
BOTH: Foo‐fool‐foo‐foo‐fool.
‐ [laughs]
‐ Okay, you guys, can you just
stop saying "fool"?
MAURA: You're all fools.
‐ Mom, it's just a stupid word,
you cunt.
‐ What?
What did you just call me?
Do you even know
what that means?
That's the worst thing
you can call a woman.
‐ I thought it was
a type of fool.
‐ Who's teaching you
these words?
‐ I can't remember.
‐ [in English accent]
I cunt remember.
‐ [laughs]
MAYA:
It's an English accent!
‐ Okay, you know what?
Um, you really need
to get out of the car
'cause we're gonna go.
‐ No, no.
‐ Aww, no!
‐ Please?
Mm?
‐ I love you guys.
ANNA: Love you.
‐ Love you more!
MAURA: Bye.
MAYA: Bye.
‐ Love you.
BOTH: Love you.
‐ I miss you already.
‐ I'm gonna miss you.
‐ Miss you.
MAURA: No!
‐ No!
‐ [screams]
MAURA: Love you guys!
MAYA: Love you!
MAURA:
You're my world!
KATHY:
I'm just kinda concerned.
She's been using new words,
and I don't think
she really knows
what they mean.
Um, I thought maybe
it might be a good time
to do a mother‐daughter
shopping day,
and I thought if Maya came,
she'd be more open?
‐ We really don't need
anything, but...
‐ Fool, fool, fool, fool, fool,
fool, fool, fool, fool, fool...
‐ Okay.
ANNA:
Maura would hate this store.
‐ Okay, not loaded.
‐ Not loaded.
That is loaded, though.
I agree.
‐ We don't like it.
‐ Yeah, I don't like it.
Ew.
Anna.
‐ Ew, is that made of hay?
MAYA: [laughing]
Ew!
ANNA: Wow.
MAYA: Ew.
ANNA:
This place.
KATHY:
Anna.
Is there anyone
you have a crush on at school?
‐ No.
Oh, my God.
‐ What?
‐ This is butt ugly.
‐ [laughing]
Oh, no!
‐ Oh, that's nice.
‐ Mom, it's so ugly.
Like...ew.
‐ It's here if you want it.
MAYA:
So not loaded.
Stupid.
‐ Not loaded.
‐ So when are we going to meet
this Maura girl?
‐ Mom, like, don't ask us that.
‐ It seems you three
are really close very fast.
‐ Yeah, that's what happens
when they're your best friend.
It's, like, yeah, fast.
That's how best friendships
happen.
‐ [gasps]
Oh, my God.
‐ Tommy Hilfiger.
‐ Wait.
It's fake.
‐ No, I don't think so.
ANNA:
This is fake Tommy Hil.
‐ This is real.
Look.
It's real.
‐ It's big, though, no?
‐ I don't think so.
I kind of think it's perfect.
‐ That's loaded.
‐ ♪ That's loaded,
loaded, loaded ♪
‐ That's not loaded, loaded.
♪ That's loaded ♪
‐ ♪ Loaded ♪
♪ It's loaded ♪
MAYA: ♪ Everybody get down ♪
BOTH:
♪ It's loaded, loaded, loaded ♪
MAYA: I really like
how this looks on me.
I wanna get it.
YUKI: Maya.
‐ Mom, stop.
Someone is gonna see my boobs.
YUKI: Ah, it's‐‐it's okay.
‐ Like, knock.
Oh, my God.
YUKI: [speaks Japanese]
‐ I love it.
‐ No, it's not nice.
It's a T‐shirt.
It's men's T‐shirt.
‐ Mom, that you wear
as a dress.
Wore it as a‐‐
‐ As a dress?
‐ Yeah, wore it as a‐‐
all the time.
‐ [speaking Japanese]
‐ Okay, fine.
You don't have to like it.
‐ [speaking Japanese]
I'm buying it for you, so no.
‐ Okay, but Mom, I want it.
[whispering]
I like it.
‐ No.
Maybe you can give it to Anna
because she's taller.
‐ Mom, stop.
I don't wanna give it to Anna.
Let me wear it.
‐ I'm not buying it.
‐ Mom, stop.
‐ No, I'm not.
‐ Stop it, stop it.
‐ Maya, stop.
Maya, stop‐‐take it off.
MAYA: Mom, please.
‐ Take it off.
MAYA: Stop touching it!
‐ Mom, stop it!
‐ It looks so good on you.
You should get it.
For Easter.
‐ No, it's just not me.
I don't like it.
It's more you.
‐ What's wrong with me?
ANNA:
Nothing.
It's just not me.
It's kinda slutty.
‐ What did you say?
YUKI: Anna?
‐ [whispering]
Nothing.
I'm just saying I don't‐‐
[knocks]
YUKI: Anna.
This is for you.
KATHY: Oh, thank you.
ANNA: Thank you.
KATHY:
What did you just call me?
‐ [whispering]
I didn't call you anything.
Can you stop yelling?
My best friend is‐‐
‐ Why are you talking to me
like that?
Why?
‐ Shh!
Lower your voice.
‐ I'm not yelling.
I'm whispering.
Why are you telling me
to be quiet?
Why are you shh‐ing me?
Did you learn that
from your dad?
‐ I'd rather be like Dad
than like you.
MAYA: Are you ready, Na?
ANNA: Coming!
MAYA:
I'm trying to look at it.
ANNA:
Ready.
[Muzak playing]
♪ ♪
‐ I hate it.
‐ But you look so beautiful,
Maya.
You look like your mother.
‐ No, I don't...
...look anything like her.
She's ugly.
KATHY:
Don't say that.
That's really not a nice thing
to say.
Your mother
is a beautiful woman.
‐ Thank you.
‐ And you are very lucky
to look like her.
‐ I don't look like her,
and I don't like this dress.
I never wanted to wear it,
and I want to take it off.
‐ Stop, Maya.
You're being rude.
‐ No, I don't like it.
You don't know my taste, Mom.
‐ Stop.
Stop.
Maya, stop.
‐ Mom, I don't wanna buy it!
I wanted to buy
the other thing.
YUKI: Stop it.
Stop acting
like a little spoiled bitch.
♪ ♪
‐ Thank you for saying that,
Yuki.
‐ Okay.
‐ Anna's doing the same thing.
‐ Oh, my God, Mom.
Mature much?
‐ Mom.
Are you serious?
You just called your daughter
a bitch,
in a store,
in front of my friend.
Do you know
how embarrassing that is?
‐ I don't care.
You know,
you are acting like one.
‐ Well, I hate you, you bitch!
‐ [gasps]
‐ I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
No, stop!
‐ I'm gonna stop...
[speaking Japanese]
‐ Mommy, stop it!
‐ [whispering]
Mom, look what you're causing.
‐ Oh.
Oh, right.
Everything's my fault.
‐ Yeah, it's your fault.
‐ Okay, you need to stop.
‐ Leave me alone!
MAYA: Mom!
YUKI: Maya.
‐ Okay, I'm calling 9‐1‐1
and Daddy!
‐ Like, this is what you do
to Daddy.
Blame him for everything
and then you're just like‐‐
you're such a...
‐ What?
‐ You're‐‐
KATHY: Just say it.
‐ A cunt.
MAYA:
Stop, stop, stop!
Stop!
YUKI:
[speaking Japanese]
‐ Mom, you're embarrassing me!
You're embarrassing me!
‐ You too, okay?
‐ [sobbing]
‐ I mean,
I think it looks stupid
with jeans, but...
ANNA:
I think it looks really good.
I don't know why
you didn't wear it as a dress,
but it still looks good.
‐ Thanks for getting it for me.
ANNA:
Of course.
‐ Are you okay?
ANNA: No.
My mom's, like, so pissed.
All night.
She's so pissed.
TERRA:
Maura.
It's great.
Thank you.
[laughs]
ANNA: What about you?
Is your mom, like‐‐
did you guys make up?
‐ I mean, no.
You saw what my mom did.
Like, that was so crazy.
‐ What did she do?
MAYA:
Don't.
[whispering]
Tell her.
ANNA: I'm not.
It was...
a shopping trip gone bad.
‐ So now you didn't invite me
and you don't tell me stuff.
Cool.
‐ I‐‐sorry.
I'm sorry.
That's not what I meant.
Maura.
‐ Maura, are you serious?
Are you joking?
‐ Maura, come on!
PRINCIPAL: Teachers,
please don't park
in the bus turnaround.
Seems obvious.
But apparently, it's not.
And the results
we've all been waiting for‐‐
here are
the superlative winners.
[clears throat]
Most Likely to Succeed...
ANNA: Maura.
PRINCIPAL: Ashley Stewart.
‐ Maura.
ANNA: Maura.
[operatically]
♪ Maura, Maura, Maura ♪
‐ ♪ Maur, Maur, Maur‐Maur ♪
‐ ♪ Maura ♪
‐ ♪ Maur, Maur, Maur ♪
[laughs]
Stop.
PRINCIPAL: Most Athletic Boy
goes to Joey Roberts.
Best Couple: Heather Taylor
and Alex Nolan.
‐ You guys,
they actually just broke up.
‐ [sighs]
I can't keep up.
PRINCIPAL:
For Class Gossip, Ian Walsh.
And Best Best Friends
goes to Anna Kone
and Maya Ishii‐Peters‐‐
MAYA: Oh!
PRINCIPAL: And Maura Hall.
Most Musical goes to...
‐ [gasps]
BOTH: Oh, my God!
Maura!
‐ Three best friends!
There's the smile.
MAYA: There she is.
There's the happy smile.
‐ I knew we were gonna get it.
‐ Wait, how did we get
three best friends?
That's crazy.
‐ Dude, people just know.
ANNA: We are.
BOTH: Yeah.
‐ Guess we'll have to take
pictures.
‐ I mean, you guys!
‐ Bow down, fools.
[laughter]
MAYA: Fools.
ANNA: Yeah, fools.
[laughter]
Oh, my God.
MAYA: Wait, that's cute.
That blue one.
MAURA: Mm, nah.
MAYA: Nah.
‐ I'm just gonna say,
if we're gonna match
for the superlatives picture,
we don't have a lot of options.
‐ My good stuff's
somewhere else, I feel like.
‐ Wait, is this Limited Too?
ANNA: Oh.
‐ That's so loaded.
‐ Maya, I didn't know
you have Limited Too.
‐ No, it's‐‐it's The Rave.
BOTH:
Oh.
‐ Try to get it.
We have arms.
[laughter]
MAYA: Wait.
MAURA: Try to get it.
Try to get it.
‐ Okay, I have an arm too.
BOTH:
Try to get it.
‐ No, Maya,
you don't have an arm.
you don't have arms.
‐ Okay, you guys, stop.
You're stretching out my shirt.
Stop.
‐ What else do you have
in here?
‐ It's my favorite shirt.
‐ Dude, you have,
like, nothing here, Maya.
Like, I swear.
ANNA:
Oh, what about this one?
‐ No, fool!
‐ This...
‐ Okay, can I have an arm?
‐ No.
You're in the middle.
‐ [sighs]
This isn't funny, you guys.
Stop.
This is actually, like,
not fun right now.
‐ Chillax, Maya.
God.
‐ Maya, chill.
MAURA: Stop being so sensitive.
‐ I'm not being sensitive.
I just want an arm.
You guys are being
really annoying.
MAURA:
Whatever.
‐ Okay, have fun with arms.
MAURA: What is this?
Like, a fishing net?
[both laugh]
YUKI:
What?
What's wrong?
‐ Mom.
YUKI:
What?
‐ What?
‐ Is it Maura?
‐ No.
I love her.
MAYA:
Stop!
Stop looking at me!
‐ Are they being nice to you?
‐ Mom, yes!
They're being nice to me!
They're my best friends!
You don't know anything!
Why are you freaking like this?
‐ Maya?
‐ [laughs]
‐ Nothing is working in here.
‐ It's faulty!
‐ [sighs]
‐ You okay?
‐ Can you not use my gum,
please?
‐ Okay!
‐ Sorry.
I'm trying to save that
for my birthday.
‐ Why?
It's just gum.
‐ Mom, go.
Please.
Go!
‐ Mom, stop.
Can you go?
‐ Mom, please, go.
It's fine.
‐ Then tell her to clean it up.
MAYA: Okay.
YUKI: I don't like it.
‐ Okay, okay, okay!
Go.
MAYA: Mom, it's fine.
Leave.
ANNA: We'll clean it up.
Sorry.
Oh, my gosh.
[laughs]
‐ Maya, your mom has, like...
[laughing]
A scary accent.
‐ My mom doesn't have
an accent.
‐ [laughing]
Are you kidding me?
She has, like,
the thickest accent
I've ever heard.
‐ No, she doesn't.
ANNA: I just don't think
you hear it
because she's your mom.
MAYA: Anna.
‐ But I like it.
‐ You guys, my mom
doesn't have an accent.
That's, like, a really
mean thing of you to say.
Like, you guys are being
really rude.
‐ Dude, I'm not trying
to be rude.
I'm just saying, she has an‐‐
‐ Well, can you please,
like, clean up the clothes?
'Cause you're making
a really big mess.
‐ Okay, but, I mean,
you were doing it too.
‐ Not as much as you, Maura.
Like‐‐
ANNA: Guys, don't‐‐
‐ Yeah, you were.
‐ Don't fight!
Please, please.
Just remember, like,
we are three best friends.
‐ You're so right, Anna.
I'm sorry.
ANNA:
Remember that.
‐ You guys are my number ones.
Maya.
ANNA: Maya.
‐ Love you fools.
[laughs]
‐ Love you.
[bell rings]
‐ I had a really weird dream
last night about Maura.
I was like‐‐
it felt like I had something
stuck in my throat
and I was, like, pulling
and pulling and pulling
and it was, like, Maura's hair
stuck in my lungs.
Like, it kept coming out.
‐ Ew.
You have an amazing brain.
MAURA:
Hi!
BOTH:
MAURA: Hi, fools.
How you doing?
‐ Good.
MAURA: [laughs]
Best Best Friends!
‐ Whoo!
‐ Yes!
‐ Yes.
‐ I'm really excited.
ANNA: I'm really proud.
‐ [hacks]
MAURA:
So excited.
So, my mom went ahead
and got us a little something.
ANNA:
What?
MAYA:
[gasps]
Shut up.
‐ [gasps]
I was gonna say,
I love your hat.
We were supposed to be matching
and you're not matching.
Oh, my God.
‐ Oh, my God.
You got this?
‐ Is this felt?
MAURA: No, it's Angora.
ANNA: Oh, no, I know.
I love Angora.
‐ They look so good
on you guys.
Do you like it, Maya?
‐ Yeah, it just doesn't fit.
Can you‐‐
MAURA:
It looks really good like that.
MAYA: Oh, okay.
‐ Let's just‐‐yeah.
‐ Thank you.
‐ How?
‐ We need to look good.
We're gonna be looking at this
when we're 40.
PHOTOGRAPHER:
All right, Best Best Friends?
MAURA: That's us.
‐ Get ready.
‐ Oh, wait.
Hang on.
There's something else.
‐ What?
‐ Maura!
You're so nice.
‐ No, no, open it.
Open it.
‐ Oh.
‐ [gasps]
MAURA:
They're friendship necklaces.
ANNA:
Oh, my God.
‐ It's three
and it makes a heart.
I have the middle piece.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ [gasps]
MAURA: I know!
‐ Incredible.
MAYA:
It says "best friends forever."
‐ Yeah.
Put it on.
It'll look really good
for the picture.
[laughs]
ANNA: I like them together.
MAYA: Yeah, I like it.
‐ Actually,
that might be kinda weird.
With two.
‐ Oh, right.
Sorry.
Yeah, stupid.
MAURA: Yeah.
Just the one.
ANNA: Oh, yeah.
Okay, JK.
Just put it safely there.
‐ Kay.
[laughs]
Let's go.
[Vitamin C's "Smile"]
♪ ♪
Oh, uh, Maya,
I might wanna go in the middle
'cause, like, I have
the middle piece.
‐ Oh.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Well, I‐‐okay.
‐ Okay.
First pose!
‐ Oh.
‐ Okay.
Hold on.
‐ Charlie's Angels!
‐ Okay, wait.
‐ Oh, wait.
‐ Look hot, guys.
SINGER: ♪ The way that
you want it to ♪
‐ Um‐‐
‐ Necklaces!
‐ Okay.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Kay.
‐ Oh, my God.
Okay.
‐ Won't fit without mine!
Best friends forever!
SINGER: ♪ Put a smile
on your face ♪
♪ Make the world
a better place ♪
♪ Put a smile on your face ♪
♪ Whatcha gonna do, say,
whatcha gonna do ♪
♪ Put a smile on your face ♪
KATHY: I'm telling you,
a new Anna.
[line beeps]
Like she's possessed.
‐ Hold on.
Call waiting.
[line beeps]
[clicks]
Hello?
KATHY:
Still Kathy.
‐ Oh.
[clicks]
Hello?
Yuki.
LEANNE:
Hey, it's Leanne.
Just wanna say thanks
for being so good to Maura.
‐ Oh, Maura's mom.
I'm just talking
with Anna's mom, Kathy.
Maybe let's all talk.
Uh, hold on.
I'll get‐‐
Let's see.
[clicks]
Kathy?
LEANNE: No.
It's just Leanne.
‐ Oh, shit.
[clicks]
[line beeping]
[sighs]
SINGER:
♪ [indistinct lyrics] ♪
♪ Love it when you smile ♪
♪ You look beautiful
like that ♪
♪ [indistinct lyrics] ♪
♪ Your dimples are so cute ♪
[laughs]
♪ ♪
♪ I love the happiness and...
smile ♪