Wait, look, look.
- Mr. O's underwear sticking out.
- Oh, my God!
I would like put my head in the butt part
and I would wear it on my face
as a mask to fall asleep.
All right, settle down,
settle down, people.
All right, it's Monday.
We got a lot to get through.
But first and foremost is signing up for
your mandatory community service project.
More like community suck-vice.
I doubt that you will be saying that
when you hear these
extremely cool options.
OK, Sam's dad is delivering
meals to the homeless.
PB&J making party at my house!
Yeah... all right.
There's a river trash pick up.
- You can scrape gum off the bridge.
- That one.
And finally, Heather's mom...
is hosting a fashion show
at the nursing home. Huh?
OK, now I am so excited.
Sign up sheets are in the hallway.
OK, go now! Go, go, go!
Calmly! No running!
Maya Ishii-Peters, sign it!
No!
No, I'm getting in.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
Guys, guys, stop it, stop it.
It's my mom, not yours, OK? It's my mom.
Yes!
Personal space. Is it your mom?
- I don't think so.
- Maya, we're gonna be supermodels.
Litter and say bye to nature
as we know it.
Here. Pass this around.
She's at that group. Go ask her.
Spending time with the elderly
- can be so rewarding.
- Mm-hmm.
Whenever Heather and I
visit her grandma in the home,
I think to myself,
no one else even notices
these people besides us.
So true, you guys!
I mean, some of these older people
haven't been noticed in 40, 50 years.
Yeah. So let's fix that.
Now what turns heads more than a big,
beautiful hat?
Almost nothing.
Oh, my God. That's so true. Wow!
Luckily, I have my own new line of hats...
- Deb's Darling Designs.
- Aw!
- Oh, my God!
- Holy shit!
And each of you will be wearing one of
my creations as you walk the runway
with one of Franklin County's
most forgotten old people...
Hey, um, why aren't you
in your boyfriend's group?
She can't leave her best friend.
Excuse me. Can you please
go back to your own circle?
Go!
Anyway, as I was saying.
The actual fashion show is on Saturday...
...but we'II have
two rehearsals before that
to make sure you're good at modeling.
The first rehearsal is tomorrow afternoon.
Heather, don't speak over me, sweetie.
So, please. This is essential.
Bring a professional photo
of yourself to the rehearsal.
Headshots at the mall after school
- so we get the best hats.
- Yay!
So where... where are you guys
meeting at the...
Should we meet at the Orange Julius?
Or like...
Oh, we actually already have reservations.
Cool, so do we so...
- Sorry.
- Yeah, I know we can't come either.
It's fine.
- Well, bye, you guys. Whatever.
- Bye, see you guys tomorrow.
- I have a plan.
- OK, what?
There's a spot right near my house
and I feel like our pictures
will look exactly like theirs.
- Promise?
- I pinky promise.
So... what's the plan?
Oh, you are still here?
Oh, my gosh, I knew yours
was gonna be beautiful. Great.
Oh, so nice. And you know, tomorrow,
our next rehearsal,
you'll be meeting your mature partners!
Won't that be fun?
Jeez!
OK... These photos are just incredible.
So beautiful.
The zig-zaggy part is so cute
and so is your eye shadow.
- Oh, my God, you guys.
- Oh, my God.
I think your mothers
knew what they were doing,
they got you dressed up.
Oh, my God! That lip-shade!
- Can I borrow that?
- Yes!
Anna, you look so pretty!
Aw. Thanks.
Huh.
Anna, what... what?
I don't know what that is in your photo.
- That's a fan
- It's a fan.
OK, you know normally if you want
that kind of the airbrush look,
you don't keep the fan in.
Um, thank you for the note.
I don't know what you're doing here, Maya.
You know, you almost
look like you were missing
and I know you're not
because you're right there.
But I wouldn't even put that.
Honestly I wouldn't even put that
on a milk carton.
Thank you for the note.
So, Terra, you know,
she looks like she's from the 1800s.
But it's on modern paper
and that... that matters.
I found that dress in the river.
OK, so let's go try out our outfits.
OK? Yay!
I can basically see my reflection
in your lip-gloss.
- You look so cute!
- So shiny!
Oh, my God!
- Do you have any lip-gloss?
- What?
Thanks for letting me borrow these shoes,
Heather Feather.
Duh, babe.
- Oh, my God!
- What?
- Heather's wearing a thong.
- Oh, my God, no way.
Yeah.
Do I recognize that pink top,
Miss Rebecca?
Um, yeah, Heather let me borrow it.
Um, Heather do you have a pink tank
that I could borrow?
Because I lost mine.
Um... I'm sorry I'm not really allowed to
let people borrow my clothes.
You know, sometimes people lose them.
That's cool like we can buy some
'cause we have...
- Money.
Yeah.
OK, you three...
can... can you come over here
for a second, doll?
- You three...
- Yeah?
OK can you, um, look more like
the other girls with your outfits?
You know because I'd like
the outfits to be
more uniform to match the hats.
Uh-huh.
My hats can do a lot of work
but they can't, you know, do everything.
So, can we jus... There we go.
Like, just... yeah.
- Like this?
- You know, back, back, back,
there we go.
- Jess, you got the best hat.
- Oh, thank you,
but Heather definitely got the best hat.
It is quite flattering for me.
- It's just so... oh, so amazing.
- Your hat, like,
- match matched your hair.
- So cute.
Guys, do you want to see
my grandma's room?
- Duh, yes!
- Oh, my God!
There's actually, like, not enough room
for everyone so...
Um...
Ooh, how about raise your hand
if you've been to Heather's house before?
That's who can come.
When?
Girl Scouts in second grade.
Follow me, guys.
- Great idea, Becca.
- Thanks. I know, right?
Your hat matched your hair.
What?
Look in there.
- Oh, my God. I know.
- This is what they were using.
No!
Oh... my...
- Wait. Why did she take that off?
- I don't know.
Wait, I dare you to try it on.
What? I dare you.
I triple dog dare you.
- Yeah!
- This is... Oh, my God!
- Wait.
- Shh!
I can't say no to a triple dog dare.
I can do it.
Wait, block me.
- Oh, my...
- Put it on, put it on.
Put it on, put it on.
Oh, my God! How does it feel?
- Crazy.
- My God. Let me see. Turn around.
- Wait, I wanna try it on!
- Ow!
Wait, I wanna try it on.
Let me try it on.
- Stop. Stop.
- No, I wanna try it. Let me!
- Oh, my God!
- Heather, stop!
Put your pants on.
Someone's coming here...
- Stop moving.
- Stop.
Stop.
Good one, Heather.
Your mom's honking outside.
- OK.
- Thanks, Becca.
- You're welcome.
- Wait, Anna, Anna, Anna.
Why are your pants off?
- They weren't.
- Oh, here, that was so fun.
- Yeah.
I had a great time.
OK.
See you tomorrow.
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
- I can't believe that happened.
I didn't mean to steal.
I'm gonna give back to her tomorrow
- after I wash it. Yeah.
- No, no, no.
- No, that's not fair.
- What do you mean?
You got to try it on and I didn't it.
Fine, you can have it. It's on you then.
- OK, fine.
- OK, then good.
Give it... give it...
Give it to me in the car.
I will, it hurts. Have fun.
Hi, girls.
How did the community service go?
I don't know, we learn stuff, Mom, like...
All right.
- Seatbelt, girls.
- OK
- Let's just drive.
- OK.
Maya...
I'm washing my hands for a while
so no one bother me.
One, two, three.
Freak!
Damn, white lady.
- Yo
- Hi, Shuji, is Maya there please?
Bitch here she be.
Woah, you sound different. Um...
Anyways, I was just thinking I'm just,
like, feeling a little, like, guilty.
- Are you feeling the same thing?
- Yes, bothering me a lot.
You know, I just want to make sure
that you wash it
and that we give it back to her,
like, put it in her bag tomorrow.
Uh-huh. For sure, washing it right now.
We're just not
that kind of people, like...
we won't take something
on purpose, you know.
Bye!
Hey.
You notice anything different about me?
Baby got back.
You still have... Are you serious?
- Maya, no.
- What?
You promised
that we give it back, like, stop.
Right, you seriously need to chill
'cause I'm gonna give it back tomorrow.
Like, nine people have looked at my butt
and my boobs for some reason
and I've literally only been here
for ten minutes.
Nine.
Hey, bowl cut.
I mean Maya.
Don't look at me.
Ten.
OK, you got checked out ten times.
Like I do... I do, too.
Like...
- Oh, Alex, look.
- Oh, shit.
- I need it.
- What?
It, it, it.
- Anna.
- Maya.
- What? No.
- Give it to me.
Give me the... Give me the thing.
Hey.
Let's make love.
I do it all the time.
What happened to your neck?
OK, I'm sorry. OK.
She almost caught us.
So, now that you've met
your Fashion Show partners,
it's important between now
and Saturday to really bond, OK?
So turn to your partner and ask
if you are a hat what kind would you be?
I don't really wear hats.
Oh, Heather, you're so pretty,
if I were a hat I'd be you.
- You make my hair flat.
- Oh, your hair is beautiful.
- Your hair is beautiful.
- No, it's not.
I literally already love you.
I'm not kidding.
- You're not? Wow.
- No.
Chew, chew.
If I were a hat I would be of...
a kind of like...
- Oh, my God.
- We could get...
I'll give you... I'll give you a manicure.
- OK.
- You give me a foot massage.
OK... now?
Can... can... Hel... Can
you... Can you let go?
You're hurting me.
Pu, let go. Let go, Pu.
Pu diddly Pu, Pu diddly Pu, let go, yeah?
Heath, are you OK?
Yeah, I'm fine I just...
lost something.
My mom is going to kill me.
Maybe one of us took it home accidentally.
- What is it?
- Um... it-it's private, you guys.
I can't really tell you,
but it's... it's pink.
OK.
- Let's look for it.
- That's all we need to know.
OK, that's a good start.
Look, don't worry.
- Can I look in your bag?
- Yeah.
Pink?
- Anna, why aren't you looking?
- I am.
Someone took it by accident,
it's just really important.
Look in your bag.
I literally looked everywhere,
you guys. I'm freaking out.
Oh, my God,
I feel so bad for Heather.
I mean, like, we should
definitely give it back.
Like tonight or like...
- Tomorrow, yeah.
- Tomorrow.
- Tomorrow
- Seriously, Anna...
give it to me between classes
I'm gonna give it to her.
Such a hypocrite!
Tomorrow.
Hi, Anna.
- Tomorrow.
- What?
Twenty. 25, 30, I have thirty.
Thirty, 35, 40, I have forty.
I have forty.
My tallies are through the roof.
My gel pen is basically out of gel.
- So, listen to me.
- I'm listening.
- OK, so we have the thing.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- We gotta give it back.
Tomorrow...
- So. To...
- After the...
- After the show.
- ...the show.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. After the show.
- After the show.
- We are on the same page.
We'll give it back after the show.
- OK, great.
- After the fashion show.
- Yeah.
- Who has show dips?
There, let's...
- It's only fair rock, paper, scissor.
- OK. I don't care.
On 15, go.
Oh, my God.
OK, ladies, listen up.
We don't have much time before the show
but as you know
something of Heather's was stolen.
A thong.
Please call it underwear, mom.
Shut up, sweetie.
Everybody, stand up
and get in a circle please.
And whoever took Heather's thong
is going to put it in the middle
of the table
and no one will know
because we're going to just turn around,
close our eyes and hum
on the count of three. OK?
One, two, three.
OK, open your eyes.
- Yeah, yeah, you guys.
- Really?
- Gone.
- OK, I see.
No one giving back.
OK. OK.
Well, I don't have time for this shit.
I have to take care of the elderly.
So, Heather, you're gonna just have
to wear the panties you have on.
Guys, seriously, this isn't funny anymore.
Like, if someone took Heather's thong,
- just say so.
- Yeah, you guys...
It must have been Anna, Maya or Terra.
- What?
The Bible says no thongs.
Anna and Maya,
you guys were in the changing room
when all of us went to see
Grandma Mary's room on Monday.
That's probably when you stole it,
just admit it.
- That's insane, you're literally crazy.
- What?
Show me your underwear.
- OK, show you our underwear?
- Show me just the top.
Are you crazy?
- Oh, Maya, show her your underwear.
- OK, show your underwear.
Show me your underwear.
You guys, you guys, you guys,
this is getting really out of hand.
I agree and you're perverted.
Can we just let it go, Becca?
Let's do the show, let's do the show,
I'm really... I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry you lost it.
Do you guys remember it's about the hats?
Hello, welcome to the Hat Extravaganza.
Thank you so much for coming.
I realized a lot of you were already here
so thank you for leaving your rooms.
Also I'd like to thank my pals from my
book club/wine club for being here.
So, please just enjoy yourself.
OK, here we go, let's get crazy.
Liar!
- She's gonna pull your pants down.
- Who?
Becca...
Becca's gonna pull your pants down.
Oh, no, no, no, stop it.
What's wrong with you? Come with me.
Come with me.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, we got away with it.
Oh, my God. We got away with it, Anna.
What are you talking about,
we got away with it?
I was embarrassed in front
of the entire retirement community.
- Oh, my God!
- Take off the thong. We don't need it.
- No. I'm keeping it.
- "No"?
- Anna, stop it, stop it.
- Take it off, take it off.
- Anna, stop it. You're gonna break it.
- We're not stealers. We're not stealers.
Stop!
No!
Are you seriously serious?
You, like, burned my asshole.
I'm freaking seriously dead serious
'cause that thing
was ripping everybody apart.
You literally just, like, ruined my life!
That thong ruined you.
- Damn it.
- And my vagina.
I have to say sometimes things just don't
turn out like you planned them, right?
And I apologize for that.
You should be apologizing to me.
I literally can't talk to you right now
when you have an attitude like that.
Pu, can you please tell Anna that I'm not
speaking to her either right now?
Um, Pu...
can you please tell Maya that sometimes
you have to right your wrongs in life
or karma will get you which is
exactly what happened to me today?
- Thank you very much.
- You know what, Pu,
you please tell Anna
that I'd like a karma to run me over
because she destroyed the one thing
that actually made me feel pretty
like a normal human.
- But you're pretty now.
- No, I am not.
What is this thing? I mean I want one.
- We can't talk about it.
- You know, it's like pink...
and it like, it's like,
it has, it's like a stretchy.
It wasn't ours.
Yeah, but when it was,
it was really amazing.
- See, you're overreacting right now.
- No, I'm not.
- Truly... Tru... Maya...
- Anna...
Truly your reaction is telling me
that it's good that we destroyed it.
That is literally the most messed up thing
you could ever say
because you weren't
ugliest girl in school, OK?
No, no, no, no, no, no, not to be corny,
but I gotta say this...
All my life I would grow a year older
look back and think
I was prettier the year before
I never got to enjoy my beauty
but I kept obsessing over it all the time.
I wish someone had told me when
I was younger that I was beautiful
because of who I was not what I had.
Is she choking?
"I... am... beautiful."
She's saying "I'm beautiful
and I don't need things on my body
to make me feel beautiful."
- You got that from that?
- Yeah.
Wow.
How's everybody holding up? Pu?
Something magical just happened.
OK, Pu, stop it.
I get it! OK? Let go.
You know what to do.
- Maya?
- What?
I'm not abandoning you.
I'm just letting you go
and you're gonna be loved
just like I... love you.
Bye.
OK, let's go.
- Let's go.
- Are you OK?
Yeah.
- Proud of you.
- Yeah.
- Um, do I look OK?
- Yeah. Do I?
Yeah, but it's what's inside
that counts, so...
- Oh, yeah, I almost forgot.
- Right.
Pu? Pu?
I forgot your grapes, OK?
Gonna get you some purples, OK?
Purples. I'll be right back.