Gonna have
some adventures
in this baby, huh, you guys?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Mm‐hmm.
‐ I can see the moon.
‐ Me too.
‐ It's pretty cool.
I wonder if it's
different in, like, Florida.
Mm‐hmm. Yeah.
It's gonna be fun.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐  People are out
on the streets
Saying, "Hey"
‐  Walking towards me
all of the day
I don't know you, sir
But I wish
that I could know you
So I could say, "Hey, hey"
You say hey back to me
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
‐  Back in the day,
hey, hey, hey, hey
‐  Hey, hey
‐ Dad, are we gonna
be there soon?
‐ Curt, what time is it?
‐ Dad.
‐ Can I use your camcorder?
‐ Wow. Beautiful, no?
Why, yes, it is, Curt.
It is beautiful.
Whoo! We here.
Florida, baby.
Whoo!
‐ Dad, what are you doing?
You're getting further away.
I'm not gonna park
the car next to other cars.
That‐that's how
you get scratches.
You know that, right?
Doors open and ding the car.
‐ Dad.
‐ Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Come on, Maya.
Don't play with the buttons.
‐ This is vacation.
Maya, get me. Get me.
‐ Okay.
‐ Hi.
‐ What's up?
Pose.
Whoa. Just recording.
We miss you, mom.
Yeah, but I wish
I was there with you.
The only vacations we went on
as a family were‐‐
‐ Were to Grammy and Grampy's
condo in Florida, I know.
But now you get
some alone time too.
You get a break from the kid.
Is your dad's
pink earring
sparkling in the Florida sun?
Mom, you're on speaker.
I love you.
I gotta go. We wanna swim.
Whoa.
Can't wait to jump in there.
Put Maya on with you,
please.
‐ I've gotta go, though.
I wanna talk
to both of you.
‐ Hi, Kathy.
Hi, Maya. Listen.
Both of you need to remember
you're in a strange place.
‐ We have a map.
Don't interrupt me,
sweetheart.
‐ Sorry, Kathy.
Girls are getting
kidnapped in Florida.
‐ Mom.
‐ If you see a cop,
sometimes they have
fake badges
and pretend to be cops
to get you in their car,
so just, you know,
be careful of that.
‐ That's not gonna happen.
‐ Wait, Kathy.
But if we do meet someone
that wants to do that to us,
should‐‐
Well, you should run
and use the whistle
I gave you.
‐ Okay, Mom.
Okay, I wanna go swim.
Love you. Bye.
‐ Bye. Love you, Kathy.
Love you too.
‐ Okay, Maya, let's go.
‐ Okay, let's go.
‐ Hey, hey. No. No, no, no.
You can't go in the pool
when there's thunder.
‐ Are you serious, Dad?
No one is letting us
start our good time.
‐ Oh, my God.
Hey, careful with that!
C'mon, let me see that.
You're not respecting it.
Okay, be back for dinner
at 5:00 p. m.
‐ 6:00.
‐ 5:00.
You're walking around.
That's it. No bodies of water.
Okay. We have to go, Dad.
We have to go.
‐ We have to go.
‐ Okay. Wait, wait, wait.
Hold it. Hold it.
‐ Dad!
‐ Take‐‐well, just a second.
Take this.
No, wait a minute, take‐‐
Dad!
Take this.
Oh, my god, Curt.
Now, that's all you get
for the whole trip, okay?
Thank you, Dad.
‐ So spend it wisely.
‐ Thank you so much.
‐ Are you sure?
‐ Don't buy expensive
water and stuff.
‐ Thank you. Love you.
‐ Okay?
‐ We'll be careful. Love you.
- We'll be economical.
- We have our map. Bye.
‐ Don't get ripped off.
‐ Love you. Bye.
‐ Love you, too.
Oh, my god.
‐ Oh, my God.
That guy's looking at me.
Hi.
C'mon, Anna. So cool.
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
‐ Do I look okay?
Maya, can you tell us
what we're getting?
This is umbrellas.
This, um, Canada Dry.
And this...
Ooh, whoa.
Can I hold the money?
It's more mine
'cause it's my dad's.
‐ Anna, he gave it
to both of us, so...
‐ I know, but you've had it
for a little while,
so I just want a chance
to hold it.
‐ Anna, and I'm gonna pay
for it, so hold on.
Like, let me hold it.
‐ Okay, whatever.
‐ $63.29.
‐ Okay.
Do we need all three umbrellas?
We do, right? Anna? Anna.
‐ C'mon, Maya. Hold on.
Beverly, I'm sorry. Sorry.
How much did you say
this one is, again?
‐ Um, Canada Dry is $5.63.
‐ And the Cherry Coke?
‐ $6.22.
‐ Oof.
Can I‐‐
‐ 'Na‐‐take the biggest gulp.
Wicked good artist.
‐ Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
We need that.
So pretty.
Wow, I love that.
‐ Excuse me, how much
would it cost for one of these?
‐ Two for $46.25.
$46.25.
That's the exact amount
we have.
‐ Kay. Adaria, here you go.
Maya, we're not gonna
have any money left.
‐ So pretty.
‐ Thank you.
‐ I have to have it.
‐ Okay.
We'd like to two, thank you.
Thank you.
We're gonna go next. Okay.
You sit‐‐okay.
‐ Don't move.
‐ Sorry.
‐ Anna, don't move.
‐ I'm not.
‐ I'm sitting still.
‐ You do? This is amazing.
Okay, done.
Take a look.
'Na, what?
What?
‐ Stop filming, Maya.
Please.
You liked it before.
Sorry.
‐ Please, please.
Okay, okay.
‐ I don't‐‐I don't look
like this, right?
Right, May?
‐ No, not at all. Do I?
‐ Oh, my God.
Honestly, not at all.
‐ I didn't know‐‐
‐ Do you swear?
No, you don't.
Not at all.
Hey.
How was it, you guys?
‐ Good.
‐ I'm pooping.
‐ Oh. Morning, Will Robinson.
You know, I like the town.
It's a tourist trap.
I went for a run.
Bottle of water?
- Hide it. Hide it.
- $3.22.
- I am.
- Okay.
Don't get
bamboozled here, okay?
‐ Bamboozled? No. No.
Put it in the thing.
‐ Put it away. Okay.
‐ It was not worth it.
‐ Where?
‐ Beneath. Like, at the bottom.
Oh, my God.
Are you awake?
Yeah. Are you?
Yeah.
What are you thinking about?
‐ I don't know.
I guess I'm just awake.
Yeah.
Um...
sorry it's not fun yet.
No, it is.
I swear, it really is.
'Na?
'Na? 'Na!
Yeah? What?
What's‐‐
Honey, it's sunny.
It's a beautiful day.
It's calling our name.
‐ Dad. Turn it off.
‐ Please, Curt, please.
‐ All right, all right,
all right.
How are you
liking everything?
Mmm.
‐ You happy
with the sausage patties?
Did you try dipping them
in the syrup?
‐ Uh, I‐I have in my life,
yeah, but, um, I haven't here.
I'm gonna do that.
That's great.
‐ Hi there.
You don't have
a lot on your plate.
Need something?
‐ I'm fat.
‐ Anna, tell Maya
it's not true.
‐ No, I am too.
I wanna stay inside.
‐ Huh?
‐ I want to stay inside.
‐ I‐I guess I know now why
they call 'em teenagers, right?
Are the waters free?
‐ No. Enjoy your day.
‐ Thank you.
Hey, what's with the faces,
you guys?
You were dying
to go out yesterday.
Don't leave your dear
old dad lonely.
C'mon.
Don't you wanna get those
hair braids she's rocking?
‐ You happy
with the sausage patties?
Mm...
It's on me.
‐ Am I tan yet?
‐ No idea. Am I?
My face feels huge.
‐ It's not. It's not. Is my‐‐
‐ No. No.
‐ Yeah.
She's pretty.
‐ Water, water, water. $1.30.
Looking sweaty. Cool down.
- Are you thirsty?
- Yeah.
It's a good price.
Cheapest on the block.
‐ We don't have any‐‐
‐ Money, yeah.
It's hot.
Wow.
That's how
it's supposed to look?
Hmm. Thank you.
I'm telling you,
she tried on this swimsuit,
and I swear...
The beach. Anna, oh, my god.
- The beach!
- Go, go, go.
I'm gonna splash
your ass.
‐ Ah, bad news.
Storm off of St. Lucia
brought in the jellyfish.
- You're too slow.
- Guys. Guys.
Jellyfish.
No swimming today.
Bummer.
‐ Ow.
‐ Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
‐ Oh, shit, I forgot something.
Um, it's in the room.
I'll be right back, okay?
‐ Ow, ow. Ow.
‐ It's a tan, right?
'Cause you look burned.
‐ So do you.
‐ Ow, Maya, it's not ready
to come off yet.
‐ Sorry.
- Yeah.
Naño couldn't get a ball
if he tried.
‐ Okay, and Ray Rogers can?
He's a joke player, okay?
‐ Feels like we'd all eat
pepperoni pizza together.
‐ Are you hot?
‐ No.
‐ Hey.
‐ Oh, hey.
‐ Are you...on a mouse?
JK. Are you on vacation?
‐ Yeah. Are you?
‐ Yeah.
‐ What room are you in?
‐ 39K5.
‐ That's close to K9, right?
Like, as in dogs?
My brother's a K9 cop,
and, uh, it smells for drugs.
Arrest me.
JK.
‐ I love dogs.
‐ Me too.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Where are you guys?
What floor?
‐ We are in, uh, 21L4.
Four, four, four.
‐ Four, four, four.
‐ You two are cute.
‐ You really are.
It's, like, crazy.
‐ You've been to In Da Club?
‐  In da club
on a late night
Feeling right looking
to have fun
‐  I can take home
‐  Home
‐  I can take
That's awesome.
But have you guys
been to that club?
‐ It's tonight,
for 16 and under.
‐ Say hello, you guys.
‐ Dad. Dad, stop.
‐ Your dad.
‐ Dad, stop.
Wave. C'mon.
‐ Seriously.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ Peace.
‐ Wait, what are your names?
‐ Ralph.
‐ Freddy.
‐ We're Anna and Maya.
‐ Bye.
‐ Bye. Later. Peace.
‐ Oh.
‐ Dad!
‐ Come on‐‐lighten up.
- 21L4.
- Shh.
- Sorry.
- Go.
Maya loves you.
- Oh, shit! Anna!
- Shh.
Bah, bah, bah, bah, bah!
Boo, boo, boo, boo!
I'm gonna pee my pants!
Um, Anna and I wanna
have your babies!
‐ Maya. Stop. Are you serious?
Wait, do I look okay?
‐ Yes. Oh, my God. Do I?
‐ Yes.
Okay. Shh.
‐ Hi.
‐ Um, is Ralph here, please?
‐ Or is Freddy, please?
‐ You don't have
the right room.
‐ Oh.
‐ Um, this is 21L4, right?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Oh, or maybe they're in
In Da Club.
‐ Oh, yeah.
In In Da Club, you're right.
Okay.
Sorry.
‐ Sorry.
Go, go, go, go, go!
Oh, my God!
Wait, wait, wait!
‐ So you're‐‐
you're not responsible
for picking out
the ice machine, are you?
'Cause this one‐‐
‐ It's a nice one.
‐ It's great.
‐ Dad.
Can we go to the town?
‐ And chase the boys?
‐ Dad.
‐ We want to explore the town,
and I have my whistle,
so, like‐‐
‐ So it's all good.
‐ Yeah.
‐ We just wanna
explore the town.
‐ A‐line‐‐Aline, right? Aline?
Um, is it safe for them
to just, you know, hang?
‐ Oh, yeah.
There's a lot
of kid‐centered activities.
I say yeah.
Okay. Well, be back by 8:00.
Okay, love you. 8:00.
Love you. 8:00.
8:00 sharp.
Have fun, you guys.
Kids.
‐ Okay, this is crazy,
but, like, what if
one of use marries them?
Or both of us. Like‐‐
I know. I know this is crazy,
but I sort of feel that.
‐ Right?
‐ I know!
They said
that they think we're cute.
Oh, my God.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ But, like, they are, though,
you know?
And they're, like, so nice,
which is crazy. Like‐‐
‐ They're so nice. And so cute.
‐ So, so cute,
and so nice, like‐‐
‐ Maya.
‐ Let me see your ID.
‐ Um...
oh, I, um, don't have one,
but, um‐‐do you, Anna?
‐ I'm, um, only 13, so no.
‐ Right.
‐ Right answer.
‐ Well, right this way, then.
‐ Thank you so much, sir.
‐ Thank you.
‐ Something to drink?
‐ No, thank you.
‐ If you wanna stay
in In Da Club,
you have to order something.
Oh.
‐ We'll be right‐‐yeah,
we'll be right back.
'Cause we don't have any money.
He's so cool.
‐ Ew, Anna.
You're, like, grinding.
‐ Maya.
Do you know Freddy or Ralph?
‐ Nah.
Hey.
‐ Trying to be Black much,
Blondie?
‐ What?
‐ Huh? What? Nothin'.
‐ Jenny, Venice.
God.
Oh, his friends.
‐ Want me to take your picture?
Do you want me
to take your picture?
‐ Yeah.
Thank you.
‐ Thanks.
Um, you're pressing the flash.
It's the button on top.
‐ Wow, you're so pretty.
‐ Aww.
I just got a new straightener.
We're trying to meet up
with these guys
that we might go out with,
but‐‐
‐ Oh, really? It's still early.
This is Ben. He's single.
‐ That is not the truth.
‐ Are these the girls
you were talking about?
‐ Maybe.
‐ That's so mean.
They're not that bad.
‐ He calls girls butt ugly
all the time.
It's so messed up.
Well, he's never
called you that.
He's obsessed with you.
He has. He has before.
‐ I didn't mean it, though.
I was mad when I said that.
You're hot.
‐ Oh, my God,
you made them sad.
Look, you girls
aren't ugly at all.
He's just an asshole.
‐ I don't care
what that fool thinks.
He looks like he wipes his anus
with toilet bowl brushes.
‐ Oh, my gosh.
‐ I'm waiting to meet
some real men.
‐ Okay.
‐ You're so funny.
Sorry, you have
to drink with us.
‐ He has a tiny dick.
‐ You guys are like
the little sisters I never had.
Aww.
‐ We look like you a little.
‐ Yeah.
We do.
‐  Sister, sister
‐  Never know how much
‐  I miss her
I ain't ever gonna
let you go
‐ Three virgin
strawberry daiquiris.
‐ Thank you, ma'am.
‐ Two more, please,
for my girls.
‐ Thank you so much.
‐ Oh, my God. Thank you.
Oh, my God.
‐ Give them some.
‐ There's only a little left.
‐ C'mon, think about
how funny it'll be.
Please?
‐ Here, take that. Take that.
Here, here. Hurry up, hurry up.
You're going too slow.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ That's so much.
Whoo!
‐ Oh, yo, even this song?
‐ Venice, dance with me.
‐ Yeah. Okay.
‐ The weather's really nice.
‐ So, um...
‐ Oh, my God.
I've always wanted to do this.
‐ Yeah. Yeah.
I've‐‐yeah, I've always
wanted to do that.
Oh, whoa
‐ I am the candy man!
‐ Coming from Mounty Land!
‐ Whoo!
‐ Oh, my God. Maya.
That guy is looking at you.
You're a hottie.
He looks way too old
to be in here.
Get him to buy us nips, slut.
‐ I don't know him, psycho.
‐ Oh, my God, I do.
I know him. I know him.
Yes!
‐ Yeah?
‐ Hi, again.
So you don't know
Ralph and Freddy, or you do?
Or are you related?
‐ What do you want me to say?
That you know them.
I don't.
‐ Oh.
Our friends want you
to buy them, um‐‐
uh, never mind.
‐ Alcohol?
‐ Yeah.
‐ I don't care. Sure.
‐ Oh, my God,
what just happened?
‐ Got it!
‐ Go, girl! Go, girl!
‐ Got it! Got it!
‐ Hi, ugly.
There she is.
‐ Anna! Worm with me.
Where were you?
I got us alcohol.
‐ The bathroom.
I feel, like, sad.
‐ Oh, no.
Okay, Anna needs
to catch up, you guys.
‐ Ben, give Anna the rest
of your drink.
‐ Yeah.
‐ More is coming
'cause of them.
‐ Anna. Oh, my Go‐‐whoo!
Yes! Go!
Oh, my God,
you're gonna be wasted.
‐ I usually hate
the taste of alcohol,
but I love
fermented strawberry.
I could have, like, so much.
‐ Oh, my God, drink mine too.
Don't laugh. Don't laugh.
I just want her to have it.
‐ Okay, alcoholic.
‐ Thank you.
I have a big mouth. Thank you.
Love you guys.
Love you so much.
‐ You okay, 'Na?
‐ Whoo!
You're drunk!
‐ You are.
‐ He's back.
Your friend is back, Maya.
He's kinda creepy.
Ben, go talk to him
so we don't have to.
‐ Oh, my God, Ben's hot.
‐ Oof.
‐ You got it?
‐ Yeah, he got us so much.
But he was just
kicked out of here
'cause your friend is,
like, 32.
‐ Ew. He's so old.
Good job, guys.
‐ Lower, lower.
‐ I love you guys.
‐ Oh, my God. Anna, no.
‐ Babe. No.
‐ Sorry, there's a lot going on
in my life.
And the guy I like didn't come.
‐ It's okay.
‐ The guy I like didn't come.
‐ Aww, you're a sad drunk.
‐ My parents hate each other.
I'm stupid.
‐ You got me though.
You got me.
Ay‐ya‐ya!
‐ Oh, she's a fun one.
‐ I'm pissed, too,
they didn't come.
They're assholes.
‐ Don't say that, Maya.
Maybe it's still early.
What time is it?
9:00.
‐ Damn, we're supposed
to be back at 8:00, Anna.
No.
‐ Be careful of the old guy
on the way back.
I would go with you,
but I don't wanna leave
those two alone.
‐ Fuck you.
‐ Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Okay.
Jenny, Venice, Ben, love you.
‐ Bye, guys. Love you.
‐ Bye.
‐ Get off me. I'm good.
‐ Okay, okay. Get up. Get up.
‐ Is this the right way?
‐ Oh, my God. Be normal.
Be normal, Anna.
‐ Anna. Anna, is that the guy?
‐ Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
C'mon, Anna. Shh.
Please, please get up, please.
Shit. Shit.
It's a cop. It's a cop.
Oh, my God,
but it could be a fake cop.
‐ Come on, come on, come, come.
Look, when we see your dad,
don't say a lot, okay?
And if you, like,
need to lean on me,
then just say
you hurt your ankle.
‐ Mm.
You're my uncle.
‐ Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Shh, shh.
Be quiet. Your dad.
Hello?
Okay, c'mon.
C'mon.
‐ Ow.
Are you okay?
Did you hurt yourself?
I'm ugly.
‐ Huh?
‐ I'm ugly.
‐ Anna, no, you're not. I am.
Why would you say that?
‐ No, you loo‐‐you're perfect.
God made my‐‐made me, like‐‐
like he was on crack.
Forgot he was doing a human,
not a mountain.
Mountain.
My nose is like
a wedge of cheese.
‐ No, I am the cheese, Anna.
I'm, like, a whole round of it.
I'm a whole round of it.
Do you understand?
My face is literally
as round as the moon!
Do you get that?
You get that
in your thick skull?
I have a freaking round face,
and my face is hairier
than a bat!
I have a hairy, fat, round face
like a freaking fat,
hairy bat moon!
How would you feel?
Oh, my God, where'd you go?
‐ Oh, my God. Get up. Okay.
Get up. Get up. Get up.
‐ Throw up.
Oh, God.
What?
Shh. Shh. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Lay down.
Lay down. Lay down. Lay down.
Anna.
Anna?
Hmm.
‐ You okay?
Are you feeling okay?
‐ She's sick, I think. Um...
Oh, okay.
You don't have a fever.
Anna. Are you drunk?
‐ Dad...fuck you.
‐ What?
‐ You're not my mom, I get it.
‐ Maya, what‐‐what happened?
How could you let this happen?
‐ Um...um...yeah.
The‐‐these younger kids, um,
were, like‐‐
they had alcohol and‐‐
‐ Okay, tell me.
‐ They were going home
and they told us
to hold it for them.
‐ Okay.
‐ And then, like, Anna sipped
the tiniest bit
just to, like, see if they were
gonna be okay on it.
‐ Yes.
‐ Um, and we were, like‐‐
we were just, like,
really scared coming home.
And then, like,
you weren't here,
and so we were scared
and, like, we just‐‐
‐ Just‐‐I'm gonna call 911.
I'm scared.
Hello. Um, yeah. Hi.
This is Curtis Kone.
I'm at the Tropicana Hotel.
And, um...
My daughter is, um, drunk.
She's‐‐she's 13.
Yeah, at the Hotel Tropicana,
yes.
‐ Don't press charges.
‐ Anna, how‐‐
Maya, how much did Anna‐‐
Anna, how much did you drink?
‐ Fuck you.
‐ Um, a couple, um, sips.
Okay, just‐‐just, um,
a couple of sips.
Oh, okay.
Right. All right.
Uh...
maybe it's mixed in with
food poisoning, I don't know.
Okay, thank you. Thank you.
You can't get alcohol poisoning
from a couple of sips.
‐ Wh‐what's that?
When you've had
too much to drink
and you have to go
to the hospital to get it out.
Anna? Sweetheart?
You're in trouble.
But I love you.
You'll feel better
after getting it out.
Don't tell him.
‐ Anna. Anna.
I just told your dad, okay?
You have to remember.
Some younger kids
came with alcohol.
We were trying to help them‐‐
Anna.
We were trying‐‐Anna, I didn't
ask the guy to buy it for us.
Anna. Anna. Anna.
Anna. Anna.
‐ When we wake up, your dad is
gonna ask us where we were.
Remember what we were saying?
What?
‐ You asked the old guy
to buy it for us.
And then we drank it.
We drank so much.
‐ No. No. Try again.
Kids had it, and we drank it
to protect them.
So who got it for us?
‐ You did.
‐ No. Anna. Try again.
So who got it for us?
‐ You.
Are you gonna
say something?
Dad?
‐ I‐I‐‐I don't even have
the words
for how disappointed in you
I am.
I didn't think you were
that kind of a kid.
‐ Yeah. Yeah.
‐ Dad, can you please focus?
Like, not on your date? Please?
‐ Aline and I are just friends.
‐ Oh, yeah,
you didn't kiss her?
Don't tell me.
I don't wanna know.
‐ I did.
‐ Dad‐‐
‐ It made me feel really bad.
And I will do things
differently next time.
And young lady,
I hope you do too.
‐ Yes, of course.
Any little amount
to drink is wrong.
And it's a cruel lesson
that you got the stomach flu,
Anna, on the same night
as your bad behavior.
‐ So what happened, again?
You didn't drink
anything, Maya?
Just Anna did?
‐ We were going home.
Little kids gave us
their alcohol.
They were so little.
I was really nervous over them.
And she tasted it just a little
to see if they would get
too drunk, and‐‐
So it didn't have
anything to do with those boys?
Bad influences?
‐ Dad, we never saw them again.
But when‐‐when we did,
they were‐‐they were
perfect gentlemen.
‐ They ditched us
probably 'cause I'm butt ugly.
‐ No, it's my fault.
Maya, you're gorgeous.
My nose is, like,
so disgusting.
‐ My face is so big and ugly.
‐ You guys are both gorgeous.
Thanks, Curt.
They ditched you, huh?
I'm trying to think
of something to say
to make it better, but, uh...
Um‐‐
But, you know, we had
a little experience together.
Didn't we?
And we're better off
than we were, right?
Not really.
‐ No, I really like them.
‐ So that's an easy answer.
Give them the benefit
of the doubt.
And if they screw you over
again, fuck them.
Be the Anna and Maya
I know you are.
‐ Curt, how?
We're leaving today. Like...
Aline said we can use
the pool till 4:00.
Maybe they'll come back.
Okay.
We have a good time here, huh?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ Thanks, Dad.
‐ We didn't even get
their screen names.
Yeah.
For the email messages?
Fuck 'em.
‐ It's called AIM.
‐ Oh.
‐ It's not email.
‐ Sorry.
‐ Oh, my God.
That's‐‐that's them.
That's them.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, my God, that's them.
‐ One sec. Dad, dad, dad.
One sec. Stop.
Stop just for a second.
Be chill. Be chill.
Hey.
‐ Oh, my God, hey.
Whoa, what are you guys,
like, doing here?
‐ Whoa.
‐ Nothing.
What are you looking for?
‐ Yeah, my earring dropped.
‐ It's in your ear.
‐ Freddy, we hoped
we'd see you guys again
in, like‐‐in In Da Club.
‐ Yeah, we went your room too,
but maybe we, like, heard
the number wrong or something.
‐ Maya. Maya.
‐ No, no.
I thought about it all night.
I couldn't sleep.
Like‐‐
‐ Same.
We felt like we were
supposed to be with you.
Make sure you were okay.
But, like, um, he got grounded
'cause his mom found out
we used the jacuzzi again.
‐ So stupid. Not her.
‐ Oh.
‐ The situation.
‐ Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
‐ We aren't actually
staying here.
‐ Yeah.
Uh, we just live nearby.
Not here. So our bad.
‐ Yeah,
but we've waiting out here
'cause maybe you'd walk by
and we say hi.
‐ Hey.
‐ Hi.
‐ Like, now we're leaving.
Fuck it all, like‐‐
‐ Um, can we have
your screen names, maybe?
‐ Anna!
‐ Sorry.
‐ Okay, yeah.
‐ Don't lose them.
‐ Oh, my God, they're gone.
JK.
‐ You ladies are funny.
‐ I don't wanna leave you,
hon, like‐‐
‐ Yeah, hon, me too.
I really, really don't.
‐ You have the gum
to remember us by.
You're, like, the shit.
‐ Can we have
something of yours?
‐ Okay.
‐ Here.
‐ I'll treasure it, babe.
‐ Forever, baby.
‐ Enjoy it, baby. Think of me.
‐ Stay safe, okay?
‐ Bye.
‐ Bye, hon. Bye.
‐ Bye, babe.
‐ Bye.
‐ I can see it on your face.
You got a perfect ending.
Smile.
‐ Dad, stop.
‐ Oh, my God, Curt.
‐ Stop.
‐ Please, stop.
‐ I know, it's annoying.
But you'll look back on this
and really, like‐‐maybe.
You'll get that
someday, sweetie.