[door shuts]
‐ Day of the show!
Are you excited?
ANNA: Um, yeah,
I guess I will be
if it's not a total disaster
'cause nobody's prepped,
especially Maya, so‐‐
you know what, though?
I don't want to talk about it,
'cause it's stressing me out.
Dad, we're late!
KATHY: Wait, Munch.
CURTIS: Yeah!
KATHY: Anna, here.
Here's your glitter.
‐ Okay, so I said that I didn't
want that already, so‐‐
‐ But this is to remind you
that you sparkle.
‐ Okay, cool. Whatever.
Thank you!
Dad!
CURTIS: Coming.
Coming, goof.
[clattering]
‐ So, um...shoulders back.
Break a leg.
I love you.
Give me a hug.
‐ You know what?
I don't want a hug.
I'm late.
‐ You look beautiful, sweetie.
[door slams]
SINGER: ♪ I ♪
♪ I am hiding ♪
♪ The you I show to you ♪
♪ Is just a lie ♪
♪ You take what you want ♪
♪ You get what you take ♪
♪ Lie ♪
SINGER: ♪ So high, high, high ♪
GABE: Debra.
Divorce.
Wolves.
Or what, Debra?
You gonna divorce me?
You gonna feed me
to the wolves?
No.
Wol‐‐
[knocking]
Come in.
‐ Hey, there you are.
Just wanted to say,
break a leg.
‐ Oh. Um, thank you.
Uh, you too.
‐ Uh, P. S., you should totally
keep your hair like that.
It looks really cool.
‐ Thanks.
[distant chatter]
[low tone sounding]
[indistinct chatter]
‐ Phone, phone, phone,
phone, phone.
Pound, pound, pound,
pound, pound.
Okay, you guys.
Five minutes.
‐ I saw you.
I saw you with my own two eyes.
You were backing away.
Backing away.
Were you doing your business
with Sheila?
You rat bastard.
Rat bastard.
‐ Where's my hat?
ANNA: Okay, places in five.
MAYA: Hey.
‐ Hey.
‐ Umm, I didn't hear from you
last night.
‐ Can't hear you.
I have my headphones on.
‐ I didn't hear from you
last night.
either.
Um, if you don't find
your light,
the whole thing's
gonna go wacko, so...
‐ Okay, do you know
how many lines
I have to remember right now?
‐ 422. Congratulations.
Find your light.
‐ The light will find me, Anna.
Like, seriously.
Honestly,
all you have to do right now
is just, like, pep me up.
Like, pep me up.
Just say, like, "Break a leg."
Whatever. What‐‐you haven't
said that once to me.
‐ Your feelings are valid.
MAYA: Mm‐hmm.
‐ So are mine.
‐ And you can't take
constructive criticism.
That's my feeling.
‐ Are you kidding?
‐ And good luck.
MAYA: Okay, you just jinxed me.
It's "break a leg,"
so now I'm gonna
be really bad in the play,
but it's fine.
Let's just hold each other's
hand and say, "I'm sorry."
‐ I'm not ready right now.
‐ Well, I'm not really
ready for it either.
I was honestly just saying it
'cause I thought it was
the right thing to do.
So...
‐ Wow.
Places in 4 minutes, 15 seconds.
‐ Okay.
MAYA: Psycho.
ANNA: Yep.
‐ Hi.
‐ Are you still feeling sick?
‐ No, I'm just, uh,
concentrating.
‐ Kay, well, I'm really
looking forward
to 4 minutes and 32 seconds
into the play.
It's our kiss.
‐ Oh...
[chuckles]
Yeah.
‐ Kay, well...
break a leg, cutie.
GABE: You too...
Cutie.
‐ Kay.
Bye.
GABE: Bye.
[sighs]
ANNA: Actors, places.
Actors to places.
[soft indistinct chatter]
‐ [sighs]
[distant giggling]
‐ Shut up!
[clattering, squeaking]
[applause]
‐ [clears throat]
I saw you!
I saw you with my own two eyes!
GABE: You're nuts.
‐ Sheila was backing away
from you.
She was scared out of her mind.
‐ She's not in her light.
She's not in her light.
‐ [sighs]
She was scared out of her mind.
Honey, help me with this,
will you?
It's giving me a rash.
‐ A rash, a rash.
Always something with you.
‐ Bryce, are you there?
MAYA: Be careful with it.
‐ Go to two.
Go to two.
MAYA: Careful with it, I said.
Jesus Christ!
‐ All right, relax, will you?
You're wriggling around
like a worm,
and you're hairier
than a bigfoot.
‐ [chuckles]
[audience member coughs]
Your fingers are greasy
schlubs, that's why.
Forget it, will you?
I said just get it‐‐off!
Jesus Christ.
GABE: All right.
MAYA: Jesus Christ, I said.
Jesus Christ.
‐ Cue 30.
GABE: What do you want?
Want me to stay?
ANNA: Cue 30.
GABE: Want me to go?
Make up your mind, woman!
Make up your mind.
‐ No, that's cue 22.
MAYA: Yeah.
Too damn dark in this joint.
[clinking]
Don't you dare
make another drink.
I'm telling you,
don't you do it!
‐ Or what, Debra?
You gonna divorce me?
You gonna feed me
to the wolves?
I don't have to listen
to your loud‐mouth crap.
Just let me do my business.
‐ Yeah?
Were you doing your business
with Sheila?
You rat bastard.
[loud bang]
‐ You wanna do this?
Let's do this.
Let's let it all out.
‐ Go light. Go light.
GABE: Come on, baby.
‐ Shit.
GABE: Give me your best shot.
‐ You get away from me.
‐ Isn't this...what you want?
‐ You don't know the first
thing about what I want!
You get your hands off me,
you pig!
‐ [gasps, panting]
Or what?
[scattered laughter]
‐ [whispering]
Come on, Maya.
[audience member coughs]
‐ [chuckles]
‐ Or what?
‐ Or...
‐ [whispers]
Come on, Maya.
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
MAYA: Or...
or...
♪ ♪
‐ [gasps]
‐ [whispering]
"Or I'll scream so..."
‐ Or I'll scream so loud,
you won't know what hit ya!
AUDIENCE MEMBER: Whoo!
[light applause]
‐ Yeah, yeah.
Just...
go to sleep.
‐ I already am, Joe.
I already am.
[dramatic opera music]
♪ ♪
SINGER: [singing in Italian]
[male singer joins,
singing in Italian]
♪ ♪
[music fading]
GABE: Sun's almost up.
‐ The days are short, Joe.
The days are short.
[applause]
[cheers and applause]
[cheers and applause continue]
[soft dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[mouthing words]
ANNA: Ready, star?
MAYA: Let's do this.
YUKI: Maya, shut the door,
please.
‐ You get it.
[both giggle]
ANNA: I mean,
they're gonna swarm us.
[The Four Seasons'
"December, 1963
(Oh, What a Night)"]
MAYA: Hi.
MAN: Great job tonight.
[both speaking indistinctly]
SINGER: ♪ Oh, what a night ♪
♪ Late December back in '63 ♪
MAYA: Oh, my God,
that guy‐‐[sputters]
So crazy!
SINGER: ♪ What a very special
time for me ♪
‐ Stop!
SINGER: ♪ As I remember,
what a night ♪
MAYA: Stop!
[both giggling]
‐ Oh, my God.
Okay. Sorry.
Oh, attitude like crazy.
[gasps]
Oh, my God, cheese!
Can we have some?
‐ Thank you!
‐ Hey.
‐ Get outta here!
‐ Oh, sorry.
Go, go, go, go, go.
♪ ♪
Oh, my God!
Stop!
SINGER: ♪ I got a funny
feeling when she walked... ♪
‐ Get out.
‐ I was about to pet him.
♪ ♪
SINGER: ♪ As I recall it ended
much too soon ♪
MAYA: Oh, sorry.
♪ ♪
That guy is looking‐‐
FRED: Oh, there they are!
All right!
No. No, no.
Wait, wait, wait. Stay.
MAYA: Dad, no!
‐ No, please.
I‐‐I gotta turn this on.
All right, smile.
Come on.
One, two, three, smile.
[camera shutter clicking]
‐ [laughs] Dad!
You're gonna, like, blind me.
FRED: You were amazing!
Come on.
You have to get used to getting
pictures taken all the time
'cause you're a star.
‐ No, I'm not.
‐ That was dope, Young Bowl.
‐ Thank you. Really?
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ So what, now you're a star,
you don't bring
your own jacket?
‐ No, I'm not a star.
I'm an actress.
I forgot it.
‐ Well done.
FRED: Wasn't she great?
She was so good tonight.
I know‐‐
‐ Dad, stop, seriously.
FRED: I'm her father.
KATHY: You were amazing
tonight, angel,
and these are for you
from me and your dad.
‐ Techies don't get flowers.
Like...but thanks.
Where's Dad?
‐ Um, I don't know, sweetie.
I‐‐I was wondering
the same thing.
♪ ♪
So that glitter I gave you...
‐ Yeah, I used it.
It was an emergency, so...
‐ It was a nice touch.
You probably saved
the whole thing, huh?
[ululating]
‐ Mom, are you out
of your mind?
Don't do that.
‐ Oh, my god, my dad is being
so annoying and so loud.
‐ I don't know
what that's like.
‐ Ugh.
‐ Oh, my God,
it's your boyfriend.
[Joe Montgomery's
"Since You Fell in Love"]
SINGER:
♪ Everybody was in love ♪
♪ Everyone but me ♪
FRED: Oh, there he is!
The man of the house.
Gabe, you were great tonight.
‐ Dad, stop.
‐ Ow!
‐ Maya, stop it.
[overlapping chatter]
‐ See you guys.
FRED: Uh, hi.
We're‐‐we're her parents.
‐ Yeah, that's Gabe.
‐ So nice to meet you.
‐ Yeah, it's good
to officially meet you.
You know, she talked about you
about rehearsals and everything.
‐ No, I didn't.
‐ Well, you did.
MAYA: Stop.
You're literally killing me.
‐ Okay, okay. Hey, listen.
I want a picture of you.
I want a picture
of the both of you; come on.
The stars of the show.
Right here, come on, together.
All right?
A little closer.
‐ Dad, stop.
FRED: Yeah, that's good.
All right, you ready?
One, two, three, grandkids!
‐ Dad, don't say that.
Like‐‐
‐ All right,
all right, all right.
MAYA: He's so embarrassing.
I'm sorry.
‐ [groans]
‐ Sorry.
♪ ♪
Your hair looks different.
It's hot.
♪ ♪
‐ Thanks.
You too.
Your‐‐your hair is hot.
‐ Thanks.
‐ Welcome.
‐ [sniffs]
Um...
I didn't see you
after the play.
‐ Yeah.
♪ ♪
‐ Okay.
FRED: Hey, are you guys hungry?
Would you like
some groovy nachos?
‐ Dad, don't say
"groovy nachos"!
‐ Oh, I'd like an order
of groovy nachos too.
FRED: Two orders
of groovy nachos,
and I want a Coke
for that table over there
for that young man.
‐ Dad, don't, or I'll stick
an ice pick up your butthole!
Stop!
ANNA: Oh, no, you okay, hon'?
MAYA: No.
ANNA: [whispering]
What's wrong?
‐ Close it.
‐ What? Okay.
‐ Close it!
‐ I'll‐‐I'll keep it closed.
‐ Hold it.
‐ What's wrong, girl? You okay?
‐ Yeah, I'm fine,
I just, like,
I was out there with Gabe,
and I just, like,
tried to grab his hand
like this, and he went‐‐
‐ That's so cute.
‐ No, and he went like that.
‐ Maybe his hand slipped.
‐ No, but then
when we were onstage,
we were planning to do
a real kiss,
and he put his hand
over his mouth,
like, at the last second.
‐ It's okay.
Hey, I'm sorry‐‐sorry.
‐ Stop, we're in here!
‐ Just two more seconds.
‐ Is it my breath?
[exhales]
‐ [sniffs]
It's good.
No, no, really‐‐
‐ Oh, my God!
‐ No, no, no, no.
No, it's good.
And do you know‐‐
can I ask you a question?
were you nervous out there,
for your kiss?
‐ I mean, yeah, 'cause it's,
like, in front of everyone,
and like, it's my first kiss.
‐ So he was probably
nervous too.
I think that you just
gotta do it again,
and you gotta go
for what you want,
and it's gonna happen.
‐ Okay, yeah.
Yeah, all right.
Fine. I'm just gonna‐‐
‐ I see how he looks at you.
‐ Stop.
‐ It's true.
‐ Okay. All right, fine.
‐ Let's do this.
‐ Okay, but be quiet.
I don't want to be obvious
about it.
Okay, just like, literally
don't look, and like, if‐‐
‐ Hey.
‐ Oh, my God, my dad's here.
I'm gonna say hi.
‐ Oh, my God, really?
Okay, I'll be there in a sex‐‐
sec.
[both chuckle]
‐ What's up?
‐ You always say that.
‐ Yeah.
True.
Um...
‐ So...
‐ Yeah.
[laughs]
‐ What?
‐ I just, you know...
wanted to say that, uh,
you know...
‐ What?
‐ You were‐‐you‐‐I‐‐you were
just really good in the play.
‐ No, I wasn't.
‐ No, yes, you were, seriously.
‐ No.
‐ I knew you were funny,
but...
I've never seen you
like that before.
You're really...
[sniffs] Good.
‐ Thanks.
‐ And...
I‐‐I also wanted to say,
like, you know,
once and for all or whatever,
that, uh...
never mind.
‐ No. Say it.
Fool.
‐ I'm‐‐I'm really sorry
about everything.
I‐‐I wish I didn't do
all that stuff.
Fool.
‐ What are you even doing here?
SAM: [chuckles]
I'm, you know‐‐I'm with Gabe.
We're celebrating.
‐ Oh, yeah.
SAM: Yeah.
‐ My boyfriend.
‐ Yes.
MAYA: Yeah.
‐ Yeah, your boyfriend.
SAM: Um...
what was‐‐what was up
with that kiss in the play?
‐ I don't know. Why?
‐ No reason. Nothing.
‐ Why? Did he say something?
‐ No.
[sniffs]
Um, but I mean, you know,
I wouldn't have put my hand
over my mouth.
‐ [laughs]
‐ So you know, I guess
I should've auditioned.
So‐‐or something.
‐ I don't know. Maybe.
‐ Yeah.
‐ I guess you should've.
SAM: Yeah.
‐ Or not. I don't know.
MAYA: Kay. Bye.
‐ Bye.
[upbeat music playing]
♪ ♪
‐ So‐‐well, how was it?
How was the play?
‐ It was...good.
It was bumpy at first,
and then it got...better,
but pretty good.
‐ Anna made such an impact
as the stage manager,
and there was point whe‐‐
‐ Yeah, that's great.
[chuckles]
Hey.
Did, uh, Kathy give you
the flowers that we got you?
‐ Yes.
‐ [chuckles]
‐ Thank you so much.
‐ Absolutely.
‐ They're so pretty.
Where did you guys get them?
‐ Uh, where did we get
the flowers, Kathy?
‐ I got them
from Stop and Shop.
CURTIS: Really?
‐ Yes.
‐ You know, there are much
better places to get flowers
than Stop and Shop.
Right?
[clears throat]
Hey, did your mom clap,
or did she do that weird
yodeling thing that she does?
‐ She did the weird
yodel thing.
It was so embarrassing.
CURTIS: [laughs]
ANNA: Honestly.
CURTIS: Mm‐hmm.
‐ Where were you?
‐ You want to know?
You ready?
[keys jingling]
‐ Did you get a new car?
‐ [laughing]
New!
Used.
ANNA: What kind?
CURTIS: It's a Solara.
It's right out back.
‐ Excuse me.
CURTIS: It's really cool.
You're gonna love it.
‐ So that's where you were.
CURTIS: Uh‐huh.
‐ That's great.
‐ It's a convertible too.
MAYA: [gasps]
Oh, my God, Curt,
you got a frickin' convertible?
CURTIS: Yep, I got
a convertible.
MAYA: Can we go in it?
CURTIS: Absolutely.
MAYA: Oh, my God.
‐ Just don't drive it too far.
‐ [laughs]
‐ Oh, my God.
ANNA: He got a convertible.
MAYA: Um, I love your earring,
by the way, Curt.
‐ You know,
I've always had the hole.
I just got a new hoop.
[chuckles]
MAYA: Oh, my God,
your dad is crazy.
SAM: So I did this weasel.
Here, I did the gloves.
I also did the barbed wire.
‐ Wait, wait.
You did all of this?
‐ Yeah, last night
I went to Kinkos.
I even got the glossy‐‐
‐ Guy‐‐guys, guys.
This is‐‐this is great.
I think we're ready
to distribute.
ANNA: Sorry.
SAM: Right?
That's what I was thinking.
‐ Hey.
Um, Anna's dad
got a new convertible,
and we were gonna,
like, check it out.
What? He did.
‐ He did.
‐ Do you wanna come?
‐ Hell yeah.
‐ Yeah.
ANNA: The only thing‐‐
sorry, you guys.
There's only room for one,
so I don't know how to decide,
but I'm thinking
Maya's boyfriend...
[quiet laughter]
MAYA: Stop.
Sorry.
GABE: That's me, so...
‐ Just so they have time
to be like...
‐ Stop.
‐ All right, I'm‐‐
I'm gonna go.
‐ Kay.
‐ Don't eat all the pizza.
‐ I won't.
JAFEER: That's some bullshit.
‐ Yeah, whatever.
ANNA: Shut up!
MAYA: [laughing]
[gasps]
ANNA: Oh, my God, you guys.
‐ Wait, is it this car?
ANNA: No, it's the convertible.
MAYA: Oh, my God!
ANNA: It's pretty sleek.
That's amazing.
That's like my‐‐
MAYA: Yeah.
‐ Oh, my God. Steve.
GABE: That's pretty cool.
MAYA: I'm gonna go
in the front seat,
and you can go in the b‐‐
what?
Steve.
‐ Hey.
‐ Steve.
[chuckles]
What's up?
STEVE: 'Sup?
ANNA: You're here.
‐ Try not to tell anyone.
‐ We're just looking
at my dad's, um, convertible.
It's new, so...
‐ You mean that sweet Solara?
‐ Uh, the convertible?
Yeah.
[sniffs]
‐ So let's check it out.
‐ Kay.
STEVE: Does your dad know
that he can get
the upgrade
to the sports package?
These are pretty sweet, though.
He's got the JBL stereo.
‐ Yeah.
‐ So many stars.
STEVE: Yeah.
They're all dead.
MAYA: [chuckles]
‐ I think that
we need to, like,
leave them alone.
MAYA: Stop.
‐ You guys need to get a room.
MAYA: Anna!
‐ Don't get my dad's seats
dirty.
‐ That's disgusting.
‐ Or do, and just
wipe it down after.
It's Model 3B
high‐perforated leather.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Yeah. [chuckles]
‐ Should we go up?
‐ Um...sure.
‐ Kay..
‐ So did your parents
see the show?
‐ Mom did.
She, uh‐‐she loved
the glitter thing, by the way.
I told her that wasn't me.
That was all Kone.
"Cameron‐esque"
was my exact phrase.
As in, James.
‐ [quietly]
Yeah.
Um, are you close
with your mom?
‐ She's the strongest woman
I know.
‐ And your dad?
‐ He doesn't live here.
They're divorced.
‐ Mine are too.
‐ But your dad's here?
ANNA: Yeah.
They're divorcing, but they
kind of share the house.
‐ Sounds worse than
the "every other weekend" deal.
‐ Oh, yeah.
STEVE: Yeah.
I don't know.
‐ It's weird.
STEVE: [chuckles]
Want some?
‐ Um...
Yeah, like,
I just have to check
if Maya might want some too.
‐ I think she might be
a little busy.
Little man's making his move.
ANNA: Yeah.
[door creaks]
[dramatic musical flourish]
[singer vocalizing softly]
♪ ♪
What?
‐ What?
‐ It's...
‐ No, I'm just happy.
For her. For Maya.
[laughs quietly]
Yeah, fine. Whatever.
‐ [laughs]
‐ Can't believe I'm doing this.
‐ It's no big deal.
[laughs quietly]
‐ Oh, my God.
Sorry.
[coughs]
‐ Yeah, that's how you know
it's the good stuff.
‐ Oh, my God.
Am I gonna get drunk?
‐ Yeah.
‐ [laughing]
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
‐ [mimics engine revving]
[mimics tires squealing]
Pull over! It's the cops!
I said, it's the cops, bitch!
‐ [chuckles]
You're funny.
‐ No, I'm not.
‐ You are.
‐ Are you mad at me?
‐ No.
‐ Do you wanna, like,
kiss me now?
‐ Someone could see.
Um...
‐ We can just put
the seats down.
[whirring]
[soft music]
♪ ♪
[chuckles]
‐ [sighs heavily]
♪ ♪
GABE: [kisses]
MAYA: Uh...
GABE: [kissing]
That's my jaw.
Um...
Uh...
‐ What?
‐ You know how...
when we sort of kissed
in my room,
you said that you had
butterflies?
‐ Yeah.
‐ I‐‐I didn't.
‐ Okay.
‐ I'm sorry.
I still think that you're
one of the best actors
I've ever known, and...
it was an honor
to share the stage with you.
It j‐‐
‐ Kay.
‐ It's not you.
I'm just trying to be honest.
I'm gonna‐‐
I'm gonna go inside.
‐ Okay.
‐ Kay.
[sobs]
[door creaks, closes]
‐ [crying]
[mellow music]
‐ [laughs quietly]
I'm buzzed.
[both laughing]
‐ Oh, my God.
♪ ♪
‐ What happened to funny man?
[Maya sniffles]
‐ Maya...
Um, I have to go check on Maya.
So...bye.
‐ You do you, Kone.
♪ ♪
‐ May...
‐ [quietly]
Hey.
‐ What happened?
‐ Nothing.
‐ Was the kiss bad?
‐ No. I got dumped.
[cries]
‐ No.
‐ He dumped me.
Yeah.
‐ What is wrong with him?
‐ I don't know.
ANNA: He's such an idiot.
‐ My heart hurts, like...
‐ I can feel your heart energy,
and it's gonna get better.
Okay?
‐ Yeah.
‐ And you're gonna have
a million boyfriends
in your life, May, and they're
all gonna be so lucky.
‐ [laughing] No, I'm not.
‐ Yeah, you are.
‐ No, I'm not.
No, I know I'm ugly now.
And I'm okay with it.
‐ Don't say that.
It's not true.
‐ I don't care.
ANNA: I do.
[sighs]
[soft music]
See that one little star
up there?
‐ Where?
‐ The brightest one
that's a little droopy.
‐ Yeah.
‐ That's you.
‐ [laughing weakly]
♪ ♪
Well, all the stars are dead.
‐ They're still bright,
even at their lowest.
♪ ♪
Just like you.
[chuckles]
‐ [laughs]
♪ ♪
Thanks.
[sniffs]
[knocking]
Oh, my God.
CURTIS: You girls ready to go?
MAYA: Yeah.
‐ Dad, yeah.
Right, May?
MAYA: Yeah, let's go.
‐ Okay. Keys?
ANNA: Okay.
‐ Thanks.
‐ Did you tell Mom
that we're leaving?
‐ Yeah, yeah.
She's just...in a nasty mood.
‐ Is she okay?
I feel like
I should go say bye.
‐ Okay.
‐ Be right back, May.
[soft music]
CURTIS: Don't get caught
in her crossfire.
[chuckles]
♪ ♪
[laughter, indistinct chatter]
‐ Oh, Anna, where's Maya?
♪ ♪
KATHY: [sniffling]
‐ Hey, Mom.
‐ Hello, sweetie.
Just paying the check.
‐ I just want
to say, like, bye.
‐ Bye.
Have‐‐have fun in the car.
‐ Um...
Sorry.
I just also, like,
want to say
that I'm sorry that...
That I'm, like, kind of
not nice to you sometimes.
‐ It's okay.
It's okay.
‐ No, it's not,
'cause you don't deserve it.
And I also want to say, like...
I'm sorry that, like, Dad's
not nice to you sometimes.
‐ I‐‐I never want you to‐‐
I‐‐I don't want you to‐‐
to have to see me
like this anymore.
I never want you
to see me like this again.
I‐‐I don't want you
to be like this.
‐ I'm sorry, I'm‐‐
be mean to‐‐again.
[sniffs]
KATHY: You're so beautiful.
‐ No...
[sniffs]
‐ [giggles]
‐ I love you.
‐ And I think you are strong,
just so you know.
I really do, actually.
Honestly, you're so strong,
you're like
behind‐the‐scenes strong.
Like, you don't even know
what that means
'cause you're not a techie,
but like, it means a lot.
‐ Okay.
‐ And also...
Thanks for the glitter.
‐ [laughs]
‐ Seriously.
‐ You saved the whole show.
‐ [laughs]
[car horn honks]
‐ So wonderful.
‐ Oh.
Um‐‐
‐ You should go.
‐ No, but I don't have
to drive with him, honestly.
‐ Oh, no.
‐ I can just drive with you.
‐ It's okay.
You should go.
You're gonna go,
and you're gonna have fun.
You're gonna go
with your friends.
Come on.
‐ I'll see you at home.
‐ Yes. Have fun.
You were so great tonight.
‐ No, I wasn't.
‐ Yeah, you were.
YUKI: Is she not
gonna say good‐bye?
‐ No, she wanted me to tell you
that she's gonna wait in there.
‐ Is she okay?
‐ Yeah.
She had a little thing
with a boy.
‐ Oh.
‐ [sniffs]
YUKI: Yeah?
‐ You all set?
ANNA: Mm‐hmm.
‐ Hey, good job tonight.
Really good.
CURTIS: Good night.
‐ Thanks.
CURTIS: See you.
‐ Good to see you.
CURTIS: Take care.
ANNA: Did you beep at me, Maya?
‐ Maya, don't forget
to brush your teeth.
‐ I know.
‐ Proud of you!
MAYA: Dad, stop.
[zips loudly]
[engine rumbling]
[The Chiffons'
"One Fine Day" playing]
‐ All set?
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ Bye.
‐ Bye!
ANNA: Bye!
SINGERS:
♪ Shooby‐dooby‐dooby ♪
♪ Dooby‐doo, wop‐bop ♪
SINGER: ♪ One fine day ♪
SAM: Maya!
SINGER:
♪ You'll look at me ♪
♪ And you will know
our love was meant to be ♪
♪ One fine day ♪
♪ You're gonna want me
for your girl ♪
SINGERS:
♪ Shooby‐dooby‐dooby ♪
♪ Dooby‐doo, wop‐bop ♪
CURTIS: We're gonna have
some adventures
in this baby, aren't we?
Me and you.
SINGER: ♪ Proud to have me
right by your side ♪
♪ One fine day ♪
‐ Did your mom tell you?
ANNA: Hmm?
SINGER: ♪ You're gonna want me
for your girl ♪
‐ Hmm?
‐ What?
‐ She's getting the house.
♪ ♪
But, um...
but I get to look
for a new apartment.
SINGER: ♪ Who only wants
to run around ♪
‐ Will you help me with that?
SINGER: ♪ I'll be waiting ♪
♪ And someday, darling ♪
♪ You'll come to me ♪
‐ You'll have to decide
who you want to live with.
♪ ♪
Me or your mom.
SINGER:
♪ We'll meet once more ♪
♪ And then you'll want
the love ♪
♪ You threw away before ♪
♪ One fine day ♪
♪ You're gonna want me
for your girl ♪
♪ ♪
[singers vocalizing]
♪ One fine day ♪
♪ You're gonna want me
for your girl ♪
SINGERS:
♪ One fine day ♪
♪ You're gonna want me
for your girl ♪
SINGER: ♪ One fine day ♪
SINGERS:
♪ One fine day ♪
♪ You're gonna want me
for your girl ♪
SINGER: ♪ One fine day... ♪
[sweeping orchestral music]
♪ ♪