‐ day of the show! Are you excited?
Um, yeah, I guess I will be
if it's not a total disaster
'cause nobody's prepped,
especially Maya, so‐‐
you know what, though?
I don't want to talk about it,
'cause it's stressing me out.
Dad, we're late!
- Wait, munch.
- Yeah!
Anna, here. Here's your glitter.
‐ okay, so I said that I
didn't want that already, so‐‐
‐ but this is to remind
you that you sparkle.
‐ okay, cool. Whatever. Thank you!
- Dad!
- Coming.
Coming, goof.
‐ so, um... Shoulders back.
Break a leg. I love you.
Give me a hug.
‐ you know what?
I don't want a hug. I'm late.
‐ you look beautiful, sweetie.
Debra.
Divorce.
Wolves.
Or what, Debra?
You gonna divorce me?
You gonna feed me to the wolves?
No.
Wol‐‐
come in.
‐ hey, there you are.
Just wanted to say, break a leg.
‐ oh. Um, thank you.
Uh, you too.
‐ uh, p. S., you should totally
keep your hair like that.
It looks really cool.
‐ thanks.
‐ phone, phone, phone, phone, phone.
Pound, pound, pound, pound, pound.
Okay, you guys. Five minutes.
‐ I saw you.
I saw you with my own two eyes.
You were backing away. Backing away.
Were you doing your
business with Sheila?
You rat bastard. Rat bastard.
- ‐ where's my hat?
- Okay, places in five.
Hey. ‐ hey.
‐ umm, I didn't hear
from you last night.
‐ can't hear you. I
have my headphones on.
‐ I didn't hear from you last night.
‐ I didn't hear from you either.
Um, if you don't find your light,
the whole thing's gonna go wacko, so...
‐ okay, do you know how many lines
I have to remember right now?
‐ 422. Congratulations.
Find your light.
‐ the light will find me, Anna.
Like, seriously.
Honestly, all you have to do right now
is just, like, pep me up.
Like, pep me up. Just
say, like, "break a leg."
Whatever. What‐‐you haven't
said that once to me.
- ‐ your feelings are valid.
- Mm‐hmm.
- ‐ so are mine.
‐ and you can't take
constructive criticism.
That's my feeling. ‐ are you kidding?
- ‐ and good luck.
- Okay, you just jinxed me.
It's "break a leg," so now I'm gonna
be really bad in the
play, but it's fine.
Let's just hold each other's
hand and say, "I'm sorry."
‐ I'm not ready right now.
‐ well, I'm not really
ready for it either.
I was honestly just saying it
'cause I thought it was
the right thing to do.
So... ‐ wow.
Places in 4 minutes, 15 seconds.
‐ okay.
Psycho.
Yep.
‐ hi.
‐ are you still feeling sick?
‐ no, I'm just, uh, concentrating.
‐ kay, well, I'm really looking forward
to 4 minutes and 32
seconds into the play.
It's our kiss.
‐ oh...
Yeah.
‐ kay, well... Break a leg, cutie.
You too...
Cutie. ‐ kay.
- Bye.
Actors, places. Actors to places.
‐
‐ shut up!
I saw you!
I saw you with my own two eyes!
You're nuts.
‐ Sheila was backing away from you.
She was scared out of her mind.
‐ she's not in her light.
She's not in her light. ‐
she was scared out of her mind.
Honey, help me with this, will you?
It's giving me a rash.
‐ a rash, a rash. Always
something with you.
‐ Bryce, are you there?
Be careful with it. ‐ go to two.
- Go to two.
- Careful with it, I said.
Jesus Christ! ‐ all
right, relax, will you?
You're wriggling around like a worm,
and you're hairier than a bigfoot.
‐
Your fingers are greasy
schlubs, that's why.
Forget it, will you?
I said just get it‐‐off!
- Jesus Christ.
- All right.
Jesus Christ, I said. Jesus Christ.
- ‐ cue 30.
- What do you want?
- Want me to stay?
- Cue 30.
Want me to go? Make
up your mind, woman!
Make up your mind.
‐ no, that's cue 22.
Yeah.
Too damn dark in this joint.
Don't you dare make another drink.
I'm telling you, don't you do it!
‐ or what, Debra?
You gonna divorce me?
You gonna feed me to the wolves?
I don't have to listen
to your loud‐mouth crap.
Just let me do my business. ‐ yeah?
Were you doing your
business with Sheila?
You rat bastard.
‐ you wanna do this? Let's do this.
Let's let it all out. ‐ go light.
Go light.
Come on, baby.
- ‐ shit.
- Give me your best shot.
‐ you get away from me.
‐ isn't this... What you want?
‐ you don't know the first
thing about what I want!
You get your hands off me, you pig!
‐
Or what?
‐ Come on, Maya.
‐
‐ or what?
‐ or...
‐ Come on, Maya.
Or...
‐
‐ "or I'll scream so..."
‐ or I'll scream so loud,
you won't know what hit ya!
Whoo!
‐ yeah, yeah. Just...
Go to sleep.
‐ I already am, Joe.
I already am.
Sun's almost up.
‐ the days are short, Joe.
The days are short.
- Ready, star?
- Let's do this.
Maya, shut the door, please.
‐ you get it.
I mean, they're gonna swarm us.
- Hi.
- Great job tonight.
Oh, my god, that guy‐‐
so crazy!
♪ What a very special time for me ♪
‐ stop!
♪ As I remember, what a night ♪
Stop!
‐ oh, my god.
Okay. Sorry.
Oh, attitude like crazy.
Oh, my god, cheese!
Can we have some?
‐ thank you!
‐ hey. ‐ get outta here!
‐ oh, sorry.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Oh, my god!
Stop!
♪ I got a funny feeling
when she walked... ♪
‐ get out.
‐ I was about to pet him.
♪ As I recall it ended much too soon ♪
Oh, sorry.
That guy is looking‐‐
oh, there they are!
All right!
No. No, no. Wait, wait, wait. Stay.
Dad, no! ‐ no, please.
I‐‐I gotta turn this on.
All right, smile.
Come on. One, two, three, smile.
‐ dad! You're gonna, like, blind me.
You were amazing! Come on.
You have to get used to getting
pictures taken all the time
'cause you're a star. ‐ no, I'm not.
‐ that was dope, young bowl.
‐ thank you. Really? ‐ mm‐hmm.
‐ so what, now you're a star,
you don't bring your own jacket?
‐ no, I'm not a star. I'm an actress.
I forgot it.
- ‐ well done.
- Wasn't she great?
She was so good tonight. I know‐‐
- ‐ dad, stop, seriously.
- I'm her father.
You were amazing tonight, angel,
and these are for you
from me and your dad.
‐ techies don't get flowers.
Like... But thanks.
Where's dad?
‐ um, I don't know, sweetie.
I‐‐I was wondering the same thing.
So that glitter I gave you...
‐ yeah, I used it.
It was an emergency, so...
‐ it was a nice touch.
You probably saved the
whole thing, huh?
‐ mom, are you out of your mind?
Don't do that.
‐ oh, my god, my dad is being
so annoying and so loud.
‐ I don't know what that's like.
‐ ugh.
‐ oh, my god, it's your boyfriend.
Oh, there he is! The man of the house.
Gabe, you were great tonight.
‐ dad, stop. ‐ ow!
‐ Maya, stop it.
‐ see you guys.
Uh, hi. We're‐‐we're her parents.
‐ yeah, that's Gabe. ‐
so nice to meet you.
‐ yeah, it's good to
officially meet you.
You know, she talked about you
about rehearsals and everything.
‐ no, I didn't. ‐ well, you did.
Stop. You're literally killing me.
‐ okay, okay. Hey, listen.
I want a picture of you.
I want a picture of the
both of you; Come on.
The stars of the show. Right
here, come on, together.
All right? A little closer.
- ‐ dad, stop.
- Yeah, that's good.
All right, you ready?
One, two, three, grandkids!
‐ dad, don't say that. Like‐‐
‐ all right, all right, all right.
He's so embarrassing. I'm sorry.
‐
‐ sorry.
Your hair looks different.
It's hot.
‐ thanks.
You too. Your‐‐your hair is hot.
‐ welcome.
‐ Um...
I didn't see you after the play.
‐ yeah.
‐ okay.
Hey, are you guys hungry?
Would you like some groovy nachos?
‐ dad, don't say "groovy nachos"!
‐ oh, I'd like an order
of groovy nachos too.
Two orders of groovy nachos,
and I want a coke
for that table over there
for that young man.
‐ dad, don't, or I'll stick
an ice pick up your butthole!
Stop!
- Oh, no, you okay, hon'?
- No.
What's wrong?
‐ close it. ‐ what? Okay.
‐ close it! ‐ I'll‐‐I'll
keep it closed.
‐ hold it. ‐ what's wrong, girl?
You okay?
‐ yeah, I'm fine, I just, like,
I was out there with
Gabe, and I just, like,
tried to grab his hand
like this, and he went‐‐
‐ that's so cute. ‐ no,
and he went like that.
‐ maybe his hand slipped.
‐ no, but then when we were onstage,
we were planning to do a real kiss,
and he put his hand over his mouth,
like, at the last second.
‐ it's okay. Hey, I'm sorry‐‐sorry.
‐ stop, we're in here!
‐ just two more seconds.
‐ is it my breath?
‐ lt's good.
No, no, really‐‐ ‐ oh, my god!
‐ no, no, no, no. No, it's good.
And do you know‐‐ can
I ask you a question?
Were you nervous out
there, for your kiss?
‐ I mean, yeah, 'cause it's,
like, in front of everyone,
and like, it's my first kiss.
‐ so he was probably nervous too.
I think that you just
gotta do it again,
and you gotta go for what you want,
and it's gonna happen.
‐ okay, yeah. Yeah, all right.
Fine. I'm just gonna‐‐
‐ I see how he looks at you.
‐ stop. ‐ it's true.
‐ okay. All right, fine.
‐ let's do this.
‐ okay, but be quiet.
I don't want to be obvious about it.
Okay, just like, literally
don't look, and like, if‐‐
‐ hey.
‐ oh, my god, my dad's here.
I'm gonna say hi. ‐ oh, my god, really?
Okay, I'll be there in a sex‐‐ sec.
‐ what's up?
‐ you always say that.
‐ yeah.
True.
Um... ‐ so...
‐ yeah.
‐ what? ‐ I just, you know...
Wanted to say that, uh, you know...
‐ what?
‐ you were‐‐you‐‐I‐‐you were
just really good in the play.
‐ no, I wasn't.
‐ no, yes, you were, seriously. ‐ no.
‐ I knew you were funny, but...
I've never seen you like that before.
- You're really...
- Good.
‐ thanks.
‐ and...
I‐‐I also wanted to
say, like, you know,
once and for all or
whatever, that, uh...
Never mind.
‐ no. Say it.
Fool.
‐ I'm‐‐I'm really sorry
about everything.
I‐‐I wish I didn't do all that stuff.
Fool.
‐ what are you even doing here?
I'm, you know‐‐I'm with Gabe.
We're celebrating. ‐ oh, yeah.
Yeah.
‐ my boyfriend.
- ‐ yes.
- Yeah.
‐ yeah, your boyfriend.
- Um...
What was‐‐what was up with
that kiss in the play?
‐ I don't know. Why?
‐ no reason. Nothing. ‐ why?
Did he say something?
‐ no.
Um, but I mean, you know,
I wouldn't have put my
hand over my mouth.
‐
‐ so you know, I guess I
should've auditioned.
So‐‐or something.
‐ I don't know. Maybe.
‐ yeah. ‐ I guess you should've.
Yeah. ‐ or not. I don't know.
- Yeah.
- Kay. Bye.
‐ bye.
‐ so‐‐well, how was it?
How was the play?
‐ it was... Good.
It was bumpy at first,
and then it got...
Better, but pretty good.
‐ Anna made such an impact
as the stage manager,
and there was point whe‐‐
‐ yeah, that's great.
Hey.
Did, uh, Kathy give you the
flowers that we got you?
‐ yes. ‐
‐ thank you so much. ‐ absolutely.
‐ they're so pretty. Where
did you guys get them?
‐ uh, where did we get
the flowers, Kathy?
‐ I got them from stop and shop.
Really? ‐ yes.
‐ you know, there are much
better places to get flowers
than stop and shop.
Right?
Hey, did your mom clap,
or did she do that weird
yodeling thing that she does?
‐ she did the weird yodel thing.
It was so embarrassing.
Honestly.
Mm‐hmm. ‐ where were you?
‐ you want to know? You ready?
‐ did you get a new car?
‐ New!
- Used.
- What kind?
It's a solara.
It's right out back.
- ‐ excuse me.
- It's really cool.
You're gonna love it.
‐ so that's where you were.
Uh‐huh. ‐ that's great.
‐ it's a convertible too.
Oh, my god, curt, you got
a frickin' convertible?
Yep, I got a convertible.
- Can we go in it?
- Absolutely.
Oh, my god. ‐ just don't
drive it too far.
Oh, my god. ‐
‐ oh, my god.
He got a convertible.
Um, I love your earring,
by the way, curt.
‐ you know, I've always had the hole.
I just got a new hoop.
Oh, my god, your dad is crazy.
So I did this weasel.
Here, I did the gloves. I
also did the barbed wire.
‐ wait, wait. You did all of this?
‐ yeah, last night I went to kinkos.
I even got the glossy‐‐
‐ guy‐‐guys, guys.
This is‐‐this is great.
I think we're ready to distribute.
Sorry. Right? That's
what I was thinking.
‐ hey.
Um, Anna's dad got a new convertible,
and we were gonna, like, check it out.
What? He did.
‐ he did. ‐ do you wanna come?
‐ hell yeah. ‐ yeah.
The only thing‐‐ sorry, you guys.
There's only room for one,
so I don't know how to decide,
but I'm thinking Maya's boyfriend...
Stop.
- Sorry.
- That's me, so...
‐ just so they have time to be like...
‐ stop.
‐ all right, I'm‐‐ I'm gonna go.
‐ kay. ‐ don't eat all the pizza.
‐ I won't.
That's some bullshit.
‐ yeah, whatever.
Shut up!
Oh, my god, you guys.
‐ wait, is it this car?
No, it's the convertible.
Oh, my god!
It's pretty sleek.
That's amazing.
That's like my‐‐ Maya: Yeah.
‐ oh, my god. Steve.
That's pretty cool.
I'm gonna go in the front seat,
and you can go in the b‐‐ what?
Steve. ‐ hey.
‐ Steve.
- What's up?
- 'Sup?
You're here. ‐ try not to tell anyone.
‐ we're just looking at my
dad's, um, convertible.
It's new, so...
‐ you mean that sweet solara?
‐ uh, the convertible? Yeah.
‐ so let's check it out.
‐ kay.
Does your dad know that he can get
the upgrade to the sports package?
These are pretty sweet, though.
He's got the jbl stereo.
‐ yeah.
‐ so many stars.
Yeah. They're all dead.
‐ I think that we need to, like,
leave them alone.
Stop. ‐ you guys need to get a room.
Anna!
‐ don't get my dad's seats dirty.
‐ that's disgusting.
‐ or do, and just wipe it down after.
It's model 3b high‐perforated leather.
‐ yeah. ‐ yeah.
‐ should we go up?
‐ um... Sure. ‐ kay..
‐ so did your parents see the show?
‐ mom did.
She, uh‐‐she loved the
glitter thing, by the way.
I told her that wasn't me.
That was all kone.
"Cameron‐esque" was my exact phrase.
As in, James.
‐ Yeah.
Um, are you close with your mom?
‐ she's the strongest woman I know.
‐ and your dad?
‐ he doesn't live here.
They're divorced.
‐ mine are too.
- ‐ but your dad's here?
- Yeah.
They're divorcing, but they
kind of share the house.
‐ sounds worse than the
"every other weekend" deal.
- ‐ oh, yeah.
- Yeah.
I don't know. ‐ it's weird.
Want some?
‐ um...
Yeah, like, I just have to check
if Maya might want some too.
‐ I think she might be a little busy.
- Little man's making his move.
- Yeah.
What? ‐ what?
‐ it's... ‐ what?
‐ it's... ‐ no, I'm just happy.
For her. For Maya.
Yeah, fine. Whatever.
‐ ‐ can't believe I'm doing this.
‐ it's no big deal.
‐ oh, my god.
Sorry.
‐ yeah, that's how you
know it's the good stuff.
‐ oh, my god. Am I gonna get drunk?
‐ yeah.
‐ Oh, my god. Oh, my god.
‐
Pull over! It's the cops!
I said, it's the cops, bitch!
‐
You're funny.
‐ no, I'm not.
‐ you are.
‐ are you mad at me?
‐ no.
‐ do you wanna, like, kiss me now?
‐ someone could see.
Um...
‐ we can just put the seats down.
‐
Uh...
That's my jaw.
Um...
Uh...
‐ what? ‐ what?
‐ you know how...
When we sort of kissed in my room,
you said that you had butterflies?
‐ yeah.
‐ I‐‐I didn't.
‐ okay.
‐ I'm sorry.
I still think that you're
one of the best actors
I've ever known, and...
It was an honor to share
the stage with you.
It j‐‐
‐ kay.
‐ it's not you.
I'm just trying to be honest.
I'm gonna‐‐ I'm gonna go inside.
‐ okay. ‐ okay.
‐ kay.
‐
I'm buzzed.
‐ oh, my god.
‐ what happened to funny man?
‐ Maya...
Um, I have to go check on Maya.
So... Bye.
‐ you do you, kone.
‐ may...
‐ Hey.
‐ what happened? ‐ nothing.
‐ was the kiss bad?
‐ no. I got dumped.
‐ no.
‐ he dumped me. Yeah.
‐ what is wrong with him?
‐ I don't know.
He's such an idiot.
‐ my heart hurts, like...
‐ I can feel your heart energy,
and it's gonna get better.
Okay? ‐ yeah.
‐ and you're gonna have
a million boyfriends
in your life, may, and they're
all gonna be so lucky.
‐ no, I'm not. ‐ yeah, you are.
‐ no, I'm not.
No, I know I'm ugly now.
And I'm okay with it.
‐ don't say that. It's not true.
- ‐ I don't care.
- I do.
See that one little star up there?
‐ where?
‐ the brightest one
that's a little droopy.
‐ yeah.
‐ that's you.
‐
Well, all the stars are dead.
‐ they're still bright,
even at their lowest.
Just like you.
‐
Thanks.
- Oh, my god.
- You girls ready to go?
Yeah. ‐ dad, yeah.
- Right, may?
- Yeah, let's go.
‐ okay. Keys?
Okay. ‐ thanks.
‐ did you tell mom that we're leaving?
‐ yeah, yeah.
She's just... In a nasty mood.
‐ is she okay?
I feel like I should go say bye.
‐ okay.
‐ be right back, may.
Don't get caught in her crossfire.
‐ oh, Anna, where's Maya?
‐ hey, mom.
‐ hello, sweetie.
Just paying the check.
‐ I just want to say, like, bye.
‐ bye.
Have‐‐have fun in the car.
‐ um...
Sorry.
I just also, like,
want to say that I'm sorry that...
That I'm, like, kind of not
nice to you sometimes.
‐ it's okay.
It's okay.
‐ no, it's not, 'cause
you don't deserve it.
And I also want to say, like...
I'm sorry that, like, dad's
not nice to you sometimes.
‐ I‐‐I never want you to‐‐
I‐‐I don't want you to‐‐
to have to see me like this anymore.
I never want you to see
me like this again.
I‐‐I don't want you to be like this.
‐ I'm sorry, I'm‐‐ be mean to‐‐again.
You're so beautiful.
‐ no...
‐
‐ I love you. ‐ I love you.
‐ and I think you are
strong, just so you know.
I really do, actually.
Honestly, you're so strong,
you're like behind‐the‐scenes strong.
Like, you don't even
know what that means
'cause you're not a techie,
but like, it means a lot.
‐ okay. ‐ and also...
Thanks for the glitter.
‐ ‐ seriously.
‐ you saved the whole show.
‐
‐ so wonderful.
‐ oh.
Um‐‐ ‐ you should go.
‐ no, but I don't have to
drive with him, honestly.
‐ oh, no. ‐ I can just drive with you.
‐ it's okay.
You should go.
You're gonna go, and
you're gonna have fun.
You're gonna go with your friends.
Come on.
‐ I'll see you at home.
‐ yes. Have fun.
You were so great tonight.
‐ no, I wasn't. ‐ yeah, you were.
Is she not gonna say good‐bye?
‐ no, she wanted me to tell you
that she's gonna wait in there.
‐ is she okay?
‐ yeah. She had a little thing
with a boy. ‐ oh.
‐ Yuki: Yeah?
- ‐ you all set?
- Mm‐hmm.
‐ hey, good job tonight. Really good.
Good night. ‐ thanks.
See you. ‐ good to see you.
- Take care.
- Did you beep at me, Maya?
‐ Maya, don't forget
to brush your teeth.
‐ I know. ‐ proud of you!
Dad, stop.
‐ all set? ‐ mm‐hmm.
‐ bye. ‐ bye!
Bye!
Maya!
We're gonna have some adventures
in this baby, aren't we?
Me and you.
♪ Proud to have me right by your side ♪
- ‐ did your mom tell you?
- Hmm?
♪ You're gonna want me for your girl ♪
‐ hmm?
‐ what?
‐ she's getting the house.
But, um...
But I get to look for a new apartment.
♪ Who only wants to run around ♪
‐ will you help me with that?
‐ you'll have to decide who
you want to live with.
Me or your mom.