‐ Oh, God.
You can't put that there.
‐ Oh, where can I put it, then?
I've got waiters
coming in and out.
Just somewhere not in the way.
One, two, a‐one, two, one, two.
I, I am hiding
The you I show to you
is just a lie
You take what you want,
you get what you take
Lie
‐  High, high, high
‐ Maya!
Are you ready?
Come on, let's go!
‐ Wait, Mom,
you're making onigiri?
‐ Yeah.
‐ No, I want a turkey sandwich.
‐ Oh, go get dressed.
Go get dressed.
You'll catch cold.
‐ Okay, but can you make
a turkey sandwich?
‐ I will.
Mom!
Can you help me find
my HitClip?
I can't find it!
Mom, come on!
Ah.
Okay!
Coming.
I last saw it
in the living room.
I have it!
- Give it back!
-  I have it
I love this song
‐ Maya, give it back!
‐  Za‐la‐la‐la‐la‐‐
‐ Stop! Shuji!
‐ Shuji, stop!
‐ Just 'cause we're
half‐siblings doesn't mean
you get to keep half my stuff!
‐ Don't say that!
We're brother‐sister, you‐‐
‐ Shuji, stop it!
‐ No, we're not, you idiot.
Half, half.
‐ Ow!
Mom, just tell him to stop!
‐ Just‐‐just stop.
Give him that "Shit Grip" back.
Huh?
‐ Did you just call it "shit"?
Mom, that's not
what it's called.
It's called a HitClip.
Say it again, say it again.
‐ HitGrip.
‐ No!
HitClip!
‐ HitGrip!
‐ Say "Oreo McFlurry."
‐ Oh, Maya, no.
‐ Say it!
‐ Come on, do it.
You got it.
‐ Oleo MacFurry.
Enough!
Okay, go get ready‐‐
Go!
Shuji!
- Go get dressed.
- You bitch!
- Breakfast ready.
- Come on.
‐ Yuki!
‐ Yes, Fred?
You think I need
to wear a coat today?
‐ I don't know.
It's in the 60s.
So not a cardigan.
You think I need
to wear a coat?
‐ Cardigan or coat,
whatever you like.
Come on, everybody,
breakfast is ready!
Hurry up!
Oh, honey,
this looks beautiful.
Ugh, I am so hungry.
This is great.
Uh‐‐oh, hey,
do we have any hot sauce?
Yeah.
Ugh, I'm sorry, it's gone.
So I'll get it this afternoon.
‐ Shut up.
‐ Get off of me.
‐ Stop.
Just give it to me.
‐ No.
Get away, you annoying freak.
‐ Mom!
‐ Maya, enough.
Shut up.
‐ Oh, my God, Mom, you just
told your daughter to shut up.
What's wrong with you?
‐ Maya, stop it.
‐ That's crazy.
What a big bite.
Ay, ay, ay, ay, yah.
Oh, it's‐‐that's Kathy.
‐ I didn't even eat.
‐ You were late, so come on.
‐ I got to go, too.
‐ Don't forget to bring‐‐
take everything.
I'm seeing Frank and his trio.
Oh, honey,
can you call Richard?
He's gonna ask
about the tour dates.
Can you just give him a call?
‐ Okay.
‐ Thank you.
‐ Bye.
‐ All right.
‐ Oh!
Maya, Shuji!
Your lunches!
‐ Bye.
Bitch.
‐ No parking
if you're not handicapped.
‐ Bitch.
‐ You don't have a sign.
‐ Bitch, bitch.
I'm sorry.
Mm‐hmm.
‐ No.
Mm.
Yuki...
‐ Mm.
‐ Oh, I‐‐
I got to go.
Ah.
Hello, Doctor?
Yeah, this is Yuki.
I can't make it today, uh,
can I reschedule, please?
Oh, okay.
Good‐‐goodbye, Doctor.
‐ Mm.
Ah...
‐ Ah, mm.
‐ Ah.
Eh?
‐ Okay.
Mm.
‐ Mm.
‐ You knowing English and
working as an interpreter
inspired me to learn English.
It's what helped me
get this job.
‐ Wow, that's very good.
Yeah.
‐ Arigato.
‐ Ooh‐‐
‐ Sorry.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
It's only my boobs.
Your boobs?
‐ Stevie Wonder?
No.
‐ Yes.
Ah!
‐ Eh?
Ah.
If you see me walkin'
down the street
And I start to cry
each time we meet
Walk on by
Make believe that you don't
see the tears
Just let me grieve
in private
'Cause each time I see you
I break down and cry
Walk on by
Don't stop
I just can't
get over losin' you
And so if I seem
broken and blue
Walk on by
Foolish pride,
that's all that I have left
So let me hide
The tears and the sadness
you gave me
When you said goodbye...
‐ Hey. I didn't know when you
were gonna come home,
so I made
my world‐famous daddy chili.
‐ Were the kids okay?
‐ Yes, yeah, they loved it.
They're in their rooms.
They're fine.
Oh, and I got
some more hot sauce
'cause I didn't see any
in the fridge
and I figured you had a woozy
of a day at the‐‐
at the bank or,
well, wherever you‐‐
I don't know where you were.
‐ I had a long day.
‐ Yeah, well...
‐ But let me‐‐
‐ Oh, no, come on, please.
Let me do this.
You sit right here.
‐ Oh, okay.
Thank you.
‐ All right.
I added a few more
interesting spices here.
‐ Ah, that's‐‐that's enough.
‐ Ah, it's never enough.
There you go.
‐ Thank you, thank you.
Shuji, can you pause the game?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Look.
This reminded me of you.
I love you.
You're my number‐one son.
‐ I'm your only son, Mom.
‐ I know, but...
Anyone would be so lucky
to have you.
‐ Okay, okay, thanks, Mom.
I love you, too.
‐ Okay, okay.
‐ Yes.
Thank you
for the dope painting.
‐ All right.
‐ I like it.
‐ Yeah, it's nice, isn't it?
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ Mm.
Okay. Back to game.
‐  Daddy, Daddy, Daddy, Daddy,
Mommy, Mommy, Mommy, Mommy
Silly, silly, silly, silly
‐ Oh, my funny girl.
Go to sleep.
‐ I don't want to.
‐ I love you.
‐ Do you love me
more than Shuji?
‐ Mm, equal.
But you are
my number‐one daughter,
and I'm so glad
you're my daughter.
‐ That doesn't count.
‐ Yes, it does.
It's important.
‐ Okay, then can I have
a present like Shuji got one?
‐ Okay, when you turn 18,
I'll give you a present
that I got from Stevie Wonder.
‐ Who's that?
‐ Oh, you don't know?
‐ No.
‐ It's okay.
Now go to sleep, okay?
‐ I'm not tired.
‐ Yes, you are.
I'll sing you a song.
‐  Mommy, Mommy,
Mommy, Mommy
‐ No, uh, stop.
‐  Daddy, Daddy,
Daddy, Daddy
Chili, chili, chili, chili,
go to sleep, go to sleep
Everybody sleep, sleep,
everybody sleep, sleep
‐ Okay, okay, enough, enough.
‐ I don't want to.
‐ Go to sleep.
‐ I don't want to go to bed.
Okay.
Fred?
‐ Mm, mm‐hmm?
‐ Listen.
Are you all right?
‐ I want to tell you a story
that I never told you before.
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ Many years ago
I was working on a film called
"Seven Nights in Japan."
It was a British/Japanese
co‐production.
And we were all staying
in a small remote village.
And I was the only one
who spoke the two languages.
And the very first morning,
I brought the British crew
to the Japanese dining room.
The whole Japanese crew
were eating breakfast,
and they're all cracking
raw egg
and putting it over rice.
The British crew,
they all went like,
"Ew, we're not gonna
eat that."
So they asked me
for milk and sugar.
So this time
the Brits pour sugar
and milk over hot rice.
And when they were
eating this,
the Japanese crew
all went, "Ew."
And I was always in the middle
of the two cultures,
stuck there.
And I feel
like I've been like that
with you and with my family.
Sometimes I never know
what's right by you
and what's right by the kids.
I'm being too Japanese
or trying to be too American.
I feel like I'm always stuck
in the middle
of the two cultures.
‐ You...
you never talk about this.
‐ But I'm happy right now.
I'm happy with this life.
‐ You were gone
a long time today.
I missed you.
‐ I missed you, too.