‐ Okay,
why do you keep doing that?
‐ Um, they feel
like marshmallow.
Think that's what happens
when you get your braces off.
‐ Oh, my God, they look
so different.
‐ Thanks.
‐ Do you, like, feel older?
‐ Um, a little,
because this morning
I woke up, and, like,
my boobs were a little bigger.
‐ I mean...
‐ A little bit.
‐ Like, they're huge.
Wow.
‐ They're not huge, but
they're‐‐
‐ No, they're huge.
‐ Girls, uh, let's get
some furikake.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ I know.
‐ Crazy.
‐ Let's go.
‐ All right, let's go.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, miss.
Hi.
‐ Hi.
Wow, you're stunning.
How tall are you?
‐ Um, I'm 5'7 3/4".
‐ You're a model.
Anyone ever tell you that?
Look at your legs.
So long.
‐ Well, thank you.
Thank you.
‐ I'm with Premier Models.
I'd love to have you
come in and try out.
‐ Are you serious?
- Oh, wow.
- Yeah!
‐ Thank you so much.
‐ Here's all the info
for tomorrow.
‐ Okay.
‐ Appointment time here.
‐ Excellent.
Looking forward
to seeing you tomorrow.
‐ You too.
‐ Oh, sorry, hi!
‐ Hi, sorry.
Wait, what was that?
What?
Stop, what?
‐ She just scouted me.
To model.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ I just got scouted.
‐ Mom, Anna's gonna be
a model.
I am hiding
The you I show to you
is just a lie
You take what you want
you get what you take
High, high, high
I told you
a hundred times already,
absolutely not.
‐ Mom, like,
you're not listening, though.
Please, like,
it's all the fashion hubs.
It's New York,
Philadelphia, Tucson‐‐
Like, it's all of them,
and then we can go.
‐ Fine, how much and when?
‐ I told you,
the appointment is today,
and it's, like, 3,000 bucks.
‐ No.
‐ Please, Mom.
‐ I am not spending
this kind of money
on this kind of thing.
We shouldn't be paying them,
they should be paying you!
‐ You keep saying that.
Not the good places.
‐ I am done talking about this.
‐ You don't get it at all.
I've wanted to model
since I was literally born.
Do I help‐‐
‐ Every sign points to a scam.
And I didn't know
you've been wanting to do this
since you were born.
‐ Does a scam have
a pamphlet?
So I don't know why
you keep saying that.
Do you just think
I'm too ugly to model?
‐ You already have
a freshman boyfriend, okay?
And this is where
I draw the line.
‐ Okay, well, the good news is,
is, you're not the boss.
Ever think of that?
So I am calling Dad.
‐ Great, call him.
‐ 'Cause he's the real boss,
you bitch.
‐ You're a bitch.
‐ Oh, am I?
That's so mature.
‐ You're the one
who is acting like a bitch.
‐ Why do you talk to me
like that?
‐ I'm the adult.
I know better.
You're the kid.
Act like a kid.
‐ Don't leave.
Don't leave.
Mom!
No, honestly Anna,
if you were my daughter,
I would totally let you model.
You've done
a runway show before,
and you, like,
you wear hats so well.
Yeah.
They just, like, treat me
like a kid.
Otherwise they're just, like,
"Oh, do everything,
you're an adult."
And then, like, they treat me
like a kid
when it's convenient for them.
Yeah, they're psychopaths.
Like, you need
to get out of there.
Like, I'm‐‐
I'm not kidding.
‐ Can I sleep over?
Yeah, definitely.
Thanks.
‐ When you come here,
I'm gonna, like,
take pictures of you,
and I'm gonna prove
that you're a model.
Like, you seriously
are such a model.
You're more beautiful.
‐ Okay, I gotta go.
- I'll see you soon.
- Okay, love you, bye.
‐ What?
‐ Look what
Mom and Dad let me get.
‐ What is that?
‐ Nokia 3310.
Oh, my God.
‐ Cell phone, dummy.
‐ Nokia 3310.
‐ Strawberries.
‐ It's got a calculator
and a stopwatch.
So now I can time
how long it takes you
to do something annoying.
‐ Dank.
‐ Stop!
Mom?
‐ Hmm?
Do you have
a present for me?
‐ Yeah, I got
the stains out for you.
‐ Where's my cell phone?
‐ Well, you're not
mature enough
for a cell phone, Maya.
‐ What are you even
talking about?
Not mature enough?
‐ You don't even know
how to wipe.
‐ What are you even
talking about?
I wipe fine, Mom.
‐ 11 seconds.
‐ Stop, Shuji.
Mom, I'm so mature.
Why don't I have
a cell phone?
‐ When you're
in eighth grade,
maybe you can have
your own.
‐ Eighth gr‐‐
I'm, like,
never gonna reach
eighth grade.
What are you even
talking about?
‐ Here's my number.
You can call me...
when you learn
how to wipe my butt.
‐ Mom!
Shuji, stop.
That's so unfair.
‐ This is you being immature.
‐ So you love him
more than me?
Okay, I'm gonna run away.
‐ Okay.
‐ So, you're okay with that?
That I'm running away?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Mom, you're okay
with me running away?
I'm going to run away.
‐ All right,
I'll see you later.
‐ Oh, my God.
Okay, so you're okay
with your daughter
running away?
Running away!
I hate you!
Do you hear that, Mom?
You're never gonna
see me again!
I hate you!
I'm gonna die
on the street!
Mama, can you drive me
to Anna's first, though?
Hello?
It's Maya.
‐ Mai?
I thought I was coming to you.
‐ I don't want
to be there anymore.
Like‐‐
What's wrong?
My mom gave
Shuji a cell phone
and said that I wasn't
mature enough for one.
‐ Oh, my God,
that is insane, Mai.
You're the most mature person
I've ever met.
‐ I know.
That's what I said to her.
‐ Yeah, yeah, I agree.
‐ I just don't want
to be there anymore.
I think we should run away.
‐ Mai...
‐ I'm serious.
‐ I know, but it's, like,
I want to be with you,
of course I want
to be with you,
but, like,
where are we gonna go,
and, like, what
are we gonna eat?
‐ Anna, you're gonna model.
‐ Maya.
‐ I'm serious!
Like, you make
tons of money from that,
and that's, like,
what we spend.
We can, like, spend it
on whatever.
‐ Okay. Yeah.
‐ Yeah?
‐ I mean,
I have to try out still.
But I actually don't have
a parent's consent.
‐ Then I sign it.
‐ Maya‐‐
Please?
‐ You really think
I could model?
‐ You're gonna be a model.
‐ Yeah.
‐ My daughter's gonna be
a model.
Please...
‐ Okay.
‐ Really?
And I'll be your mom?
Makeover!
‐ Oh, my God, stop.
‐ Tickle, tickle, tickle.
‐ Okay, we're packing.
‐ I love this.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
‐ Love.
‐ I wanna wear that.
‐ Okay, but, like‐‐
‐ It's, like, silk.
Yes!
Yes.
‐ Look.
Okay, Anna...
‐ Love.
Love that.
‐ Love, right?
‐ Love.
‐ Okay, I'm gonna wear those.
‐ These are like...that.
‐ I want to wear those.
‐ Super low.
‐ Okay.
‐ I love these.
I'm just gonna leave
these options for my mom.
‐ Okay.
‐ And then
I'm gonna get some makeup,
and, um, I'll go get ready.
And don't go
in that drawer, though.
‐ Why?
‐ 'Cause my mom says not to.
I don't know why.
‐ Okay.
Ah.
No, I'm your mom.
Mom.
You go to get Maya‐‐
I've gotta get
my giant pocketbook.
Mm‐hmm.
Mommy's drawer.
‐ No, Daddy,
I'm, like‐‐I do love you.
I was just gone
'cause I'm modeling now.
I'm a model.
I'm just kidding.
I'm still trying
to get an agent.
‐ Mine.
Map.
My map.
This is my coin.
This is just for adults, honey.
It's not for kids.
Just gonna eat
my Thursday candy.
This is my...
Oh.
Mm.
It tickles.
It's a massager.
Okay, I got
so much good stuff.
Oh, you look
so beautiful.
‐ No, you do.
‐ No, I don't.
I'm ugly.
‐ Mai.
‐ No, it's okay.
I'm ugly.
Kind of accepted it.
It's actually kind of freeing.
‐ Okay, that's not true.
I don't know if all of this
is, like, the best idea.
‐ Why?
‐ Well, it's just, like,
I don't know.
No, I'm so excited.
I'm, like‐‐
I can't wait.
Honestly, I'm just, like,
where are we gonna sleep?
Or, like, what
are we gonna eat?
And, like‐‐
Oh, see, you always know
what I need.
‐ No, I don't want
you to feel stressed.
I think this is gonna be fun.
‐ Yeah.
I think I'm just stressed out
about leaving Daddy.
‐ Well, why don't
we just bring Daddy?
‐ You sure?
‐ Seriously.
Daddy, Mommy, and model.
‐ Maya.
‐ Stop, I'm serious.
You're gonna be amazing.
‐ Thanks.
‐ Listen to me.
‐ Okay.
‐ You're seriously gonna get
signed as a model,
and we're gonna move
wherever we want,
and we can get
whatever we want.
‐ Maya.
‐ I'm serious.
And call me "mommy."
‐ Maya.
‐ Call me "Mommy."
‐ Okay, Mommy.
‐ That's gonna be you now.
‐ Maybe in a couple of years.
Knock on wood.
Next stop, Fifth and Krueger.
‐ Okay, next stop.
‐ Is that us?
‐ Hold on. Hold on.
Okay, two stops.
Two stops.
Here, you want a snack?
‐ Oh, my God, Mom.
Mom, thank you so much.
‐ You're welcome, honey.
‐ Can I have more?
I'm a little hungry.
‐ No, you have to watch
your figure.
Little bites.
‐ You look beautiful, girl.
‐ Thank you.
‐ I wonder if our parents
are wondering
where we are right now,
like, freaking out.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ Freaking out.
‐ When my mom realizes
that I'm not sleeping
over at your house,
she's gonna be, like,
missing me.
‐ I bet you mine are calling
the cops right now.
Fred, we gotta plant
some flowers in the front.
‐ I know, I know‐‐
Hey, you know, where's Maya?
‐ She's at Anna's,
spending the night.
‐ Ah, okay.
‐ She's run away.
‐ Good.
'Cause she's the only one
that knows
where the AC adapter is.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
See, I told my mom
this isn't a scam.
‐ You're the only model here.
‐ They must really like me,
I guess.
‐ Okay.
‐ Thanks, Mom.
‐ Mm‐hmm.
Okay, uh, Anna?
‐ Yep, this is her.
‐ Okay, great.
Come on back.
‐ Just to the‐‐
wanna come?
‐ Uh‐‐
‐ No, you're gonna go.
‐ Sorry, how old are you?
‐ She's‐‐
‐ 13.
‐ 14.
I'm her mama.
‐ Uh, okay.
‐ And she's done
lots of runway before,
so you can just‐‐
‐ Okay, that's not really
a prerequisite.
‐ And I just got
my braces off.
‐ Okay.
‐ So...
‐ A lot of people
come through here
wanting to work
with Premier Models.
So, you know,
we'll take a few pictures,
see where you land,
and, uh, if it does work out,
we will need payments,
$3,000.
‐ That's good.
And I'm her parental consent.
And I consent.
‐ She signed it.
‐ It's signed.
‐ As long as, uh‐‐
as long as
the payment works out,
then we should be good.
So, uh, you ready
to come on back
and give it a shot?
‐ Okay.
‐ Um‐‐
‐ Anna.
‐ Uh, what cup size are you?
‐ Cup size is a B.
‐ Okay, that'll work.
Go ahead.
Hi.
‐ Ooh.
Car report.
Best and worst deals.
‐ I don't know
why you're freaking out, Daddy.
You're freaking me out.
She's been in there
a long time, yeah.
Ooh, I don't know.
I don't know.
I think she's
been in there too long.
Maybe I should go
check on her.
Okay.
Sorry, to‐‐Anna?
Oh, my God.
Um, we‐‐we gotta go.
Daddy's outside, freaking out,
so I think we gotta go.
‐ Did you give him food, Maya?
Just give him some food.
‐ No, Daddy
at the police station
has his shift wrong,
and done,
and he has a gun
on a holster.
And he said we gotta go.
‐ He has a gun?
‐ He has a gun.
‐ Oh, yeah, he does.
‐ So put your shirt on.
‐ Okay.
‐ Thank you.
Thank you.
‐ But you‐‐
‐ Go, go, go.
All right, give me those.
Creepy.
Come on.
Ugh, fucking weird.
That was crazy.
That guy was, like‐‐
I don't know.
I didn't like that.
You were in,
like, someone's bikini.
‐ Did I do something bad?
Was that bad?
‐ No.
No, you didn't do
anything bad.
‐ Yeah, 'cause I know
it was weird,
but that's what models do.
So I'm just not ready to model.
‐ Yeah, that's okay.
‐ Yeah.
It just was kind of crazy
what he did to you, like‐‐
‐ It was my fault, though,
because he asked me
if I like bikinis,
and I said yes.
Where are we going?
Home?
Or, um‐‐
‐ I mean, if you want
to go home...
‐ I'm not saying
I want to go home.
I'm saying,
do you want to go home?
‐ That's up to you.
‐ Yeah, I know.
‐ Okay.
‐ Yeah, we don't need
to go home.
‐ So, we'll‐‐
We'll just stick‐‐
‐ Right?
‐ Yeah! Let's do it.
Let's just stick
to the plan.
Like, I don't‐‐
I don't want to go home.
I don't want to see them.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Right now.
‐ Same.
‐ The bus stop was actually
on the other side.
‐ Sorry.
I wish I had someone
to call to give us a ride.
‐ Well, that's why
my mom should've given me
a cell phone.
They really come in handy.
‐ Where are we going?
‐ Um, we're gonna go...
‐ Maya, my arms are heavy.
‐ Yes, I know.
I want to find
a place to rest.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ What?
‐ Look!
Oh, my God.
He's so cute!
You're so cute!
‐ Hi!
‐ Hi! I love you.
‐ Oh, my God, hi.
Hi.
Yeah.
His butt is so bushy.
‐ What's your name, buddy?
Your name, buddy?
‐ Let's call him Golden Butt.
Golden Butt.
‐ I love it.
‐ Should we put Daddy
on Golden Butt's head?
‐ They could be animal buddies.
Oh, yeah.
‐ Animal buddies.
‐ So cute!
‐ So cute.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ There you go.
‐ So cute.
Oh, the animal buddies.
Oh!
Oh, my God.
‐ Hey! Drop it.
Drop it!
Oh, God!
Here, hold it.
‐ D'you think he's still alive?
Drop.
Drop. Drop it.
‐ Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, look.
‐ Is he?
‐ Look.
‐ It's‐‐
‐ He's peeing.
He's peeing.
Daddy is still alive.
‐ Wait, but I can't‐‐
‐ No, no, no,
Daddy's still alive.
Look.
Look, look, look.
He's alive!
‐ No!
Luther!
Luther, come here, baby.
Come on, baby.
Hey, girls,
are you okay?
‐ Your dog has my hamster.
‐ Oh.
Bad Luther.
No‐‐
Drop the rat.
Oh, I'm so sorry, girls.
Do you live
in the neighborhood?
‐ No.
‐ Well, do you want
to come inside
and use my phone
to call your parents?
‐ Um...
‐ Okay, well come on in.
‐ Yeah, okay.
‐ It's gonna be okay.
‐ You okay?
I'm sorry about Daddy,
but I also don't think
we should call our parents
'cause they're gonna kill us,
okay?
Who are you gonna call?
I'm so, so, sorry,
girls.
I'm really sorry.
No, it's okay.
‐ Well, come on inside.
‐ I'm sorry, Daddy.
‐ I'm sorry I was a bad mom.
‐ No, you weren't.
I was.
‐ It's my fault.
I love you, Daddy.
‐ Love you, Daddy.
‐ What's with all the shit?
‐ You mean our stuff?
Like, we ran away.
‐ Yeah.
Like, our moms
are being assholes, so‐‐
‐ Is that why
you two look like
you got sand in your vaginas?
‐ Um, Daddy just died,
so it's not funny.
‐ Wait, what happened
to your dad?
‐ Steven, Daddy?
My hamster?
You know?
You don't listen.
Like, he doesn't always listen.
‐ No, I‐‐it's not‐‐it's‐‐
he got, like, mauled
and chomped, and, like,
bitten and eaten alive
and stuff.
‐ Oh!
‐ Let's, uh‐‐
let's do something fun
to get your mind off Daddy.
We can take a ride
into the moonlight
and play some jams.
‐ Okay, sure.
‐ Sweet.
‐ Um, do you have
your driver's license?
‐ I've got
my brother's learner's permit.
We look the same.
‐ Yeah.
‐ And plus, we're not gonna
get pulled over.
- That's stupid.
- No.
First we gotta pick
a mix, though.
You ever heard of this?
"My Favorite Tunes,
Love Dad."
‐ I love you.
‐ Dee, dee, dee.
Um, love your car.
‐ Mayor...Maya.
Let's all chill.
‐ Okay.
California baby
Caught my eye
Lying on the beach
While I surfed by
Then when we met
I'll never forget
You were so tan
And me in my van
California baby
By my side
Don't you cry
I'll be right beside you
Do or die