‐ huh! ‐ Anna, stop!
I'm not scared.
‐ hey, guys. ‐ hey.
‐ hey, there.
Hey, what's the rush, slick?
Betty Ann's up tonight!
You're not gonna
characterize me that way.
It's not gonna happen. I told him Betty
Ann does really weird stories...
And he's been looking
forward to it ever since.
Ooh, pressure's on.
This better be good.
I'll see what I can do.
‐ they, like, do this
sometimes, it's like...
‐ oh, my god, no, I'm‐‐ love this show.
I'm watching it.
[Show continues in
background[ It's so good.
- ‐ okay.
- Siesta time, man.
- Ahh...
- So scary.
Most people think
dolls are just toys,
but they're really like
perfect little people.
And it's almost as if the
dollmaker took a person
and shank him down to doll size.
But that's not how
dolls are really made.
‐ Anna, should I come? No.
It's okay, you can stay.
‐ no, do you want me‐‐
submitted for the approval
of the midnight society...
Talk to me like you
aren't some jealous dick.
The point I was trying to make is
you don't bring in a paycheck
by doing "riee‐kay," okay?
It's reiki, asshole!
There you go! You know,
you're an asshole.
I married‐‐ we both know that
people are getting laid off
at my job, and you said you wanted
to help... You make me so mad!
And you're not helping! You're
the one that wanted a divorce.
- No!
- Yes!
We agreed that we didn't
want to be together.
‐ no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We said it was a separation. We said it
was a separation! You're not going to
put this on me! And you're
making it impossible for me
to live with you! No, you
don't get to do that!
I'm talking!
You broke my dead mother's teacup!
What is wrong with you?
Shut up! Shut up!
‐ oh! Are you okay?
‐ yeah, yeah. ‐ are you okay?
- ‐ oh, yeah, are you okay?
- ‐ I'm okay.
Ha... Ha... Ahh...
‐
‐ oh, my god, Anna.
Wait. ‐ what?
‐ there were five leaves
here a second ago.
Now there's only three.
‐ Maya, stop.
You did that.
‐ no, I didn't do that.
Literally, a leprechaun came in here‐‐
I'm not even kidding you‐‐
and took two leaves away.
‐ Maya, stop! ‐ Anna!
Swear on my life I'm
not doing anything.
Have we never talked about
the little green man
that lives in the forest?
Swear! Look...
Five twigs‐‐ one, two,
three, four, five.
He's gonna come by and take it.
‐ where is he? ‐ you
have to close your eyes.
You have to close your eyes.
‐ don't touch it. ‐ I'm‐‐
hands are behind my back.
Hands are behind my back.
My eyes are closed.
Oh...
My god!
Anna! ‐ Maya...
‐ I did not do anything!
‐ I heard you... Move... Them.
‐ the little pitter‐patters?
That was his feet. That
was the green man's feet.
Swear on my life he lives here.
I'm not even kidding.
Is this magic? Like are we
freaking in magic right now?
‐ stop! ‐ did you not see the smoke
that came out of my mouth?
I'm a freakin' dragon!
‐ go again.
Maya, stop! ‐ get away from it.
‐ it almost caught me.
‐ it won't touch you.
I have a magic shield
covering your face.
‐ and when I do it, it
doesn't work‐‐look.
‐ I'm sorry, I have that pow‐‐ ‐ so your‐‐your
powers are stronger than mine right now.
‐ it's a natural skill.
‐ bring me to it.
Bring me to it!
Haa‐aa‐aa‐aa‐aah!
Haa‐aaa‐aaaa‐aaaa‐‐
- Maya.
- What?
‐ I'm stuck.
‐ hold on. ‐ I'm stuck.
‐ I'm gonna send you powers so the
jeans that trap your ass fly off!
‐ oh, my god, Maya! ‐ stop!
‐ Maya, Maya, Maya. ‐ stop, Anna, Anna.
‐ don't do that without telling me.
‐ I sent too many powers to your ass.
‐ yeah, but you have
to tell me next time.
‐ I know, I didn't want to surge
too much power in your ass.
‐ I could get killed by this tree.
‐
‐ seriously... Seriously. ‐ no, I know.
‐ I know it's crazy and
new, but I'm dead serious.
I know!
You think your parents
are gonna keep splitting
the house in half?
‐ um...
Maybe. Probably.
We're, like, still a family, so...
Aah! ‐ aah! Stop it!
Jk, jk. ‐ no‐‐anna, no.
‐ ‐ Anna, no, no.
‐ oh, my god!
‐ no, stop it, Anna! ‐ I
was joking, but look!
‐ stop it! ‐ this is in the tree.
- Stop!
- Oh, my god!
- Don't let it get away.
- Get it seriously.
‐ okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Stop, stop, stop! ‐ what? Stop?
‐ why is there fricking
paper in the tree?
‐ paper comes from trees, you nut.
‐ or, what if it's...
‐ what?
What if it's‐‐ ‐ yeah.
What if it's‐‐ ‐ it's
Wendy Rochelle vicanny.
Wiccany.
Knock, knock, anybody home?
‐ what? ‐ it's mother witch.
It's mother witch. ‐
no, I know, but Anna,
that's a v, not a w.
‐ Maya, are you out‐‐ ‐ that's a‐‐
‐ are you serious? ‐ yeah!
‐ come on!
In Germany, they pronounce vs as ws.
Viccany is an alias for wiccany.
She has to just have that...
‐ oh, my god! ‐ to protect
herself with signs and codes.
‐ and‐‐and things like this... ‐ yes.
‐ like vs... ‐ and she
left this for us to know
that this is all real,
and this is a sign.
‐ oh, my god.
‐ hi.
‐ Hi, mother witch.
‐ with her power and her guidance,
we can ask for all the shite
we want in the world.
Anything we want!
Aah!
‐ oh, my god! ‐ Anna, anna‐‐
‐ did you do that? ‐ stop‐‐I
swear I didn't do that!
I didn't do that. Did you do that?
‐ no.
‐ Anna, you did that! ‐ I didn't‐‐oh,
my god. It's mother witch.
She did that. ‐ Anna, stop, stop, stop.
‐ oh, Maya, Maya, Maya. ‐ so that means
she's here and she wants us to do this.
‐ and she wants us to get
anything that we want.
- ‐ whatever we want.
- Oh, my god.
- ‐ oh, my god, stop!
‐ oh, my god‐‐okay. ‐
‐ what do we wish...
For?
What do we wish for? Rah, rah, rah.
What do we wish for?
- Rah, rah, ree.
- Go Maya.
‐ go, go, Anna, go! ‐ go, Maya.
‐ I wish for blonde hair! ‐ go, Maya.
‐ I wish for more money!
‐ I wish for my dad to be home!
‐ I wish I wasn't a problem!
‐ I wish for a bigger
house and no body hair!
‐ only one at a time. I
wish for white jeans.
And that the closet never
happened with Brandt.
‐ you just said one at a time.
For our omikochan to smell better!
‐ I wish I had my period.
‐ I wish for a group of
friends that love us!
‐ I wish for peace everywhere!
‐ wah, wah, wah, wah‐‐ yuki:
Maya.
‐ mom. ‐ hmm?
‐ if you were in Sophie's choice
and you had to pick one of us to die,
who would you pick, me or shuji?
You have to pick.
‐ I'll pick myself.
‐ no, that's not the point.
You have to pick a kid. That's like...
What it is.
‐ well, she'd obviously
pick you to die,
'cause she loves me more.
She's loved me a year longer
because I'm a year older.
Dill hole.
‐ "dill hole"?
Mom, is that true?
‐ shuji...
‐ okay, I knew it. So you
do love shuji more than me.
You'd pick me to die.
Is that what you'd do?
You'd pick your only daughter to die?
Guys.
It's okay. I don't really care,
'cause I have powers now, so...
I can reverse that easily.
Mom, look at me!
You clearly love shuji more
if you're not gonna even
look at your own daughter in the face.
‐
‐ mommy!
Stop! You guys, stop ignoring me.
- ‐ hello?
- Hello!
‐ daddy! Oh, my god!
Daddy!
‐ ‐ they were ignoring me!
‐ ah, oh, my tour ended early.
You didn't even tell me.
It's noth‐‐ I'll tell ya later.
Are you sure?
‐ oh, yeah, yeah, we're good. I
should leave home more often.
‐ my powers...
I'm a witch.
- Everything okay?
- No, I'm good, I'm good.
Okay.
‐
‐ can I get it?
Hi, you've reached the kones'.
This Anna. Who'd you like
to speak to, please?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, Anna, it's Maya.
Anna, oh, my god, it worked.
My dad is home.
What? ‐ yeah, he just came home.
‐ wait, wait, what?
‐ and my hair is more
blonde on one side.
It's crazy, like... Has anything
you wished for happened?
‐ Oh, my god!
Um.... ‐ think about it, 'na.
This is really serious.
'Na. ‐ um...
‐ swear to god, wish again.
- Wish again.
- ‐ okay.
Oh, my god. ‐ oh, my god.
Hold on.
I wish my parents were back together.
‐ can you pass the salt, please, Kathy?
‐ lt's right next to you.
Anna?
Anna.
‐ sorry, no, I'm here. Um...
It didn't work.
‐ oh, my god, okay, I just did
a spell for you to hear me.
That's freaking crazy. Okay,
on my end, it's working.
You probably just, like, need to
strengthen your powers or whatever,
and then, like, we can
get anything we want.
'Na, we're witches.
‐ okay, last night I made a spell book.
‐ oh, my god. ‐ we can
get anything we want.
‐ okay, okay. So with this book...
‐ yes. ‐ my power...
Who should we cast the spell upon to?
‐ big smelly bush.
‐ okay, weakling.
‐
‐ no! ‐ Anna!
‐ Maya, what are you doing?
You might only have a
limited amount of energy.
You have to choose carefully.
Think about it. ‐ yeah,
but what are you thinking
catching it with your bare hands?
‐ I have a invisible energy
glove that repelled it.
And it can also pull your
farts out of your butt.
‐ Anna, no, I don't
wanna fart in class!
‐ okay, sorry.
‐ okay, let's get serious, though.
‐ okay.
‐ if we have a limited
amount of magic...
‐ right.
‐ what do we want?
Think about it. ‐ oh, my god.
‐ oh, my god, don't look up, though
‐ I really, really, really
wish that I never loved Alex.
‐ really?
‐ we're on and off all the time,
and I‐‐just like my biggest nightmare
is ending up like my parents, so...
‐ yeah.
‐ I'm gonna do "I never
loved him" spell.
‐ okay. ‐ oh, my god!
And then you could also do a "hex
the asshole" spell for Brandt.
‐ oh, 'cause Brandt's
an asshole for me.
Or...
I could do a love spell
for me and Brandt.
Because think about it.
If he was my boyfriend,
then no one would be saying the
stuff they're saying to us.
‐ mmm.
Got it. You're insane.
‐ I'm inthane?
Okay, fine.
I'm doing a love spell for me and b.
‐ okay. You have your
spell, I have mine.
Okay, we'll need lovage,
Rosemary, rose petal,
Violet, and yarrow.
Pluck hairs from your head
and hairs from your lover.
Twist them together.
Melt your ex‐lover's cloth.
A lover's lace tied in a devil's knot.
The fingernails of a weak virgin.
Psst!
Can I clip your nails?
‐ No.
‐ does vendy wiccany say anything
about needing a Brandt doll?
A what‐‐ uh... No.
‐ Yes, of course.
Just a touch.
Brandt, stop!
Stop! Ugh.
We haven't had friends over in a while.
Isn't this nice?
You couldn't help but
come over, could you?
Vichaliani potroachi louder‐o‐‐
mm... I don't know.
Is this crazy?
Probably.
It's not like I've fallen out of love
with you in just a couple of weeks.
We fight, you know?
We're fiery.
‐
Yes.
Yeeeessss!
Maya, the sun is at 176 degrees north.
‐ okay, it's almost high noon. It
won't work if we don't do it now.
‐ yeah, I know what it means.
‐ we gotta go.
‐ I know.
Hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm.
Hmm.
Get ready, she's here. ‐ okay.
She is? ‐ she's here.
Vendy Rochelle wiccany.
- She's here.
- She's here, she's here.
Brethren of all energy,
heaven and hellions, mother witch.
Bring us mortimo in reality
which all of us revel in.
‐ Alex, love‐o, anti.
Bendicular‐ano. Bingo.
Macho nacho wilacho
freakano table‐dora,
bring my love Brandt and his fedora.
Bring my love Brandt and his fedora,
for my lover's soul cloth.
For the lover who betrayed you,
his cloth for the lover
who betrayed you.
His cloth for the lover
who betrayed you,
his cloth for the lover who
betrayed you... Shh... Shh!
His cloth.
Stay out, weaklings.
- Just keep going.
- Stay out!
‐ what are you doing? ‐
you're not allowed in there.
‐ I'm gonna hex you.
‐ tattletale bitch.
‐ like honestly, I
have to if you don't‐‐
we're trying to do a thing!
‐ aah!
‐ gah, shilaylay pumpano! ‐ go
back, be bald, shilaylay pumpano!
Shilaylay pumpano!
Shilaylay pumpano! ‐
ah‐ah‐ah‐ah‐ah‐ah‐ah‐‐
someone's getting the principal.
All of you, leave! ‐ aah! Aah!
Gah‐gah‐gah‐gah‐gah‐gah!
‐ ah‐ah‐ah‐ah‐ah‐ah‐ah‐‐
ohh!
Aah!
Shilaylay pumpano,
shilaylay pumpano, shilaylay pumpano,
shilaylay pumpano‐‐ I can't stop!
I'm gonna die! I'm gonna die!
Shilaylay pumpano!
‐ it's okay.
‐ Girls.
My office.
Anna, you can show Maya the way.
‐ right now, or...
‐ oh, my god, 'na, don't look up.
Look.
Did the anti‐love spell work?
‐ Oh, my god.
It worked a little.
‐ really? ‐ I love him less.
‐ really?
Oh...
‐ it still hurts.
What?
Stop. ‐ Brandt is behind you.
‐ no, he isn't.
No, he isn't. ‐ he is.
I could feel him. ‐ well,
then I have to turn
so he can't see.
It worked. He's following me.
Oh, my god, it worked.
‐ yeah, yeah, yeah.
‐ Okay.
‐ cuckoo, cuckoo!
‐ shalaylay pumpano.
Good‐bye. ‐ I'm gonna go‐‐stop.
‐ oh...
‐ hey, whazzup?
I like your hair.
‐ are you serious?
Look, just get away from me, okay?
I don't like you.
You're ugly.
Stop putting your hair in my locker.
And stop talking to me.
I don't fucking like you.
I know, but it was just pretend.
It's like... It's not a big deal.
‐ your principal said that Maya was
putting her hair in Brandt's locker,
and you knew about it, and that
doesn't sound like pretend to me.
‐ was it doll hair, hmm?
What's goin' on with you?
‐ I really don't think this
sharing of the house is working.
I think it's making it worse.
I mean, I know we're
trying to be a family...
That's not what we're talking about.
No‐‐don't tell me
what we're talking about.
I wanna know what you think.
Tell us what you think.
‐ um, I think that you guys
should just stay married.
See? She's confused.
What we're doing, this whole
thing is just too hard on her.
I told you, one of us should
have moved out. I told you this.
We weren't gonna do that. ‐
but you just slept with him.
‐ excuse me? ‐ Anna.
‐ last night, like didn't you‐‐
I heard you go into her room.
Didn't you not‐‐
I mean, do you just sleep with anybody?
Are you in love with‐‐ are
you in love with my dad?
Are you just a Monica?
‐ a Monica?
‐ Lewinsky.
‐ spying... Is not okay.
Curtis, this is not working.
Someone's moving out.
‐ I'm sorry, mom.
‐ she's right.
It's not working.
‐ dad.
No!
You guys, I'm fine!
I'm sorry, I'm just hormonal!
You guys.
Fine!
No slamming doors in this house!
‐ I'm sorry!
‐ the fuck is your problem?
‐ oh... Nothing, it's just like
everyone's ruining my life right now.
Even Brandt doesn't love me. ‐ I
don't wanna hear about Brandt.
Fucking burning hair?
You're such a brat.
‐ well, it's hard for me too.
‐ shut up. ‐ you don't know.
It's hard for me too!
‐ shut up, you idiot.
You should just go away.
‐
Hello? Maya?
‐ Anna... I think that
everyone hates me right now.
Me too.
That's why I found a
spell to disappear.
Meet me at our spot, kay?
‐ what do you mean, disappear?
Someone's gonna move
out and it's my fault.
We'll do it together.
I'll see you soon. Bye.
‐ Anna?
Anna?
Bye.
‐ sss...
‐ hey, 'na.
‐ hey.
‐ I think someone was following me.
‐ oh, I sent an owl to make
sure that you got here safe.
‐ oh, thanks.
Are you okay?
‐ join me. I'm just in
the middle of spelling.
The knife's right there.
Very slowly. ‐ c‐c‐cut my hand.
Cut a finger or my‐‐ ‐
‐ I cut it.
‐ shh...
Okay, I'm ready.
Are you ready?
- ‐ mm.
- ‐
anaminimatu.
‐ anaminimatu.
‐ presence is too much
for those around...
‐ or those around too much.
‐ surely pretend we are gone...
‐ and never did exist.
Okay. Ha.
What?
‐ oh, my god.
Oh, my god, it's starting to, um...
Oh, my god, it's starting to work.
Oh, my god, I feel it in my arms.
‐ Anna, stop. ‐ it's
happening right now.
‐ stop it, Anna, you're scaring me.
‐ I'm not trying to. ‐ stop!
‐ it's happening. Do
you see my fingers?
They're like leaving me.
But the pain's going
away, too, actually.
‐ no, Anna, stop. Stop it, Anna.
‐ where am I? ‐ Anna,
you're right here.
Look at me, okay? You're
not disappearing.
You're staying here. I love you.
‐ I'm sorry. ‐ no, stop, look at me!
Do you see me? You're
not going anywhere.
Stay! Stop!
Can you stop, please?
'Cause I need you.
I'm your family.
Let's be together forever, please.
You're here.
I love you.
♪ Though I'm far away.
‐ awoooooo!