[BREATHES HEAVILY, DISTORTED]
Stardust,
we need to hide in Windsor Caves
or Claw will kill us.
[SIGHS]
No Puff Paws,
I can't leave without Dingle Pan.
Do you want me to stay with you?
You'll stay with me?
Yeah.
OK. Kiss me.
[KISSING]
[BEATING]
[MYSTICAL TRIBAL MUSIC PLAYS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SIGHS]
[YUKI] Maya Chan,
did you brush your teeth?
Yeah, I'm in bed! I'm asleep now!
[YUKI SIGHS]
[YUKI SPEAKING IN JAPANESE]
[MAYA SPEAKING IN JAPANESE]
[YUKI IN ENGLISH] I love you.
- I love you.
- Let me turn the light off.
No, no, can you leave that on?
OK. All right.
[YUKI AND MAYA SPEAKING IN JAPANESE]
[DOOR CLOSING]
[MYSTICAL TRIBAL MUSIC PLAYS]
[PUNK ROCK MUSIC PLAYS]
[TAP RUNNING]
[SHUJI, DOOR KNOCKING] Hurry up dummy!
- We're gonna be late for school!
- It's my bathroom, too! Shut up!!
[SHUJI] What are you doing in there?
Shaving your back?
You can't just barge in!
I was brushing my teeth!
[YELLING] There is no privacy
in this house!
[ANNA HUMMING]
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Is it just me,
or it's super dry last night?
My nostrils are crusty.
This is too strong, again.
-[CURTIS] It's a light roast.
-[KATHY] Light roasts
are stronger, Curtis.
You know I don't like it strong
and yet you continue to make it strong.
- It's Peruvian.
- Yeah, well, it tastes like shit.
[ANNA] OK, I'm gonna go. Love you. Bye.
- Bye, sweetie.
Just use more cream, like...
- OK, thank you. I-I love you.
- OK, thanks. Love you.
- I got to go.
- Have a good day at school.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[MRS. BELL] Pay attention, people.
We're discussing The Hero's Journey.
- Maya.
- Ah.
Um, what are we gonna do this weekend?
Like I really want it to be fun.
-Yeah. Fun.
-[MUFFLED] Do you wanna go see,
like a movie,
or something. That would be fun.
[MYSTICAL TRIBAL MUSIC PLAYS]
We could tell your mom
that we're gonna go see
Chicken Run and then see
Coyote Ugly instead.
[MUMBLING]
What?
[MYSTICAL TRIBAL MUSIC PLAYS]
- Maya.
- Yeah. What?
- You're not listening, obviously.
- Yes, I am.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGING]
Um, I got to [IN JAPANESE] poo.
OK, let's go.
Or actually,
can... can I go in there alone this time
'cause I kinda want some privacy.
Oh, yeah. You're your own person.
- OK. Thanks.
- You just always
want me to go in there with you.
Yeah, I know,
it's just gonna be like, a nasty one.
So, I don't wanna put you
through that, you know.
It's OK.
I'll just breathe through my mouth.
OK, or can you just, like keep watch
outside, and that, so, no one can come in?
OK.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Hey.
[MYSTICAL MUSIC PLAYS]
Sex.
Sexual.
Vagina. Vagina...
[HEATHER] You, guys, I can't wait!
B♪Witched is like the best band.
- ♪ Gotta let me in ♪
[ALL] ♪ Hey, hey, hey! ♪
[ALL] ♪ Let the fun begin. Hey! ♪
You guys, we have to be good about
calling Q102 tonight from 6 to 7.
Like, we need to win
these backstage passes. We have to.
No one ever calls. It's gonna be so tight.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[MYSTICAL TRIBAL MUSIC PLAYS]
Oh, my God.
Guess who's coming to our town
this weekend. B freaking Witched.
This is so jacked.
You, like, B♪Witched.
- Whoa. Like, uh, I'm the wolf today...
- Yeah.
[ANNA] Hey, hey, hey...
Yeah. So, we need to call
the radio station tonight between 6 to 7
to try to get backstage passes.
And the good thing is that, like no one
ever calls, so, it's gonna be tight.
[MAYA] Oh.
- Are you so going right now?
That was a hard long one, huh?
So weird, it doesn't smell
like poop at all in here.
Your body must be changing or something.
Yeah.
All done.
So, we called 603, 606, we'll skip 605
- 'cause everyone's gonna call at 605.
- Yo, I found the Spice channel.
Yesterday, I mapped it out.
Every 48 seconds
it shows a titty
and it lasts for about a second.
- It's awesome.
- Wow, that's so, like... specific.
Hey, Sam, is it weird
to see your mom on screen?
- Do you stay hard?
- Fuck you. I stay hard 24/7.
Are you guys, like talking about,
like masturbating, or...
Yeah, Maya. Just ignore them.
Like, they're pervs.
It's just porn, dork.
OK, well, do you mind
keeping the sex talk down?
Can you just suck my balls?
- Oh, can I barf all over your fat face?
- Sam!
Hey, I heard Connie M. puts peanut butter
on her crotch and has a dog lick it.
[GABE] Are you serious?
[JAFEER] I'm serious.
- Eww.
What the fuck?
[ANNA] That's nasty.
I could never do that.
So, I'm coming home with you, right?
- To make the calls?
- Yeah, yeah.
'Cause I just... I just don't want
to do it in my house, so...
[MAYA] Yeah.
Yeah. Oh...
- Dammit!
- What?
No, I forgot, I forgot. I have to, um...
go to Sam's house to do a math project.
- Tonight?
- Yeah.
- Do plans mean like zilch to you?
- No, I made a plan with Sam first,
so, obviously I'm keeping that.
Means a lot to me.
- Just remember to call Q102...
[MAYA] Yeah.
- At 6:00 p.m.
- 6:00 p. m. I know.
- I'm not stupid. Don't worry, we'll win.
- I refuse to be home this weekend.
I'll call at 6:00.
♪ I really wanna win for the weekend ♪
♪ I really wanna win
For the weekend, weekend ♪
♪ I really wanna win for the weekend ♪
No one come in for an hour,
I'm taking a nap!
[KATHY] You think since you have a job...
[CURTIS] You got a great kid.
[KATHY] ...and make money,
that makes you better than me. I know.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
[CURTIS] Just get a job, OK?
Just get a job.
[KATHY] OK, then
who's gonna drive Anna to school?
[CURTIS] I'm not gonna talk to you
like that, OK?
Like this. All I do
is trying to take care of...
["THE EARTH, THE AIR, THE FIRE, THE WATER"
BY LIBANA PLAYING]
♪ Ae, ae, ae, ae aio, aio,
aio, aio ae, ae, ae, ae ♪
♪ The earth, the air, the fire, the water
Return, return, return, return ♪
♪ Ae, ae, ae, ae aio, aio,
aio, aio ae, ae, ae, ae ♪
♪ The earth, the air, the fire, the water
Return, return, return, return ♪
♪ Ae, ae, ae, ae aio, aio,
aio, aio ae, ae, ae, ae ♪
♪ The earth, the air, the fire, the water
Return, return, return, return ♪
♪ Ae, ae, ae, ae aio, aio,
aio, aio ae, ae, ae, ae ♪
[SIGHS]
[KATHY] I just hate you!
- I can't do this one more minute!
[CURTIS] OK, OK.
[KATHY] Move away!
[CURTIS, GRUNTS]
[KATHY] No, shut up! No!
[CURTIS] Come on.
- Hey, grow up! Grow up!
[KATHY] Don't tell me to grow up!
- Fuck you!
[DOOR KNOCKING]
Mrs. Zablowski? It's Anna Konkle.
Sam?
Maya?
Mrs. Zablowski, I'm so sorry
to come unannounced.
Hope I'm not interrupting.
Um, I just wanted to stop by while May
and Sam did their project,
I promise I won't distract them.
Thank you.
Oh, uh, Maya's not here,
but Gabe and Jafeer are.
Oh, did she just leave?
Um, I haven't seen Maya.
Oh.
That's weird.
- 'Cause she said that she was here, so...
[SUZE] Oh.
I bet Sam would love to see you.
And I'll make Bagel Bites.
I love Bagel Bites.
♪ Pizza in the morning, pizza
In the evening, pizza at supper time ♪
♪ But pizza on a bagel,
You can eat pizza anytime ♪
[YUKI] Maya, dinner's ready!
Maya!
[DOOR OPENING]
- I told you dinner is ready.
- I know. I'm coming down.
What's that smell?
[IN ENGLISH] Let's go down. Let's eat.
[MAYA] OK.
[DOOR CLOSING]
Why do you think she would lie?
I'm not sure.
She might be going through something
that has nothing to do with you.
It's all about boundaries.
I pretty much know
everything about her, though.
I don't know what she could possibly
be going through that I wouldn't know.
[MYSTICAL TRIBAL MUSIC PLAYS]
- Mama.
- Mm-hmm.
[SPEAKING JAPANESE]
[IN ENGLISH] Why are you talking
like that?
I'm not talking like anything.
[SCOFFS]
- Tonight we pay respect to Ojichan.
- Why?
It's his birthday, moron.
What, did you forget?
No.
OK, mama.
Can I help you clean up it all?
[ALBERT] Oh.
[SUZE] Oh. You know what?
Why don't you go up
and say hi to the boys.
- Yeah.
- I think they're watching
- a movie or something.
- Armageddon.
[LAUGHING]
Um, I just want you guys to know, like...
- I really love talking to you.
- Yeah, we don't wanna keep boring you.
No, no.
I could talk to you guys for hours.
I could even sleep here. Just kidding.
I'll go check on those rascals.
- Thank you.
Happy birthday, Ojichan.
[YUKI] Thank you
for always watching over us.
Mama.
What do you mean,
"he's always watching over us"?
He protects us
and watches over us all the time.
Uh, when you're walking the street,
or when you're brushing your teeth.
All the time.
- Even when I'm in bed asleep?
- Yes.
[MAYA] Hmm.
Like, even when I'm...
I don't know, like napping?
Yes.
[JAFFER] Dude, was that boob?
[SAM] That was her foot, idiot.
- You promised her boob.
- It's coming.
[JAFEER] I don't see anything.
I don't see...
- Oh, ho ho, yeah.
- There it is. Oh, my God!
- That is nice.
- Hey, guys...
- you mind if I join in on the movie?
- Anna, get out!
- What?
[ALL] Get out! Go!
- Is this...
- Get out, Anna!
- You're pervs.
- Hi, Anna.
[PHONE RINGING]
[YUKI] Hello.
- Hi, Yuki.
[YUKI] Oh, Anna, hi.
- Um...
Sorry to call so late.
[YUKI] Mm-hmm.
- It's just kind of an emergency.
- Um, is Maya there, please.
[YUKI] What happened?
Is everything OK?
Um...
It's not really an emergency.
[YUKI] Oh...
- So, don't... don't worry about it.
[YUKI] OK.
- I... I just really need to talk to Maya.
- Is she there?
[YUKI] Bed time.
Don't call so late.
- Talk tomorrow. Bye, Anna.
- OK, but can you just tell me...
Hello?
[MUSIC PLAYING ON THE RADIO]
Just hung up on... are you kidding...
And lied to, and...
stupid pervert boys.
[ANNOUNCER] Hello. What's your name?
- Diana.
[ANNOUNCER] Diana, you are caller 20.
- The winner...
[DIANA] Oh, my God! Thank you so much!
[ANNOUNCER] You just won
two backstage passes
to see B♪Witched at
the Eastlake Amphitheater this Saturday.
[DIANA] Oh, my God! Yes! This
is the happiest day of my entire life!
[ANNOUNCER]
What's your favorite radio station?
[DIANA] Overhead, Q102! [SHOUTING]
Mommy!
[YUKI] What's wrong?
- It's Ojichan! I see Ojichan!
[YUKI] That's nice. Say hello.
Sorry.
I didn't mean to do that. I wasn't doing
what you think I was doing.
I was just scratching.
Go away, please! Go away!
The Gobi desert is amongst
the driest places in the world.
[MAYA] Na?
Na?
Are you mad at me?
Why weren't you in carpool this morning?
'Cause I, like slept in.
- Oh, really? Oh.
[MAYA] Yeah.
[ANNA] Guess what?
- What?
I went to Sam's
and you weren't there. You liar.
- Oh, my God.
- Yeah. Busted buddy.
[MAYA] Na.
- Na, listen. OK.
- I'm trying to watch the video.
[MYSTICAL TRIBAL MUSIC PLAYS]
[MAYA] Go away. Go away.
Na.
- Na. Listen.
- I already told you, I'm trying to...
I'm sorry, I lied, OK?
That was really messed up.
But I'm doing it because I am hiding
something about me
that has nothing to do with you.
I swear on my life.
Will you listen?
What?
I see dead people.
Oh. I, like, see ghosts all the time.
- For real?
[ANNA] Yeah.
Who do you see?
I see my Ojichan.
What is an Ojichan?
- It's my grandpa. Yeah.
- Oh.
And it's like really freaky.
I'm not kidding.
I have an idea.
[ANNA AND MAYA]
Spirit, show yourself.
Spirit, reveal.
Spirit, show yourself,
so, Maya knows you're real.
[ANNA SIGHS] I think he's here.
Oh, my God.
I don't know I could be wrong,
I just feel it.
- OK, so, put your hands on it.
[MAYA] OK.
Ojichan...
are you here?
- Don't move it. OK, I'm not.
- I'm not.
[ANNA] Ojichan...
are you here?
- Oh, my God. Are you moving it? God!
- I'm not moving it. Are you moving it?
[MAYA SHIVERING] OK, that's crazy!
- I don't want to do this.
- It's OK. Put your hands back.
I'm with you.
Put your hands on it.
Ojichan...
why are you here?
[ANNA HEAVILY BREATHING] Oh, my God!
[MAYA] Oh, my God.
[BOTH] C...
L...
I...
T...
[ANNA] T, C-L-I-T, clit.
Clit.
- Clit.
- I don't know what clit.
- I don't know clit.
- Eww.
- Clit!
- Maya!
- Anna!
- You're doing that.
- I'm not.
I was not touching.
I swear on my life, I'm not moving it.
- You're moving it.
- My fingers are barely touching it.
OK, well, same.
Why is your grandpa saying "clit"?
I don't know. Maybe it's not him.
- It's him for sure.
- It is.
- I can feel him.
- I don't know, now, I feel like...
- this is crazy...
- Maya, let's just try one more time.
- OK, OK.
- OK. OK.
Ojichan, why are you haunting Maya?
[MAYA] Oh, my God. M...
[ANNA] A...
- It's moving fast!
[MAYA] No. S-T...
[ANNA] S-T...
[BOTH] U...
R-B...
Whoa!
That is crazy, Ojichan.
Why did you just flick it?
- I did not flick it.
- What the hell?
That was not me. That was literally him.
We're in the middle of contacting him.
- I didn't flick it. I didn't.
- What the hell?
You guys are playing Ouija?
We're not playing, it's serious, so...
That shit's so stupid.
[ANNA SIGHS]
- You realize
one of you is just moving it
and it's just your subconscious, right?
[MAYA SOBBING]
Are you OK?
Yeah.
I need to tell you my subconscious.
OK.
I'm like Sam...
only I'm grosser, 'cause I'm a girl,
and I'm a pervert.
And I really shouldn't be doing
what I'm doing.
I've been putting my hands
down my pants, um...
my area...
down there to feel good.
Um, when I'm in bed...
sometimes I put my hands
between my legs to feel good.
Really?
Yeah.
Hey, you mean like this?
Not exactly, um, sort of.
You don't feel gross?
How gross can I feel if you do it, too?
Promise I'm not a pervert.
[WHISPERING] I promise.
And swear you won't tell anyone.
- Oh, my God. I swear. You swear, too?
- I swear. Yeah.
- Pinky swear.
[ANNA] Pinky swear.
[KATHY] Oh, is this about me drinking...
[KATHY AND CURTIS FIGHTING]
[RELAXING MUSIC PLAYS]
[OWL HOOTING]
Sweet! Sweet, I see.
[MYSTICAL TRIBAL MUSIC PLAYS]
[DRUMS PLAYING RAPIDLY]