Maya, Shuji, fax...
OK.
Dear family...
arrived in Cleveland today.
The weather is cold,
but my drumsticks are on fire!
How are you all?
Miss you very much. Love, Dad.
Dear Dad, I miss you so much.
Yesterday I scored a goal at soccer.
I wasn't ready.
I was right there with you.
Get it, Alice.
Dear Maya. I wish
I could've been there to see your goal.
I'm not surprised though,
I was quite the athlete myself.
Must be in the genes! How's Anna?
Are you making any new friends?
Dear Dad,
Anna's still my best friend,
but my impression of Jim Carey
is getting really good
and there are at least four popular kids
that want to be our bf's,
"Best friends" now.
I'm also starting to sleep
in my own bed more. Ask Mom.
Actually don't.
Dear Maya. That sounds nice.
I miss sleeping in the bed with your mom.
It's lonely out on the road sometimes.
We've all got our ways of dealing with it.
For me, it's reading your letters.
So, please keep sending!
Love, Dad.
♪ High ♪
♪ I am high ♪
♪ That view I showed to you ♪
♪ Is just a lie ♪
♪ You take what you want
You get what you take ♪
♪ High, high, high ♪
What?
Alex broke up with Heather.
Hmm-hmm. Hmm-hmm.
Are you losing your mind?
- It's all happening.
This is the moment. Oh, my God.
All right, everybody,
take your seats, please.
- I have some very exciting news.
- Alex Nolan is single.
I mean, like, if you're a girl
that's more exciting
maybe.
Just like, you know
the whole school's been talking about it.
I'm not weird, you guys are weird.
OK.
This Friday is Trailview Middle's
"Night of Amazing Music"
which means the band and the chorus
will be performing for the whole school.
And what's more,
you all will be performing
an original piece of music,
written by yours truly.
You'll find the music on your stands.
Na, I only have three notes solo.
How many do you have?
I have, like a five-measure solo.
All right,
let's try the piece. Shall we?
One, two, three...
All right, hol...
Just hold it.
Hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it.
Timpani. I... I don't know
what that is you're playing
but you should be playing
a straight 4/4 count in time.
Yeah, sorry.
Do you mean the snare 'cause I feel like
- Timpani was doing four, four.
- No, Timpani... No, the snare is fine...
Try to stay within the four, four times.
You want me to do it differently?
- 'Cause I was doing a four, four.
- So... No, right. Somewhere in there.
I'll tell you what. Play it like your dad.
Why don't we try it
from the top again.
Do you wanna watch me practice
for my chorus solo audition later?
I mean, I would,
but I have enough on my plate
with that three notes solo,
you know what I mean?
- But you're the best singer I know, so...
- Yeah.
Do you think Alex is gonna come
to the show later?
- Yeah, it's kind of... Oh, my God.
- Hey.
- I'm, uh, I'm Brendan.
- I'm Anna.
- I know who you are.
We're in band together.
I mean, anyone who does music
at Trailview knows you.
Really?
Are you excited
for the "Night of Amazing Music"?
Sure. I am, yeah.
- What... Are you Maya?
- Yeah.
I'm gonna get a new hat
after school for it.
- Are you allowed to do that?
- I'll do what I want.
OK.
Good.
Oh, my God!
- Where?
- Um...
After you've build the deck.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Why not?
- I don't know.
- What's the question?
- The question is...
- I forgot the question.
When you've build the deck.
- Question and the answer is...
- Pretty anemones.
♪ Loving you ♪
♪ Makes me feel free ♪
♪ 'Cause at the end of the day ♪
♪ You're my Mister May ♪
♪ You're my Mister June, July and August ♪
♪ August, Baby
Every month you are to me ♪
♪ And we have a family ♪
Oh, my God! Fax is coming in.
It's to me.
Dear Maya...
Dear Dad,
guess what?! We have our
first big band concert Friday night.
The whole school's gonna be there.
Wish you were coming.
I got a huge solo.
Like daughter like father! Meow, Maya.
Mom, help me with the fax.
Mom!
Ah.
- Oh my God, Dad!
- What?
What?
I have one good eye left, OK?
I'll protect you from this one.
I don't think it's funny.
Look, mom, I am dad
and I'm 12 feet away from the flame.
That's not what I did.
- That is what you did. You're like...
- That's not what I did.
It's so far away.
- OK.
- That's immature.
Oh, you think so? Don't you dare.
How was school today, sweetheart?
Um, it was good,
like I have a music concert on Friday.
And I have a solo in band
and I also have a chorus solo hopefully,
if it goes well...
Oh, that's great, no?
- That's amazing.
- I'm so proud. Yeah.
- Congratulations.
- I'm in. I'm totally in. You in, Kathy.
- Of course I'm in.
- Yeah. Good.
Afterwards we'll go for ice-cream
and we'll have an ice-cream cake.
Yeah.
Dear Maya.
I'm coming home early from the tour,
so, I can see my little girl's show.
I am so proud.
See you soon! Love, Dad.
Very good.
Excellent.
All right, hold it.
Hold it, hold it.
What was that?
You're late.
- Let me see if we can work on this.
- OK.
I just wanna... I know...
I know you can get it.
- Yeah.
- All right. Yeah, but just from the top...
- Hmm-hmm.
- And that's the first two beats, OK?
- All right. OK.
- So count it out. One, two, three, four...
One, two, three...
One, two, three, four...
Here, here.
Am I early or late?
Early.
No.
Late.
No! Try it again. From the top, please.
- One... One, two, three, four...
- three, four...
No! Again! One, two, three, four...
One, two, three, four...
One, two, three...
No, it's late, it's late, it's late.
Again, again, again!
Saved by the bell.
Miss Ishii-Peters.
You need to practice this
before tomorrow, please.
All right, everybody, let's pack it up.
You'll get it.
Can you help me after school?
I have chorus practice. I would, but...
- Or maybe Sam can help. Sam?
- No, don't ask him. Stop...
- Sorry, he's already here.
- Fuck you, Anna.
Can you help Maya?
Sure. I am the best drummer in the bands.
He kind of is, so...
OK, fine, can you just, like, help me
after 3:00, I don't really care.
- Yeah, I don't... I don't care either.
- I don't care either.
Let's just not care and just
don't be late, but, like, whatever.
- See you at 3:00.
- I'll see you at 3:00. Don't be late.
Wait, is that for me?
Hector.
Oh, my God!
It says Anna.
- Really small. Yeah.
- What?
Oh, my God.
- Amazing!
- What does it say?
I don't know. Doi!
- I haven't read it yet. Doi.
- Uh! Doi.
We are going to look
at the microscope today.
We're gonna be very delicate.
Time to pair up.
Jared, you go with Connie.
Alex, go with Anna.
♪ Waiting for the Sun
So I can see your face again ♪
♪ I miss you, oh, so much
Can't take another now ♪
What you're gonna do?
- What's up?
- Oh, what's up?
You smell nice.
Um, can you, like read that? Or...
I can't quite... I don't know
how to use a microscope, so...
It says, "I like playing
with you, Anna. Let's hang out sometime."
Oh, my God!
- Whoa!
- Who's Anna?
It's just me. Stupid.
- He... he likes you.
- Who?
You? What?
Who's... who's that?
Oh, him. I don't know. Who cares.
- Yeah.
- So, what's up with your,
um, your G.F. or whatever?
I broke up with her.
I don't have one anymore.
Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
It's chill.
What did you hate about her?
She was just, like, always there.
If I was your boyfriend,
I mean, girlfriend
I would not be anywhere,
unless you wanted me to be somewhere.
And then I'd be there on time.
Cool.
It's crazy there's this, um...
like, kind of music concert thingy
tomorrow night...
- so...
- Cool.
- And I'm in, like the band and chorus.
- Nice.
I barely have time for a boyfriend,
but I do have a little.
Are you gonna go, or...
Well, I... I think we have to go.
Like, hate that thing.
Let's focus on the basics, all right?
Let's start with your breath.
All right?
- Yeah.
- OK.
OK. So, close your eyes.
And breathe.
Sound forward.
We do one more.
And who'll be auditioning
for a solo, raise of hands.
Girls, fantastic.
Heather, come on up.
You're gonna go first.
An audition etiquette,
everyone, no laughs, no sounds.
Right here.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
I can feel your breath,
it's kind of distracting me.
Sorry.
Here.
Put these on.
Listen to this.
♪ ...I don't know yet
Tell it to your friends ♪
♪ Leave your troubles so far out
That they'll forget to come ♪
♪ In the blink of an eye ♪
♪ Oh! Let's say
It's the time of our lives ♪
♪ Let's say it's the time of our lives ♪
- You OK?
- Ow.
That was fantastic, Heather.
- Thank you so much. Very brave.
- So good.
- She's really good. She's really good.
- Really good.
That was fantastic, Heather. Anna?
Come on up.
Everyone applaud for Anna as well.
OK. And good luck.
You're gonna be great, honey.
Fantastic. Go for it.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Let's say it's the time of our lives ♪
That... that was really good.
That was really good.
Thanks.
Round of applause again.
You guys have made my decision tough.
Anna, you will be singing the two-bar solo
and, Heather, you will doing
the sign language solo
that accompanies it.
And actually I know one.
Thank you.
- And then Commonwealth of Nations.
- Hmm-hmm.
But then I wonder if, like the...
Daddy!
Oh! Sweetheart! Oh!
- It's so good to see you. Oh!
- Hi, Daddy.
- Hey, Shuj.
- OK, Dad. Look at my new dance.
Welcome home.
- Dad, look.
- That's great.
Gigs went really, really great.
Oh, man!
So good to see you guys!
- Are you ready for the big day?
- Yeah.
- Yeah? Timpani.
- Yeah. I know.
- You need some help rehearsing?
- I'm killing it.
- You are? I would love to see that.
- Yeah.
Can I see that?
- Can I help you? I kill that.
- No, Dad, I'm like...
I kill on Timpani.
After dinner.
Rehearsal, like do it
the solo in front of you?
Yeah.
OK. Hamper sounds good.
- Dad. Stop!
- OK.
So, start playing.
- OK, just don't say it like that.
- I... I didn't say it like anything.
Yes, you did.
Can you just shut up for a second,
'cause I was about to play
and you are messing me up.
Maya, just...
- Come on, calm down.
- I am calm, Dad.
I'm just trying to play for you,
so, can you, like, stop.
Don't look at me like that.
It's gonna mess me up.
Look away.
Don't look at the drum,
literally look at that wall over there,
and listen.
Dad! OK.
All right, all right,
I... I got to stop you.
- Oh, my God!
- You are holding the mallets wrong.
- You know, let me show you.
- Dad, this is why
- I didn't want to do this with you.
- If you can't play for me
- how you're gonna play for everyone else.
- I don't know
because not everyone's in, like,
a professional Steely Dan Cover Band, Dad!
And they never will be
if they don't know how to practice!
Oh, no!
Now, I'm gonna suck
tomorrow night 'cause of you.
Oh, fine. It's all because of me.
- Get out!
- Fine. I... I looked at your wrong.
Yeah, you did.
You know, Anna goes first today.
Hi, Ma. I got you some ginger ale
to settle your tum.
What are you doing?
You shouldn't look at the crowd.
It's just gonna make you more nervous.
You're right.
Anna, your parents are here.
- Together?
- Yeah.
Oh, my God.
That is so embarrassing.
Alex. Six o'clock.
Oh, no, I don't know
what o'clock is. He's right there.
Oh, where?
- He has a rose.
- Oh, my God!
- He came.
- I'm getting nervous actually.
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to Trailview Middle School's
performing art showcase.
La musique!
Oh, shit!
Unfreeze.
Oh, no, don't do this. Fuck!
Quickly. Maya, quickly.
Sam, can you take my solo
'cause my hands are claws.
- Just remember what I said.
- What... what did you say?
What did you say?
Hey, Anna, your song was awesome.
- Oh, really?
- You really act it out.
Thanks.
Ladies and gentlemen,
you're in for a special treat
this evening.
The band has been
hard at work on an original song
composed by me.
Just breathe.
One. two...
Go.
Great job.
- Don't read it now.
- What?
Hey, honey.
Hey, Dad.
You were great.
- Oh, thanks.
- Really great.
- It was fine. No.
- So proud. Yeah.
- Thanks.
- Your Mom had to leave early.
Yeah, I know. I saw.
But I don't care. Is she OK?
Yeah, she's fine. You know her.
She was in, uh, a mood.
Yeah.
Dang it.
I forgot to buy you flowers.
- Dad, stop, it's fine.
- I mean, look at that nice young man.
He's got flowers.
♪ Waiting for the sun
So I can see your face again ♪
♪ I miss you, oh, so much
Can't take another now ♪
♪ Without you in my arms... ♪
You know what?
Here. Five, six, seven... Seven...
Seven dollars. There.
- Dad, it's fine.
- OK, OK.
Um, you're gonna ruin my shirt, Sweety.
- OK. You know what?
- OK.
You were great.
Maya?
Can I... can I come back?
How are you? You OK?
Did you like my solo?
Did I like it? I... I will never forget it.
- So, it wasn't amazing?
- It was.
I... I don't think it fit with the...
with the rest of the show, but...
- Uh...
- Thanks.
It was amazing.
You know I only made up that solo
to impress you, right?
That I was only supposed to play
three notes.
You... you don't have to come up
with some fancy solo to impress me.
In music
every single note is important.
I would be proud of you
with just playing those three notes.
Are we OK?
Yeah.
- Hi. Sorry.
- Hey. Uh...
No, no, it's OK. It's all right.
Um, you know what?
Um, we'll see you outside.
- Yeah, OK, we'll see you outside.
- OK, OK, all right. All right.
So what? Are you like...
Are you gonna make fun of me?
Probably at some point but not tonight.
Where did that come from?
I don't know, like...
You really like The Exorcist.
- Hi. Hey.
- Hey.
- How was I?
- Oh, my God. That was crazy.
- Oh, did you find Alex?
- Hmm-hmm.
- And?
- Can't really talk about it.
Oh!
Sometimes love means...
um, ignoring someone for years.
- That's a 100% true.
- Yeah.
Um, can you look at this for me?
What is it?
- Nothing, it's...
- Back off.
He did it a little bigger this time.
I guess he like loves me or whatever.
What are you gonna say?
Which one should I say?
- I have a boyfriend! We do!
- We have a boyfriend!
Dear Maya, it's tough
having to get back on the road
but your performance inspired me.
We've got a pretty big gig in Florida.
Had my own solo
and it brought down the house!
Wish you could've seen me.
Love, Dad.