Welcome!
♪ I... ♪
♪ I am high ♪
♪ The you I show to you is just a lie ♪
♪ You take what you want ♪
♪ You give what you take ♪
♪ The high, high, high ♪
- OK, so screen names...
- OK.
So I have three options here for me...
Stardust4eva, Sclub7...
- which might be taken already...
- Mm-hmm.
And Babyspice666.
Isn't 666 like the Devil's number?
No.
Six is my favorite number
and my lucky number, so...
Oh, my God!
- Good job.
- I got mine.
OK, cool, my turn.
What do you mean?
I just signed on to mine.
You got a screen name. Now it's my turn.
But I haven't added any "Buddies".
You, like, don't need to.
You just have one buddy.
Your boyfriend buddy.
Maya, that's not even funny.
Like, we're barely boyfriend-girlfriend.
Yeah, right.
"Hi, Brendan. It's Anna.
I'm hogging the computer.
I love you."
Who's "hockey00?"
It's Alex.
Stop.
So funny.
My God!
It's messed up.
He probably got knocked off.
- That's shady.
- That happens.
That's not cool.
- OK, let's talk to Sam.
- OK, fine.
What's his screen name?
OK.
It is "LittlemanbigD1814"
"Little man big D?"
Ew!
He's so nasty.
It's funny, though.
Type it in.
Hey, hun. It's Anna.
No, and me. Say, "Me, too."
- Maya.
- Say, "Me" ah... "and Maya."
OK.
OK, he wants to know my screen name.
I want to type.
Don't have one yet. Dash from Maya.
Tell me when you do.
Dash from Sam. TTYL.
Oh, my God. Who's "Dogwigs2332?"
Oh, my God, Brendan's online.
Oh, my God!
- Oh, my God.
- Stop. Should I respond?
Like, what if Alex comes back on,
and I'm distracted.
Yeah, but he's like your boyfriend,
so you have to respond.
Yeah, I know. WUWU?
"WUWU"?
What the fuck is WUWU?
Oh, my God.
He doesn't even know what WUWU means?
I don't know what it means.
What does it mean?
What's up with you.
WUWU.
I can't believe
you don't know what that means.
Smiley face.
OK, it's my turn.
Maya, Brendan just IM'd me.
No, let me set up my screen name.
- Maya, we're talking.
- Give it.
Stop! It's my turn!
Please, don't break my keyboard.
Don't break my keyboard.
Give it to me! Thank you. Finally, like...
I just... OK, let me say good-bye.
OK, say good-bye and then bye-bye forever.
OK, screen name. So I'm gonna be...
Viper911.
- My God! What the eff! It's taken.
- I'm sorry, hun.
- But look, AIM gives other options.
- Oh, yeah.
Let me see.
I'm just gonna do this one.
- The "D" one?
- Yeah.
It's Viper with a "D" 911.
Diaper emergency!
Think about it.
I think it's, like, cool.
Waz up dingleberry?
Oh, my God!
Your screen name what the eff!
Can I just check to see
if Brendan's still online?
Anna, like, you were just talking to him.
You don't even like him that much.
There he is.
What's that thing next to his name?
- It's weird.
- Oh, wait.
He has a quote. It's like...
Wait. That's about you.
What do you mean?
He's, like, obsessed with you.
He wants to hug you.
It's just an away message, Maya.
OK, I wanna see who else is on.
What the eff? Everyone's signing off.
Have you ever been in a chatroom?
OK, what's that one? M4m.
Holy eff. No way, Maya!
- What?
- Local one.
"Hot people of Franklin County."
Wait. Should we go in there?
- Are we allowed?
- We're hot. We're in Franklin.
OK, yeah, I guess they can't see
if we're hot or not, so just... do it.
Do it.
- Oh, my God.
- Uh, like, 16 people.
Oh, my God.
This is so crazy.
Say something.
What do I say?
- You do it.
- No, you do it.
You do it.
OK, fine.
What do I say?
OK. 'Sup hotties?
I'm hot girl.
Maya!
Oh, my God.
Wait. It's, like, going so fast,
you know, it, like, gets lost.
OK, Maya, "PhuckMaStick" just said "asl".
What does "asl" stand for?
Oh, my God. Can he see?
Of course not.
My dad doesn't have a webcam.
- Accept or decline?
- You do it. You do it.
- Cool.
- Accept.
OK.
'Sup, baby.
How hot are you? Show me!
- My God!
- Oh, my God!
- Oh, my God, Maya.
- Oh, my God, 'Na, stop!
- You're freaking me out.
Stop!
Hey, I need to use the phone right now...
so IM time is over.
Got it.
Like, now.
- OK.
Look out.
Good-bye.
Listen, Sam,
it was, like, so messed up.
It was crazy, crazy-crazy.
Wait. You talked to some guy in town?
Well, he can't find you
unless you've told him where you live.
Are you say... We were in a room
for Franklin County for hot people,
like, that's what we were in.
He doesn't know your name.
Does he?
Sam, you're scaring us. Why?
Sam, stop. No.
He just knows our screen names, like...
You're fine, Diper911.
It's just for guys who wanna hook up.
All right. I'm gonna hang up now.
Later, losers.
Bye.
Oh, my God.
Stop. It's my mom. It's my mom.
Jesus!
- Love you.
- Love you, Anna.
Maya.
No. Frickin' like, "Do your homework."
Sponges and sea stars,
like, it's not that hard.
♪ Toc, tic, toc, tic ♪
♪ Toc ♪
- Maya?
- Welcome!
Are you done with your homework?
- You've got mail.
- Yeah. I'm doing it.
Like, I need the computer
for a research project, so...
Research project?
Yeah. It's due tomorrow.
Tomorrow? Well, then hurry up
and finish it.
Duh! It's literally what I'm doing,
so can you leave me alone, please?
OK.
So... I heard something today
while I was, um,
driving Anna and Maya home.
They were whispering, but...
What?
You have a boyfriend.
- What?
- Mom, what, you spying on us?
Who? Someone we know?
Brandon.
Mom, it's Brendan. It's not Brandon.
You're not even a good spy,
and we're just taking it
really, really slow.
We just barely started going out.
Is he a catch?
Because you are catch. Kinda major catch.
Curtis, is this from Wok N' Roll
or Shanghai?
Because Wok N' Roll is the one
that made me sick
after your mole removal.
I thought that was Shanghai, so...
OK, so this is Wok N' Roll.
Seriously I reminded you this morning
before you left.
Now again you made me...
It's Chinese food.
No, it's not Chinese food.
That one place makes me sick,
and the other place doesn't.
I'm calling Anna for homework help.
OK.
- Hello?
- Oh, my God, 'Na!
I'm back
in "Hot people of Franklin County."
Oh, my God, you're back in?
There's like 19 people in here.
What are they saying?
They're saying so many things,
like, "discrete?"
"Purple pussy cat."
- "Looking to play."
- You love playing.
Oh, my God, some random guy
just IM'd me again.
- 'Na...
- Oh, my God, Maya, be careful.
Remember last time.
Flymiamibro22.
- That's a hot screen name.
- Yeah.
OK, I'm clicking on it.
He says, "Hey, hottie. Zup.
What you look like?"
Oh, my God, 'Na, he thinks I'm hot,
and he's saying hi. Help me.
- What do I say back?
- Well, he can't find our age.
Yeah, obviously.
OK, let's just say we're like...
Well, um...
We are both 13, so, like, 13 plus 13,
that's like 26.
I'm just gonna say we're 26.
Say we have blonde hair
and brown eyes,
- like, if we were one person.
- OK. I love that.
Blonde hair. Brown eyes.
Oh, my God, he thinks we're hot.
OK, wait.
He's 30. He's a computer programmer
and a total gym rat.
Oh, my God, he's a freaking gym rat.
That's like...
what is that?
OK. Are you hot?
Um, it's a chatroom
for hot people.
- Remember?
- Shh!
Oh, my God, he says,
"People tell me I'm hot but I am humble.
It's not for me to say."
That means he's hot.
Wait, that's what people say that are hot.
I know.
I'm, like, into this guy.
Oh, Maya, can you hold on?
I just have call waiting.
OK.
Hello?
Hi. Can I please
speak to Anna please?
This is Brendan Tooler speaking.
Hi. It's Anna.
Uh, hi.
What's up? You called...
Yeah, is that cool?
Yeah, I just... I'm talking to
Maya on the other line
so I'm just gonna have to...
um, tell her that I'll call her back,
I guess.
Oh. OK, sure.
OK, hold on.
- Maya?
- What?
Oh, my God, Brendan just called me.
- Wait. Really?
- Like...
- Oh, my God.
- Are you kidding?
Anna, this is like real...
Um, can I call you back
and just talk to him for a minute, like...
No. Go, go, go.
I'm talking to Flymiami.
Well, you're still
chatting with him?
I know it's crazy.
- Progress check in the morning.
- OK.
- OK. Be good over there, bye!
- Bye.
I like nature too.
Sand dunes.
Ha. JK.
Mm.
I shouldn't have said that.
That's like...
♪ Yeah... ♪
♪ I'm the one you need ♪
Flymiamibro?
'Sup?
Yo, girl,
you got an email address?
Yeah, I'll give it to you, hottie.
- That's hot.
- You're hot.
- You're so fricking hot.
- I've never felt this way before.
- Me neither. My heart's gonna burst.
- Bang!
- Am I dead?
- You could take it, bitch.
Because I'm in heaven with you right now.
- Bury me.
- When I think of other girls,
I wanna barf my guts out.
I wanna eat that barf and guts up
like a big, old bowl of lentil soup.
Yum, yum, yum, yum...
Sometimes there's so much beauty
in the world
I feel like I can't take it.
I love you more than I love my own dad.
- Maya-chan!
- Aah!
Why are you still up?
I just finished the research project.
- Go to bed.
- OK.
I think I'm in love.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
- Mai?
- That's a really big word.
- No, I know.
And you just like, barely know him
is the only thing.
No, I know, but, like,
sometimes you can just tell.
- You haven't met him yet?
- It's from the way we're talking.
Wassup, Maya?
Hey.
See. Even Evan's way less hot to me
since I met Flymiamibro.
- That's how you know.
- Oh, my God. Don't look.
Hey, Anna. Hey, Maya.
- Hey, Brendan.
- Hey.
I burned this for you.
'Cause you said you love music.
You don't have to listen to it.
No, I do love music. Thank you.
- Bye.
Oh, my God,
he's, like, in love with you.
- We talked for hours last night.
- Wait. Really?
It's all moving too fast.
No, I think it's moving exactly
the right speed.
I do.
Seventh grade rules.
♪ Good girlfriends ♪
♪ The blonde one ♪
♪ Is making me... ♪
I can't believe he made me a mix CD.
The song sucks.
Play the next one.
Oh, my God, he wants to slow-dance
with you...
Maya, shut up!
♪ Whatever you want ♪
♪ Whatever you need ♪
♪ Is yours girl ♪
♪ But whatever you do ♪
♪ Please don't stop the love ♪
♪ Some say that I'm professional ♪
♪ 'Cause I know how to handle mine ♪
♪ Be still, be cool and wait awhile ♪
♪ And I'll show you
What some say is right ♪
♪ Now don't get the wrong impression ♪
♪ I don't do this all of the time ♪
Anna, does your dad have a digital camera?
♪ All I wanna do... ♪
Mm-hmm.
You think we can take a picture of me
and send it to Flymiamibro.
- No.
- Why?
- I don't think that's a good idea.
- No. Yes, it is.
It's just not something
we should be doing.
It's just like a picture of me
so he can know what I look like.
- No. We are not doing it.
- No... Anna, yes.
Maya, I'm putting my foot down.
Absolutely not.
That's hot.
And make sure you're getting the boob too.
Sure, do.
OK, let me see it.
Let me see.
Oh, My God.
That looks bad. That's blurry.
- You look beautiful.
- Oh, wait, I like that one.
That's good.
Showing a lot. Um...
How about just this one?
That's literally just my hand.
I know but it's beautiful.
OK.
- Oh, my God.
- Stop. I'm gonna send it.
Oh, my God.
Stop it! stop it!
Anna, Anna, stop.
- What if he doesn't think it's pretty?
- I can't believe you just did that.
What if he doesn't think it's pretty?
Oh my God, he already responded.
"So hot."
OK, I'm sorry, we have to meet.
- What?
- Ssh!
I have to meet you...
- Maya, don't send that.
- Stop.
- In person.
- Maya, don't send that.
- No. Don't send that.
- I sent it.
I sent it.
- Maya!
- Stop.
Oh, my God!
Are you like so nervous?
- I mean... a little.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
It's like I know he's the one, you know.
Who are you guys talking about?
None of your freaking business, Jafeer.
Yeah, it's none of your freaking business.
If you really want to know...
I've met someone.
Or I'm about to meet him after school.
Wait, you haven't met him in person yet?
- That's shady.
- Oh, no, we've talked on AIM like a lot.
He's probably some wart-y old dude,
who has a beer belly
or suit socks and lives with his mother.
Or he's a computer genius
with a tight bod, Jafeer.
- Like you wouldn't even...
- Can we just change the conversation?
- What?
- Start a new one.
We weren't even talking to you.
It's just kinda lame.
- OK, well...
- OK, well, stop... like, don't listen.
- Anyway, Mai?
- What?
I'm like, so excited for you, honestly.
- I really, really am.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I just wanna ask one quick question.
- OK, what?
Are you sure that you want to meet him,
because what if he's pissed
that you're a kid.
I don't think that's a possibility,
like, I don't.
- OK.
- I'm not gonna stand him up.
I couldn't do that to him...
- Right. OK.
- You know. Yeah.
- I just feel like we need back up.
- Yeah.
- Like someone that can protect us.
We should ask Brendan.
'Sup, B?
Spencer.
You're OK, Maya? Can I get you some water?
I'm good.
I'm good. Don't leave.
What if he gets mad when he sees me
that I don't look like what I said I look?
Maya, you're fine.
You're fine as hell. You're finer
than you even described.
Yeah.
And maybe he doesn't look like
how he described himself.
I mean, he could really be
anybody in here.
Yeah.
♪ Love ♪
♪ Mm-hmm ♪
♪ Love is strange ♪
♪ Yay-yay ♪
♪ Lot of people ♪
♪ Mm-hmm ♪
♪ Take it for a game ♪
♪ Many people ♪
♪ Mm-hmm ♪
♪ Don't understand ♪
♪ No, no ♪
♪ They think loving ♪
♪ Yay-yay ♪
♪ Is money in the hand ♪
Do you know what's crazy?
I was just thinking that, like,
in three years, we'll be driving...
♪ Sylvia ♪
♪ Yes, Mickey ♪
♪ How do you call your loverboy? ♪
♪ Come here, loverboy ♪
♪ And if he doesn't answer? ♪
♪ Oh, loverboy ♪
♪ And if he still doesn't answer? ♪
Maybe his Ferrari broke down.
- Hmm-mm, maybe, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Yeah, yeah.
I think it's getting dark.
We should just get home soon
before it gets too late.
Do you think he...
Do you think that he came and saw me
and thought I was ugly and left?
Well, if he did that, then he's an idiot.
Yeah, or I'm like an idiot
for thinking he would like me.
- Mai.
- No, no, I'm fine.
Here, go get yourself a Mountain Dew.
Thanks.
Thanks for coming with us.
Sure.
Oh, what are you doing?
I can't... I can't...
What...
They don't have any Mountain Dews left.
Can we go?
Please?
- Mm-hmm.
- Like now?
OK.
That means a lot to me.
Welcome.
You've got mail.
Computer...
Good-bye.