[MISCHIEVOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
[BOY WHISPERING] Pass it to Anna.
[GIRL 1 WHISPERING] Pass it to Anna.
[GIRL 2 WHISPERING] Pass it to Anna.
[GIRL 3 WHISPERING] Anna?
[MAYA] Oh, my God, you always get a note.
[ANNA WHISPERING] Shut up!
[BRENDAN VOICE-OVER] Yo, wassup!
[BRENDAN VOICE-OVER CONTINUES]
Tight. B.
Oh, my God! You have to go.
[MUSIC INSTRUMENTS PLAYING]
That's how it happens, Anna.
Mm. What happens?
Maya.
[MOCKING]
[MR. WYZELL] All right.
Page 1. Section A.
- Whoa. Whoa. Whoa...
[IN SPANISH] ¡Silencio! ¡Silencio!
I'm serious. Stop!
All right. We've got a lot to get to.
Come on.
One. Two.
Can I go to the bathroom?
[MUFFLED LAUGHTER]
I'll hold it.
You know what?
Actually, need to go really bad.
♪ I... ♪
♪ I am high ♪
♪ That view I showed to you ♪
♪ Is just a lie ♪
♪ You take what you want ♪
♪ You give what you take ♪
♪ The high, high, high ♪
Stop, Maya.
We're going. [CHUCKLES]
I don't know yet.
Oh, my God, 'Na,
I feel like everyone's staring...
No, they are not.
They are already hooking up.
That's her friend Maya.
Oh, my God, they're talking about us.
We're on top.
- Shh! He's right there. He's right there.
- No, he's...
[ANNA] He's right there.
Stop. Stop. Stop! Stop!
I'm serious. Please, stop. Please.
Don't look.
[BRENDAN] Hey.
- Oh, hey.
So, are you... are you
coming tomorrow night?
Um, I think so.
What's the movie about?
It's about hairless wild snatch.
Ew!
What?
I actually saw it in the theaters,
and I jizzled all over the place.
Really? Shut up!
So, are you in?
Um, OK. Well, can Maya come?
[MAYA] No, like I don't care.
Uh, yeah. Sure.
- Cool.
- Hi.
- Cool. We'll see you tomorrow.
- OK.
[MAYA] Bye!
- Bye.
[MAYA] Five! Six! Seven! Eight!
[SINGING]
♪ Why-oh-why ♪
♪ Hey, hey, hey! ♪
♪ I wanna be... ♪
♪ You gotta be bold ♪
♪ You gotta be wiser ♪
♪ You got be tough, you got to be strong ♪
♪ You got to be calmer ♪
You don't wanna do it anymore?
- What? Keep going.
- You don't wanna do it, Na?
What if Brendan wants to kiss me tomorrow?
I don't know if I want to.
You don't?
He tried last time, and it just felt,
like, really weird and unnatural,
but it's like, "Why?
I'm hot. He's hot." Like...
I think he's gonna.
Maybe it's gonna feel natural on Saturday.
Like, it won't be as weird as that time.
Maybe.
Anna, it's so simple, like...
It's like, this, like...
- I don't know.
[MAYA] You know what I mean.
Yeah, that looks good.
[MAYA] You have to do tongue.
- Kinda small head. [CHUCKLES]
[MAYA KISSING]
[SUCKING]
[MAYA] Stop it!
[DOOR OPENS]
- Hey, Anna, did you...
[SCREAMING] Dad! Get out!
[MAYA SHRIEKS]
Maya! Please, get out!
- No!
[ANNA] Maya is, like, naked!
- I'm just looking for my Discman.
- Dad, get out!
[MAYA] Get out!
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
- I don't think I'm gonna go tomorrow.
- Hmm?
- I don't think I wanna go.
- Why?
'Cause I'm not invited.
[ANNA] Yes, you are.
No, I'm not.
You asked.
Brendan didn't actually invite me.
Oh, my God, you always do this.
He just said you're going,
so that means you're invited.
Yeah, but you're gonna be, like,
off making out with him,
and I'm just gonna be, like,
sitting there by myself.
Why don't you find somebody
to go with you?
[MAYA] Like who?
Flymiamibro's like at
a computer conference
this weekend in Tucson.
I don't know. You could ask
one of the guys from soccer practice.
Mm.
[GROANING] No.
[JOVIAL MUSIC PLAYS]
[WHISTLES BLOWS]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Maya... just do this thing.
[INDISTINCT]
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
[GROANS]
- Did you get anybody?
- No.
Literally, no one will even
look at me, like...
Aw! I'm sure that's not true.
[BOY] Yeah!
[WHISTLES BLOWS]
[MAYA] 'Na, can you, like, focus?
You're off in Brendan-land waving it up.
Maya, I'm, like, waving at my BF.
Like, just chill.
Whatever.
Why don't you just go ask Sam?
Stop.
- Like...
- No, I don't want to...
Not to, like, hook up. Just to hang with.
[BOYS CHATTER INDISTINCTLY]
Please.
- Go. Come on.
- Fine. Whatever.
- Be nice.
- I am nice.
Hey, turd-hole.
Practicing with all your friends?
Ha-ha-ha. What do you want?
Um, are you going to, uh...
that movie thing or whatever tonight?
- What movie?
- Wild Things. At Brendan's, like...
Yeah. Why? [CHUCKLES]
- Well...
[JENNA] Oh, my gosh! Wow, Sam!
You're, like, really good at that.
Oh, thanks, Jenna.
It's... it's just dribblin'. [CHUCKLES]
Wait, what? Are you guys serious?
[SCOFFS] Oh, my God!
Dribbling's in basketball, moron, like...
No.
It's in uh... soccer.
- Dribbling is in soccer, too.
- Yep.
That's what it's called, dribbling.
So, Jenna, a bunch of us are going
to Brendan Tooler's place tonight
to watch Wild Things.
It's going to be fun.
- You should come.
- Um, yeah.
OK. That sounds fun.
Maybe you can show me
some of your moves there.
Well, there is not gonna
be soccer practice,
so that literally makes zero sense.
Um, cool, yeah.
- See you there.
- All right.
OK, I'm sorry,
but she was actually not invited.
I think it's really weird
that she'd show up.
Like, it's psycho, Sam.
I don't know
why you're being such a biatch,
because she's actually pretty nice.
Nice raging, dumbnuts.
I'm freaking nice, too.
And this is the den where we watch movies,
and sometimes, I play video games.
[ANNA] Oh, my God, it's so cool.
[INDISTINCT]
[MAYA] Yeah.
- No, it's not. It's a duck.
Wow thang!
Hmm-mm.
What's up?
- Hey.
- 'Sup! 'Sup! 'Sup!
- JK.
- What's up, Skyler?
Hey. Who's ready for some snacks?
[ANNA] Oh, my gosh.
[ANNA] Hi, Mrs. Tooler.
I'm Anna Kone.
Anna! I've heard so much about you!
I've heard so much about you.
Oh, Anna, you are just adorable.
Brendan, you talk about her all the time,
but you didn't say how adorable she is.
Mom, leave.
- Um, your den is so stunning!
[MAYA] Yeah.
So polite.
She's a keeper, Brendy.
I'm gonna stick your head
in the oven, Mom,
if you don't shut up.
OK. I can take a hint.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
That must be Cousin Richard.
I'll got let him in.
Go.
Your mom is really sweet.
Yeah. Whatever.
- Hey.
[BRENDAN] Hey.
- Oh, my God.
[BRENDAN] Everyone,
this is Cousin Richard.
- You got the movie?
[RICHARD] Yeah.
Used my bro's ID.
- They bought it.
[ANNA SNICKERS]
Why do you need an ID?
'Cause it's like X-rated I think.
I thought this was about animals.
Well, there are beavers, you know.
Oh, my God, Sam! You're, like, so funny.
So let's get the party started.
Ladies and germs,
tonight's feature film stars Matt Dillon,
Kevin Bacon, Denise Richards,
Denise Richards' blammos,
and Neve Campbell.
It is rated "R" for adult language
and sexual situations.
- Yes!
[BRENDAN] Let's go.
Yeah.
With a runtime of 108 minutes
including credits,
which you wanna stick around for,
I give you Wild Things.
[ALL CHEERING]
- Yeah, this is good.
[TAPE WHIRRING]
[MUSIC PLAYING IN MOVIE]
[WHISPERING] Switch seats with me.
Why?
So you'll be closer to...
Shh!
[CHUCKLING] You can sit beside Brendan.
[ANNA] No.
[MAYA] Yes.
[CHEERING ON TV]
[CHEERING CONTINUES]
So who's washing your Jeep
this weekend, Mr. Lombardo?
[MAN ON TV] Washing that old Jeep of mine
is sort of waste of time.
- Don't you think?
[WOMAN ON TV] Not at all.
[LAUGHTER]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION ON TV]
[INAUDIBLE]
[WHISPERING]
Brendan wants to hook up with Anna.
Brendan wants to hook up with you.
- No, he doesn't.
- Yes. He does.
Listen.
Cousin Richard literally just told me.
[INAUDIBLE]
My God, go! Go follow him.
No! No.
[MAYA] Go! Go!
- You should go follow him.
Go. It's now or never. Go.
Come with me. Come with me.
- No, let her go.
- I'm letting them go, Jenna.
Jenna, shut up!
- Will you please come with me?
[MAYA] No.
I'm gonna be there with you in your head
the whole...
Move.
Go! [SNARLS]
Bye.
- They're gonna get it all tonight.
- Oh, my God!
Don't try anything, perv.
I'll just move.
Sam, I was kidding.
Is this OK?
Absolutely.
[TENSE MUSIC IN MOVIE]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[DOOR OPENS]
- Hey.
Just gonna use the bathroom.
OK.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYS]
So you got my mom's money.
How much?
[SIGHS]
[MOVIE CONTINUES]
[LAUGHTER ON TV]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION ON TV]
[GARGLING]
[SENSUAL FEMALE VOCALIZING]
Hey.
[DRAMATIC CINEMATIC MUSIC PLAYS]
[KIDS CHEERING]
After tonight the three of us
are not to be seen together again.
After tonight?
[JEERING]
[MAYA] Oh, busted.
[INDISTINCT]
How was it?
I'll tell you later, OK?
Was it good?
Oh, here it is. Everyone needs to shut up.
[SENSUAL MUSIC PLAYS]
God in Heaven.
[MOANING ON TV]
Are you OK?
What happened?
- 'Na, what's wrong?
[MOUTHING] Stop.
[MAYA] And then, like, were your lips
close together
when you guys were standing
close together?
Yeah... and then they touched.
They did.
- That's, like, romantic.
- No, it wasn't.
- Yo, it literally wasn't at all.
- Why?
He puts his lips, like,
all the way around mine...
- Ew!
- And, like, sucked.
[CHUCKLES] What?
- It's not funny.
Wait. And then what? Was that it?
Like, he just sucked?
No, and then he put his tongue
in my mouth, and he, like...
did like a torpedo cat tongue,
and, like, drilled my mouth.
What was it like?
- What did he do with it?
- Like this.
- Ew! Ew! Stop!
[ANNA] Yeah.
I can't. I wish I could.
What did you do with your tongue?
Did you do it back or did you just, like...
It was, like, pinned back,
like, it was in trouble, you know.
- That's crazy.
- I know.
It was awful.
I'm sorry.
Well, at least you just, like,
had your first kiss, you know.
I wish that I hadn't.
- Don't say that.
- I really do.
Everything is just different now,
and I just have to breakup with him, so...
[MAYA] Really?
[INHALES DEEPLY]
Yeah.
He's not the Brendan that bought us snacks
at the bowling alley, you know.
Mm-hmm.
He's like the Brendan that drilled
the back of my throat with his tongue.
So... it's up to you
to get the next boyfriend.
Why?
What about Cousin Richard?
- Do you like him?
- No, I don't. It's not him.
Oh, it's someone?
Is it Sam?
No.
No. Let's just go to bed.
- Wait, look at me...
- What?
And let me ask you again. Is it Sam?
- Is what Sam?
- Do you like Sam?
Mm-mm.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
Hey, butt-rat!
Hey, Maya.
What the hell? You're, like, being weird.
I'm mad at you.
- OK.
[MAYA] Seriously?
I normally say things to you,
and then you say, like, mean things back.
Mm. Sorr...
God, you're just, like, being so lame.
It's like ever since you started dating
whatever her fricking name is,
- you're just being...
- Her name is Jenna.
Maybe if you try to be nicer to me
once in a while.
- I'm nice.
[SAM] Oh, yeah?
So how about you say
something nice right now?
[HESITATES] Like, right now?
- Yeah.
[SCOFFS]
[MAYA] Argh! OK, like...
You're, like, less dandruffy
in carpool this year. [CHUCKLES]
Oh, my God.
OK, I'm sorry. OK.
You... [SIGHS]
OK, you're...
you're, like, the funniest person
in our entire grade.
- Not bad.
- Yeah?
Do you have something nice
to say about me?
- Yeah.
- If you want.
Well, you do a really good Ace Ventura.
And?
And um...
you are a awesome friend.
That's it?
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACH]
- Hey, Maya. Hi, Sam.
- Hi.
[JENNA] Walk me to class?
Um, sure. See you later, Maya.
Whatever.
You've... left your locker open.
[ANNA] OK. So, can I read this to you?
[MAYA] Yeah.
OK. "Dear Brendan, wassup!
This is Anna Kone. We've been
boyfriend-girlfriend for three weeks now,
which is the longest relationship
I've ever been in.
I've been doing a lot of thinking
since we kissed last night at Wild Things.
This is hard, but I don't think
you're the one for me.
So I'm breaking up with you.
I hope we can still be friends.
See you in band. Anna Kone."
That's really good.
Should I mention about the kiss
that it was bad that he needs to work on?
No, I don't think so. That's mean.
[ANNA] Right.
- Yeah.
Will you give it to him for me?
Yeah. I will.
[TOILET FLUSH]
[DOOR OPENS]
Shh!
[WATER RUNNING]
It's Becca.
[MOUTHING]
[WHISPERS] Do you think she knows?
Hmm.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
You need to get that to him
before she does.
- OK. I can give...
- Run fast. Go! Go!
[DOOR OPENS]
Excuse me. Have you seen
Brendan Tooler? Skyler? No?
Have you seen Brendan or Skyler? Brendan?
Have you seen Brendan or Skyler?
None of you!
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
Phew!
- Hey, Kone,
[ANNA] Hey, Becca.
Oh, my God.
[BRENDAN VOICE-OVER] Dear Anna,
I don't think it's a good idea
that we go out anymore.
I'm breaking up with you. Brendan.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATION]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
I couldn't find Brendan
or Skyler anywhere,
- so I can't reach...
- It's OK.
It's OK. We got broken up with.
- Oh, my God, no.
- Yeah.
- I'm sorry.
- It's whatever, like...
I should've been faster. I'm sorry.
- I'm an idiot.
- No. I am.
[SIGHS]
- It's OK.
[ANNA SNIFFLES]
[ANNA] Your beady stupid little eyes,
your fat nose.
[MUMBLING]
I play your stupid saxophone like that,
asshole.
What?
Your mom said she overheard some stuff
in carpool about you and Braydan.
That's not his name,
and I don't wanna talk about it.
You really shouldn't hold things inside.
Are you guys serious?
What do you want me to say right now?
Do you want me to tell you
that I got dumped?
It's embarrassing.
That's what's happened, so...
- You're so much cuter than he is.
- Totally.
You're gonna have so many boyfriends
in your life...
- Totally.
- Before you
find the one you wanna be with.
I guess, yeah.
But... but look...
this is it. This is... This is love.
And you didn't have that with Brendan.
I know I didn't, and I still kissed him.
- Well, you had your first kiss.
- Oh!
[SNIFFLES]
We had and I wish I didn't.
It was disgusting.
You know... life is...
It's about experiences,
and someone else will come along.
Kissing definitely gets better. Right?
Yeah.
[JOVIAL MUSIC PLAYS]
What is wrong with you guys?
See. It gets better...
- OK. Oh, my God!
- And better...
and better.
[JOVIAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ALL VOCALIZING] Ooh!
Ooh!
Ooh, ooh!
[MISCHIEVOUS MUSIC PLAYS]