Last time on Pen15...
I just think the real thing
is that we've changed.
Yeah. So weird.
It's like, I think
we're on another level.
But you look
so beautiful, Maya.
You look like your mother.
I don't look
anything like her.
She's ugly.
‐ Maya, stop acting like
a little spoiled bitch.
‐ I don't like you.
You're ugly.
Maya.
You're gonna be okay.
My parents,
they're divorcing,
but they kind of share
the house.
‐ Sounds worse than
the "every other weekend" deal.
Did your mom tell you?
She's getting the house?
You'll have to decide
who you want to live with.
‐ Wait.
‐ That's the lead.
‐ Oh, my God!
‐ That is incredible.
‐ Wait.
Gonna be in the spotlight
‐ I know that you cast
your play already,
but if you have
an understudy role, I'm free.
We're techies‐‐we handle
all the technical elements
of the play.
‐ Kone, I'm making you
stage manager.
‐ Maya, you gotta remember
your lines.
‐ All you have to do right now
is just, like, pep me up.
‐ Good luck.
‐ Okay, you just jinxed me.
- It's "Break a leg."
- Ready, star?
Sam, how much do you like Maya
on a scale of one to ten?
Maya Ishii‐Peters?
You were just really good
in the play.
I've never seen you
like that before.
‐ When we sorta kissed
in my room,
you said
that you had butterflies.
I‐I didn't.
It's not you. It‐‐
‐ Maya!
‐ Vince Carter put
his whole arm in the rim.
‐ I know, he was, like,
hanging there from his elbow.
I know.
‐ Sam.
‐ Anna, stop.
‐ Hey.
Turn around. Like...
‐ She said my name.
‐ I know. I didn't.
‐ Turn around.
So, like, do you think
that the dress is
too short, or‐‐
‐ No, I love it.
‐ Are you sure?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Alex doesn't like it.
‐ What?
I love it.
I think you should wear it.
‐ All right.
Look at his shoes.
I think I saw them at Payless.
- Sad.
- I know.
Those are disgusting.
Oh, my God.
‐ Does anyone know
what these lines stand for?
Hmm?
These six lines...stand
for the six million people
killed in the Holocaust.
Jewish people, gypsies,
handicapped people,
homosexuals,
but mostly Jews were rounded up
by the Nazis, put in camps,
and eventually killed.
Six million lives.
Can you even comprehend that?
These camps...
‐ Oh, my God,
I feel, like, so bad
for the Jewish people
in World War II.
‐ I do too.
Prisoners were
systematically murdered...
‐ I could cry, honestly.
Over time
by their ruthless Nazi captors.
‐ Me too.
Mr. O: When a Nazi
would show up
at a Jewish person's door,
they were given one hour
to pack a bag
before being loaded
into a train
and taken away forever.
Yes, Miss Roth?
‐ I'm Jewish,
and it's really messed up,
you guys.
‐ I'm half.
‐ Oh, yeah.
‐ My grandfather once married
a Jewish woman,
but they got divorced
after a year.
‐ Ah. Okay.
It's actually such crazy timing
that we're talking about
the Holocaust right now,
because my bat mitzvah's
next weekend.
Everyone in this class
is invited, obviously,
but you guys, I haven't
received all the RSVPs.
So please, please, please RSVP.
All right, guys, guys...yeah.
I heard
there's gonna be Dippin' Dots.
At the party.
‐ Shh.
And you have an assignment.
‐ Guys.
‐ You guys, I'm sorry.
I'm not trying to be bossy.
There's just‐‐he's talking.
Mr. O: Thank you.
‐ There's an assignment, so...
‐ I'm trying to write it down.
Thank you.
Your homework assignment is
to present to the class
what single item
that you would bring with you
if the Nazis showed up
at your door.
‐ Oh, my God.
I, I am hiding
That you I show to you
Is just a lie
You take what you want
You get what you take
They jumped
so high, high, high
‐ You know, if we were
in the States in this time,
we'd be in the internment camp.
‐ Blah, blah, blah, blah, Mama.
I just, like‐‐I don't know
what I'm gonna wear.
I feel like, if I'm gonna go,
I should wear
the spaghetti strap dress,
maybe?
Or, like, get‐‐
‐ Focus on your homework.
‐ I am, Mom!
‐ Please.
‐ I'm just, like‐‐
I don't know what to bring.
I got something
of your grandma's.
I'll go get it for you.
You can bring them
to school, huh?
Okay?
‐ Okay, I don't care.
Shuji, have you ever been
to a bat mitzvah before?
I'm invited to one.
‐ Yeah, I've been to a couple.
They're bomb.
‐ Yeah, I know.
I think there's gonna be,
like, Dippin' Dots there
or something.
But, like, if I were gonna have
a bat mitzvah,
I feel like, I don't know,
I'd have Mom and Dad get me,
like...
a water fountain of Kool‐Aid
or something.
‐ Mom and Dad could never
afford that.
‐ What are you talking about?
Yeah, they could.
‐ Mom and Dad don't even own
this house.
‐ Okay, so what,
we live here for free?
No, seriously, like...
we're, like,
upper‐middle class,
like Anna, right?
‐ We're not even middle.
We're probably low.
Lower‐middle, if anything.
‐ But, like,
we can afford things.
Like, I have clothes and stuff.
We're not poor.
‐ We're dirt‐poor.
‐ No, we're not.
Dad has money. Like‐‐
‐ Dad's basically homeless.
‐ Stop it!
‐ Yeah.
‐ Stop!
‐ We're extra‐poor!
‐ Stop! Stop it, Shuji.
Say we're not poor.
Stop.
Maya, Maya,
we found some of Ojichan's
and Obachan's things.
You can take them all to school
and share and...
this was Obachan's.
Oh, I remember this.
And, oh, look at this.
Oh, some family photo too. Wow.
‐ Have you heard from your dad?
Anna!
‐ Yes.
‐ Is he still in that
crappy motel, or has he...
‐ He's still looking
for an apartment.
‐ Look, I'm really sorry
I have to go through you,
you know, but it's just‐‐
he just won't answer my‐‐
‐ He just doesn't want to talk
to you right now,
and you know that,
and so, like...
‐ Why are you so moody?
‐ Because I'm learning
about the Holocaust, okay?
‐ Okay.
‐ Like...
Okay, I'm sorry.
‐ Mom, I'm talking to you.
‐ Okay.
‐ Why are you leaving?
‐ I get‐‐I don't know.
‐ Are we Jewish?
Like, I know
that we're Unitarian and stuff,
and Russian, German, Polish...
but are we Jewish?
‐ German.
A lot of German.
‐ Are there Nazis
in our family?
‐ No.
Grampy fought them
in World War II.
I have his war mementos.
‐ Mom.
‐ Yes?
‐ Have I discovered
a family secret?
‐ There are no Nazis
in our family.
‐ Do you think that Nazis...
are all in Hell?
I don't know if Hell exists.
But if it does,
they are definitely there.
But then if it doesn't exist,
you're saying it's just fine
they're in heaven?
‐ I'm‐‐I'm saying I don't
even know if heaven exists.
‐ So then if there's no heaven,
where do you go when you die?
‐ I don't know.
I think you just have to be
in the present moment.
Why would He let
all this happen?
‐ Grampy?
‐ No.
God.
‐ Well, maybe God is a she,
or...
or a nothing, I don't know.
I don't know why evil exists
in this world.
Anna, I don't know.
I don't know
why there's suffering.
I don't know.
‐ It doesn't make sense.
No, it doesn't.
‐ And you don't have
any answers at all.
I'm sorry.
That's so cute.
I love that.
- It's so pretty.
- Right?
‐ Wait, you've already
gotten presents
and your bat mitzvah
hasn't even happened?
‐ Yeah.
‐ You guys, they're just
from family who live far away.
This one's good,
but my cousin got me a necklace
from Claire's.
Like, I get a rash from nickel.
Like, that's why
I only wear Swarovski.
Yeah. Yeah, like,
I know that about you.
‐ Sorry.
‐ All right, gang,
time for presentations.
Who wants to go first?
Ishii‐Peters,
love the enthusiasm.
‐ Okay.
Whoo!
‐ Um...
okay, so if the Nazis showed up
at my house
and was like,
"You have one hour to pack,
and you can only bring
one thing,"
um, I would bring...
this Chanel shopping bag.
Thank you.
That's what you're
bringing to the Holocaust?
That's crazy.
‐ You might die or never see
your family again,
and you'd bring
a Chanel shopping bag?
‐ Well, I wasn't‐‐
well...I also, um...
I brought‐‐
‐ You can only bring one thing.
Thank you, Maya.
So good.
‐ I get it.
You could put stuff in the bag.
- Shut up.
- Okay.
Becca, why don't‐‐why don't you
come up?
Becca, we love you.
‐ I would bring this picture
of my great‐great grandparents
who I admire so much.
Thanks.
Great, great.
Um...
Miss Kone.
‐ I'd bring a bullet.
‐ To kill Hitler.
So that none of this
ever happened.
‐ All right, I don't think
you should have that at school.
I should probably
confiscate that.
Yeah, um, I have a question.
How are you gonna shoot
without a gun?
‐ I'd find one at the place.
‐ That's stupid.
A knife would kill
way more Nazis than one bullet.
‐ No, if you had
a ton of bullets,
the bullets would do more.
Are you kidding?
‐ But, Anna, killing is wrong.
Think about it.
‐ Is it?
Is it in this situation,
though?
Because think about it.
Sometimes you have
to take justice
into your own hands
'cause God lets
things like this happen.
- If He or She even exists.
- Okay.
You can't say that!
Guys.
You can't
bring a bullet.
‐ You guys.
You guys.
I feel like it's because
we survived the Holocaust
that so many of us
have faith today.
Like, it's this feeling
I get when I'm in temple
that despite all the odds
being stacked against me
and my ancestors, we survived.
And that's how I know
God exists.
There's signs around me
every day.
It's kind of beautiful.
On a more serious note,
if you guys park
in front of the temple
on my bat mitzvah,
my dad will have to tow you.
So, like, do not do that, okay?
‐ Mom, how 'bout this one?
Like...
‐ Maya, no. No.
‐ No, no, just to look through.
That's the one she wants.
‐ That's not appropriate
for her.
I don't even have
a jewelry like that.
‐ Mom, it's a necklace.
Like, she'll want that.
‐ Oh, how 'bout this one?
Mm, it's nice.
‐ Mom, what is wrong with you?
I'm not giving her a pen.
‐ Pen is a nice gift.
‐ Mom, oh, my God.
Ugh, you're, like,
so old‐fashioned.
Like, you don't understand.
You can't give a pen!
You have to give, like...
like, a necklace,
like something like this.
Like, that's something
she would really like,
and I feel like I need
to get that.
‐ You know, you can always‐‐
‐ Mom, seriously, please?
Like, can I just
get her this necklace?
‐ Maya, we can always get her
18 dollar.
It's Jewish good luck.
‐ Wow.
Okay, yeah,
I'm gonna write a check‐‐
or no, I'll just put a bunch
of single dollar bills
in a little envelope,
be like,
"Hey, happy bat mitzvah.
Here's $18 that you can spend
on a can of Coke!"
Are you serious?
You're acting like we're poor!
Like, what is wrong with you?
Literally,
you're ruining my life!
Like, I need it!
Guys, guys, come on.
Enough with the yelling,
all right? Come on.
Uh, Yuki, let's‐‐
let's just get it.
‐ No‐‐I mean, a necklace
from Swarovski?
Yes.
Well, if it's important to her,
you know, I can play a couple
of more gigs this week.
- I mean, look at her.
- Absolutely not.
No.
- Come on, honey.
- Absolutely not.
It's too expensive.
Welcome to Swarovski.
This is Karen speaking.
How can I help you?
‐ This necklace, Dad.
‐ Yeah, hello, Karen.
‐ Dad, this one.
‐ Um, I was wondering, uh,
how much it would be total
for the Stone Necklace.
‐ That one's 135.
Wowza.
Listen, uh, Karen, we're, uh‐‐
we're trying to get
a bat mitzvah gift.
‐ Dad.
‐ Is there something a little‐‐
‐ Hi, Karen.
‐ Hi.
‐ Hi. Sorry.
‐ That's okay.
‐ Um, okay.
How 'bout...
how 'bout the Sparkling Dance
Heart Necklace?
How much is that?
‐ That's $120.
Mom, it's only $120. Mom.
Or how about
the Flower Bracelet,
'cause that one
doesn't have a chain,
so maybe it's less expensive?
Or...
we don't have to.
We don't have to.
I don't want it. It's okay.
No, no, no, no, no.
‐ No. No. No.
We're on the phone.
‐ Hello?
‐ No, Mom doesn't want...
Uh, Karen, yeah.
- Can you just hold on a sec?
- Sure.
‐ Listen, the, um‐‐
the big diamond
that's‐‐that's a little showy.
‐ No, I know.
We don't have to.
‐ Maybe the Sparkling Dance
Heart Necklace
is‐is more appropriate for 13.
It's classy.
‐ Really?
‐ Yeah.
Yeah. Hey, um, yeah, Karen.
‐ Mom, we don't have to.
‐ Listen, is there any way
- you could do layaway?
- Sure.
- That won't be a problem.
- All right, good.
And‐‐ooh, look.
Two‐for‐one pizza.
Antonio's. Boi‐oi‐oi‐oing!
Yeah, okay.
All right, are you ready?
‐ Late much?
Oh, my God, that's my gift.
‐ Sorry.
‐ Literally so expensive.
‐ You guys.
‐ Sorry.
‐ Sorry, he just stepped
on my gift.
‐ Maya?
‐ What?
‐ You know how Becca was like,
"Oh, there's, like, a sign
so I know that God exists"?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Like, I want that.
‐ Okay.
‐ But I'm not seeing it yet,
so will you pray with me
so God hears?
‐ Okay.
God, if you exist,
make the rabbi's handkerchief
fall when I open my eyes.
Amen
I'm blue
Da ba dee da ba di
da ba dee da ba di
Oh, my God, this party's,
like, unbelievable.
Oh, my God!
They have Dippin' Dots.
Oh, my God.
‐ Okay, okay.
I'm definitely gonna get
strawberry nanners.
I'm getting it.
Glow sticks!
It's earth's poison.
But I guess it doesn't matter.
I don't care.
‐ When should I give my present
to her?
Should I give it now or later?
‐ What?
‐ Okay, later.
I'm gonna give it later
because I feel like
she's not gonna
even pay attention to it now.
Whatever Lola wants
Lola gets
And little man
Little Lola wants you
Make up your mind to have
‐ She's so good.
‐  No regrets
‐ That's why
it's musical‐theatre themed.
Resign yourself
You're through
I always get
What I aim for
And your heart and soul
Is what I came for
Thank you guys so much
for coming to my bat mitzvah.
As a woman,
I feel it's my responsibility
to make sure you all have
a great time tonight.
So let's make this party
super cool!
Yeah!
We are family
I got all my sisters
with me
We are family
Get up everybody and sing
‐ What?
You're not having fun?
‐ No, I'm just not in the mood
right now.
Yeah.
You sufferin'?
‐ Kinda, yeah.
But I don't know.
It doesn't matter, actually.
‐ Oh, see...
I don't‐‐I don't agree
with that.
There is nothing
that doesn't matter.
You know...
Becca's grandma always used
to say,
"If you're lucky enough
to live...
"live.
"And if you get the chance
to dance...
Dance."
It's electric!
You can't see it
You gotta feel it
It's electric!
Ooh, it's shakin'
Here, there, everywhere
I've got to move
Whoo!
I'm going on a party ride
I've got to groove,
groove, groove
And from this music,
I just can't hide
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
Sorry.
Went in the wrong door.
‐ Kone?
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ It's me.
- Steve.
- So embarrassing. Yeah.
I see that.
‐ Hey.
Sorry, I can't breathe.
‐ It's cool. It's fine. It's...
come on.
Follow me.
‐ Okay.
‐ You know, Becca, you're,
like, so good at singing.
‐ Thank you.
‐ Yeah, that's what
I was gonna say.
You're, like, really good.
‐ Oh, you guys are so sweet.
‐ Do you take, like, lessons
or...
‐ I take a few,
but I definitely just
love performing.
‐ Yeah.
‐ You're a natural.
‐ So good.
‐ Thanks.
‐ Hi, Becca.
Congratulations.
It's so amazing.
It's, like, awesome.
‐ Thank you.
‐ Um, I just‐‐I have my gift
for you,
so I wanted you to open it.
‐ Oh, thanks.
You could just put it
on the table behind me.
‐ Or actually, can you‐‐
it's just, like,
a really special gift,
so if you don't mind,
just, like, open it.
‐ Sure.
You've been on my mind
And I think it is the time
To let you know
‐ Do you wanna dance, Maya?
What?
‐ Do you wanna dance?
‐ No, I heard you.
I'm just like, "What?"
No, 'cause you don't have
good shoes.
‐ What?
‐ I'm just kidding.
I'm just kidding. Sorry.
Can you‐‐
I'm, like, in the middle
of something,
so it's a little annoying.
Oh, cute.
I think I have
a couple of these,
but thanks, Maya.
So sweet.
Is there, like, a receipt?
- 'Cause you can return it.
- Oh, no, it's okay.
Thanks, Maya.
‐ You're welcome.
Do you like it?
Yeah, it's‐‐
it's really pretty.
Thanks.
Anyway, so we should have,
like, a slumber party.
- Totally.
- Bring snacks.
‐ Yeah!
‐ One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, hold.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, exhale.
Working?
Sorry.
‐ You feeling better?
‐ Yeah.
I don't know what's happening.
‐ Crème de menthe?
‐ Okay.
I don't...yeah.
Thanks.
Anna, where have you been?
‐ Hi, Mai.
‐ What the hell? Like‐‐
‐ Oh, my God, I'm so sorry.
I just had, like,
a total freak‐out,
and I just bumped into Steve.
‐ Hi.
‐ He's just making me
feel better.
‐ Hey.
‐ Sorry, like...
‐ You okay?
‐ Yeah, no, I'm fine.
It's just, like,
Becca opened the gift
and didn't like it, so...
‐ Sorry.
‐ Want a drink?
‐ Oh, yeah.
Did you drink?
‐ Just a little,
but I won't have more
unless you want some.
‐ No, I‐‐let's drink, damn it.
‐ Yeah, and I love
this alcohol, actually.
‐ Yeah, it's‐‐it's good
because it doesn't make
your breath smell like alcohol,
just minty fresh.
‐ It burns.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Are you gonna get in trouble
for being out here?
Fuck 'em.
‐ Yeah.
What do you guys think
happens when you die?
‐ You rot.
God doesn't exist.
‐ Agreed.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Can I have your number?
‐ What?
‐ Uh, can I have your number?
‐ Yeah, sure.
‐ I don't usually go
for younger girls,
but you're‐‐you're different.
‐ Thanks.
I should steal it back.
Guys?
Sorry, guys?
Sorry, I think I should steal
the present back.
'Cause my parents spent
a lot of money on it.
Right?
‐ Yeah.
‐ 'Cause she doesn't even
know it's there.
Like, she won't miss it.
‐ Yeah, 'cause she's a bitch.
‐ She sounds like a bitch.
‐ She was a bitch.
‐ Take it back.
‐ Let's...
‐ Okay!
‐ Fucking get your gift back.
‐ Let's do it.
‐ Okay, so I'm doing it?
‐ We're doing it.
‐ Okay, I'm doing it.
Okay, fine. Oh, my God.
Okay.
‐ It's okay, be chill.
‐ Are they looking?
‐ Where? No.
I see her. She's right there.
Go. Go.
‐ This is my necklace,
and I'm taking it.
Just taking it back. I got it.
Oh, my God, is she looking?
‐ No, she's not looking.
You are crazy
You are a crazy girl
I see the questions
In your eyes
I know what's weighing
on your mind
You can be sure
I know my part
‐ You okay?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Anna, may I have this dance?
‐ Um, can Maya dance with us?
‐ No, I don't want
to be a third wheel.
‐ It's okay.
‐ No, I don't wanna.
It's cool.
It's all one wheel.
‐ Yeah.
It's one wheel.
‐ Stop.
‐ I'm so drunk.
I'm so drunk.
And I swear
By the moon and the stars
in the sky
I'll be there
I swear
I'm a horse.
Like a shadow
That's by your side
I'll be there
Wait, are you into Steve?
Like, are you guys going out?
‐ Shh.
‐ He can't hear.
He just asked for my number.
‐ Oh, my God, okay.
You have a boyfriend now!
‐ Maya?
‐ What?
You should meet
my friend Derrick.
I think he'd really like you.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ Stop!
‐ Future boyfriend.
‐ Shut up, Anna! No, I don't‐‐
‐ He's cool, he's cool.
‐ He's cool.
‐ Wait, we're like...
you guys.
‐ Like, yeah.
Oh, my God, stop.
We'll hang some memories
On the walls
‐ That's not what I wanted.
‐ Hey, party girl.
No hello?
‐ Hey, Mam‐‐Mom.
How was it?
Was it fun?
So fun.
‐ Can I give you a hug?
‐ Mm‐hmm.
Mm.
‐ Mm.
‐ Have you been drinking?
‐ No!
What?
Sorry.
‐ What's going on with you?
‐ Is it Maya?
No, it's not Maya.
It's you and Dad.
And nothing matters.
‐ I'm so sorry.
You can always talk to me or...
Spirit or...
whatever,
if you feel overwhelmed.
‐ Mm‐hmm.
Thanks.
Mm...
‐ But you don't need to drink.
‐ Everything is spinning.
Ugh.
Will you lay down with me, Mom?
Hold my hand.
‐ You haven't wanted me
to hold your hand
since you were eight.
Thank you.
I love you.
‐ I love you too.
‐ Mom.
‐ Hm?
What is this?
It's a necklace.
Mm.
‐ I'm sorry I made Dad
buy it for me.
You can keep it, okay?