[DOOR OPENS]
[ANNA] Bye, Mom. Love you.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Is she OK?
- She, like, didn't come down.
- That's OK.
- Are you OK?
- Yeah.
- Are you sure?
- Mm-hmm.
Really?
[ANNA] Really, Dad.
You don't have any lingering questions
on your mind?
No, I mean...
I just think that probably
the hardest part
was when you and mom told me.
Um... but I think that it's ultimately
gonna be the best for everyone honestly,
- because we could all use a breather...
[KATHY] We could all use a breather...
from the recent hostility.
[SIGHS] It's not like
things are gonna get any better.
[ANNA] And maybe sometime,
after you guys take some space,
you guys might wanna get back together
or something. I don't know.
Who knows.
Yeah.
[ENGINE TURNS ON]
[MAYA SINGING]
♪ I'm not a child ♪
♪ I'm just a woman ♪
♪ You don't have to be a girl anymore ♪
[ANNA] Hey.
Hey.
Sorry I yelled at you last night.
Yeah, I thought I'd hear from you.
Last night was just really shitty
and like...
Yeah, last night was really shitty
for me, too.
You know...
guess we just can't do everything together
like we thought.
I'm just saying "hey"
to Heather really quick.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[ANNA] Hey.
- Hi, Anna.
- Hey, um...
[ANNA] I'm sorry to interrupt.
[HEATHER] No, it's not, it's fine.
I'm sorry about your parents' divorce.
[ANNA] Oh, thanks.
[HEATHER] When my parents divorced,
it, like, sucked, but... you'll be fine.
- It's just hard to comprehend.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I know it feels
like the world's ending, right?
Yeah, it... it really does,
and I'm, like, kind of in shock.
Mm-hmm. On the bright side,
you'll get two of everything.
- So I gotta go.
[ANNA] OK. Bye. Oh, thanks.
I'm OK.
[PRINCIPAL RAVAGE]
Good Morning, Trailview Middle.
It's 55 and partly cloudy.
Bring your coats tonight for the dance.
Remember our clothing rules,
nothing short, nothing tight,
we gonna dance till the morning light.
Where's Anna?
I don't know.
She's over there.
[GABE] The popular girls.
So she's sitting with them now?
It's really different.
Do you know that she told Heather
before she told me
that her parents are getting divorced?
- Can you believe that?
- OK.
I'm gonna tell you something, Maya.
- Just... don't freak out.
- Don't say anything to me right now.
What do you have to say? What? What?
All right. I heard a rumor that
Heather is taking Anna to the dance.
What? What did you say?
That was our plan
to go to the dance together.
We had a lot of plans tonight
so that's real...
Ho, ho, bitch. OK. OK.
Well, at least we're still going together.
I mean, together, as in like a group.
Hi, guys. Hey, Maya.
[GABE] Hey, Jenna.
[JAFEER] Hey, Jenna.
Hey, Jeanine.
- It's Jenna.
- What?
- That's what I said. "Hey, Jenna".
- Wassup.
- The sun.
[CHUCKLING] JK.
[TOILET FLUSHES]
[MUMBLING] Oh, my God.
[MUTTERING]
[FLUSH HANDLE CLANGING]
- Hey.
[MAYA]
Hi.
Is something wrong with the toilet?
No. No, you don't have to look.
That's not...
Uh, you know... you can't flush pads.
No, I know. That's not a pa...
- That's not mine.
[JAN] Mm.
'Cause I don't, I don't have my periods,
so I think that's someone
that put in there...
Uh, you know, it's... it's natural.
It happens to everyone.
Good for them.
Ahem. Here. For whenever.
Well, I don't need it,
so I'll find someone who does.
[DESKTOP BEEPS]
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[DOOR BELL RINGS]
[SIGHS]
- Maya.
- What?
[IN JAPANESE] Get off the computer!
[IN ENGLISH] OK.
[IN JAPANESE] Now!
[SIGHS]
Hello. Ah!
It's your first shave before
your first dance. Are you two excited?
It's gonna be fun.
OK, this is a really big deal, girls.
Yeah. Once you start, you can never stop.
I just wanna make sure you know for sure
if you really want to start shaving.
- Mm-hmm.
[YUKI] OK.
[KATHY] OK. OK.
Yeah.
- Oh, you got me wet.
- I'm sorry.
Oh, it's OK.
[YUKI] You might bleed or cut,
so be careful.
Maya, don't shave over your knees.
[MAYA] Mom...
- Always under and under your short pants.
Mom, they're called pedal pushers, like...
OK, whatever. Pedal pushers, OK?
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
[ANNA] Why are you looking at me
like that?
I'm not looking like you at anything.
What?
What time do you think
you're gonna be at Sam's?
Um, what time? I don't know.
I'm not that good at time.
Oh, really? 'Cause I feel,
like, you're usually,
like, always on time and good with time
and, like, keeping time.
- Why do you keep saying "time"?
- 'Cause, um...
I heard that you were invited to Heather's
to get ready at her house before.
Is that what you're gonna do?
No, I didn't say that.
[STAMMERS] I might take pictures
after this with Heather
and do half the time there
and half the time at Sam's.
- Yeah. So you lied.
[KATHY] OK, Wait a second.
You're expecting me to drive you
to two places now
to have your picture taken?
Because we did not discuss this.
And... and who is Heather?
Heather... Heather Taylor?
Yeah, she's like the most popular girl
in school.
[KATHY] Ooh.
- I guess, like,
Anna's best friends
with her right now so...
I'm actually not best friends with her.
She's just being really nice to me.
- OK.
- So...
- Whatever. It's fine.
- Can you stop?
I'm not doing anything.
Stop telling me to stop.
OK, everybody, time to get out.
[DARK CLASSICAL PIANO MUSIC
BY FRÉDÉRIC CHOPIN PLAYS]
[INAUDIBLE]
[RECORD SCRATCHING]
["E.I" BY NELLY PLAYS]
♪ Uh... uh uh uh uh ♪
♪ Uh... wait a minute now ♪
♪ Uh-oh! ♪
♪ I'm a sucker for corn rows
And manicured toes ♪
♪ Fendi capri pants and Parasuco's ♪
♪ The rise of Diddy and City
With one or two throws ♪
♪ I'm draftin' 'em outta high school
Straight into the pros ♪
♪ Who knows? I know and I love it
When you make your knees ♪
♪ Touch your elbows
And break it down low to the flo' ♪
♪ And there you go
Now throw it on me slow ♪
♪ And every time I bust a rhyme, baby
Gimme some more ♪
♪ You say you like that
When I hit it from behind ♪
♪ And I'll be right back
Yeah, that's my very next line ♪
♪ I use it time after time
When I'm speakin' my mind ♪
♪ It's no matter if I'm shootin' game
To a pigeon or dime ♪
♪ I ask her who that is ♪
Hey.
Hi. Sorry couldn't make it
to getting ready.
["ROCK THE PARTY OFF THE HOOK"
BY P. O. D PLAYS]
♪ We came to rock the party
all night long ♪
♪ From the left to right
And the back to front ♪
♪ So party people
Won't you sing that song ♪
♪ Gonna get, can I get one time ♪
♪ We came to rock the party
All night long ♪
♪ And all the time
Because you know we got soul ♪
♪ And keep it live
Till the break of dawn ♪
- Can you save me a dance?
- Oh, my God.
You look, like, super-different.
Um, can I...
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYS]
♪ Waiting for the sun
So I can see your face again ♪
♪ I miss you oh so much
Can't take another night ♪
♪ Without you in my arms ♪
♪ You're the only one I dream of ♪
[BRENDAN] Earth to Anna.
Circle back in 15.
["JAMBOREE" BY NAUGHTY BY NATURE PLAYS]
♪ I want to see y'all
Who want to plan with me ♪
[SIGHS]
You OK?
I just saw something. I wish I didn't.
Does it have something to do with me?
I can't say it, but, yeah.
Oh, my God, you keep looking at her.
Maya? No, I was looking at the, uh, wall.
Yeah. No, Yeah, yeah, yeah. Right.
OK, you know what?
If you're so obsessed with her,
why don't you go dance with her
instead of me.
What, Jenna? Come on.
[SIGHS]
♪ Shake my shell with the shooters
Leed a luga with duga ♪
♪ Some say modeling and acting
Mean treach is selling ♪
[BECCA] Ew.
Alex is over there.
Yeah, I know. I'm so over him.
- Yeah, right?
- No, like, for real. This time I am done.
But, like, what if you saw him dancing
with another girl tonight?
-[CONNIE] Like, would any
part of you care?
-Not at all.
But speaking of boys, you should see...
♪ While oh damn
I know I jam I know I jam jam boree ♪
♪ I know I jam I know I jam jam ♪
♪ I want to see y'all
Who want to plan with me ♪
♪ Wave your hands across the land
If we family ♪
♪ Say hot-damn hot-damn
We want to jamboree ♪
♪ This is for my peeps here
I stand for you ♪
♪ Cause you stand for me ♪
♪ C'mon I know I jam I know I jam jam ♪
What's the deal with Jenna?
- I don't know. She's a drama queen.
- Yeah.
["ALL MY LIFE" BY K-CI & JOJO
PLAYS IN THE BACKGROUND]
- Oh, my God.
- I know.
I'm sorry, that must be really hard.
'Cause you like...
you like her or whatever.
Yeah, it is. A little bit.
Do you want to dance?
[BLOWING RASPBERRIES]
Come on, Sam.
I'm sorry. That probably hurt.
Ow!
- Just kidding.
- OK.
So, like, do you?
What?
- Do you wanna dance?
[SCOFFS] Like, whatever. Yeah, I guess.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING]
OK.
Alex, will you dance with me?
[MOUTHING]
♪ Said, I promise to never fall in love
With a stranger ♪
Oh, my God.
♪ You're all I'm thinking of ♪
♪ I praise the Lord above ♪
Holy Jesus.
♪ I cherish every hug ♪
♪ I really love you ♪
Wassup.
I just wanted to ask you something. Um...
Just say it. [CHUCKLES]
Alex, will you dance with me?
No.
- Let's get out of here.
[BOY] All right.
- What did you just say to Alex?
- Um, I just asked him to dance.
- But he said no, so...
- That's so messed up.
Thank you, guys. It's OK.
I'm OK, though, so...
No, what's fucked up
is that you would do that to Heather.
- She took you under her wing.
- And she didn't even want to.
Tell her, Heather.
My mom made me invite you,
because your parents were breaking up,
and we wanted to be nice
and that's... just so you know.
[MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING]
Flymiamibro22.
What?
It's me.
I'm flymiamibro22.
- What are you talking about?
- It's me.
What have you done?
- Oh, my God.
[SAM] Maya.
[MAYA] Excuse me.
[SOBBING]
["YOU GOTTA BE" BY DES'REE PLAYS]
♪ Listen as your day unfolds
Challenge what the future holds ♪
♪ Try and keep your head up to the sky ♪
♪ Lovers, they may cause you tears ♪
♪ Go ahead release your fears ♪
♪ Stand up and be counted
Don't be ashamed to cry ♪
♪ You gotta be
You gotta be bad ♪
♪ You gotta be bold
You gotta be wiser ♪
♪ You gotta be hard
You gotta be tough ♪
♪ You gotta be stronger ♪
♪ You gotta be cool
You gotta be calm ♪
♪ You gotta stay together ♪
♪ All I know all I know
Love will save the day ♪
Don't leave me.
Don't leave me, OK?
[CURIOUS MUSIC PLAYS]
[HIP HOP MUSIC PLAYS]
[DJ] You feelin' this, Trailview?
[INDISTINCT]
This is your last freak song,
middle schoolers.
So get your grind on.
- Oh, my God. Who is it?
- Skyler.
- Skyler L or Skyler T?
- L.
[MOUTHING]
- Who is that?
- Brendan.
Nice moves, UGIS.
I'm not UGIS, you fuck-butt.
Go fuck a dick till it comes, suck-face!
Jesus, I was just kidding.
You want me to finger you?
- Yeah.
- Just, uh... meet me back there.
Don't let anyone see you.
- Oh, my God.
- 'Na, come with me.
- It's all happening. It's all happening.
- No. No. Come with me.
OK.
Spooky in the dark. [CHUCKLES]
Stop.
So, how do you wanna do this?
Wait, hold on. Sorry, sorry, sorry.
[WHISPERING] I don't wanna do finger.
[WHISPERING] What?
I don't wanna do finger.
OK, can... can you do it?
- Um... I'm like...
- Just, like, do it.
- I... I don't know. I'm not, um, ready.
- Yo?
- Um...
- Second base?
Both of you?
- Yeah.
- Cool.
- OK. Oh, my God. [CHUCKLING]
[GROANS]
[HESITATING]
Is that good... rotation pattern?
- You're both really hard-nipped.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
- Don't tell anyone.
- Yeah.
Wait at least a minute
before you come out.
OK.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
- Oh, my God!
[MAYA WHISPERING] Do you believe
that Sam is flymiamibro?
[ANNA WHISPERING]
Oh, my God. It's so crazy.
But at least Alex didn't like
say no to you.
[MAYA] Yeah, I know, but then, like,
Brandt said that thing to me,
but then, like, I did the crazy thing,
and it felt, like, he was into it.
And then that's why he then asked, like...
Yeah.
- I know.
- Wait. Anna.
What?
- We both got felt up for the first time.
- I know. Second base.
- Together. Do you like him?
- I, like, love him.
- Wait, do you like him?
- No, he's kind of an asshole.
And he's best friends with Alex,
so it's just, like...
Something didn't happen today with Alex,
but it could tomorrow,
so I don't wanna complicate that.
- I feel, like, older.
- I know. Me, too.
I wonder when we'll get our periods.
Yeah, I know. Yeah.
Can I ask you a question?
- Uh-huh.
- But you promise not to get mad.
Yeah.
Why did you tell Heather
about your parents getting divorced
before me?
- I called you first.
- No, you didn't.
For your information, I did.
I called you first,
and you didn't pick up.
Then why didn't you leave a message?
- Maya...
[MAYA] What?
That my parents are divorcing.
- Yeah.
- And you were so mad at me that night.
So I called Heather,
because she's the only person
in our grade with parents
that are divorced.
- Lie.
- What are you talking about?
Terra Newback.
-OK.
-[MAYA] Terra Newback's parents
are divorced.
OK, I didn't think about that.
- I'm just saying, like...
- When you found out you were so weird
you didn't even care.
You didn't. You were, like...
'Cause it's a huge deal,
and I shouldn't have
found out that way. Like, are you serious?
It's not about you! Are you serious, Maya?
- It's not about you!
- OK, sorry!
It's about me,
because it's the saddest thing
that has ever happened to me.
No, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine. Stop!
Come here. I'm sorry.
[SNIFFLING]
I don't know what it's like.
I could never know, and I'm sorry.
- Parents are assholes.
- Yeah, they really are.
That's all really. It's fine.
Thanks.
Wait.
Oh, my God.
Do you wanna take a walk?
But, no, no, stop.
We're just gonna do it, like...
We're doing it.
Listen to that.
- Is that the wrong way?
- No, I think that's the right way.
Right?
I like it.
You have to inhale.
You're not inhaling.
Are you OK?
Do you wanna go inside?
No, let's just stay out here.
[NOSTALGIC PIANO MUSIC PLAYS]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYS]