Bye, Mom. Love you.
Is she OK?
- She, like, didn't come down.
- That's OK.
- Are you OK?
- Yeah.
- Are you sure?
- Mm-hmm.
Really?
Really, Dad.
You don't have any lingering questions
on your mind?
No, I mean...
I just think that probably
the hardest part
was when you and mom told me.
Um... but I think that it's ultimately
gonna be the best for everyone honestly,
- because we could all use a breather...
- We could all use a breather...
...from the recent hostility.
It's not like
things are gonna get any better.
And maybe sometime,
after you guys take some space,
you guys might wanna get back together
or something. I don't know.
Who knows.
Yeah.
♪ I'm not a child ♪
♪ I'm just a woman ♪
♪ You don't have to be a girl anymore ♪
Hey.
Sorry I yelled at you last night.
Yeah, I thought I'd hear from you.
Last night was just really shitty
and like...
Yeah, last night was really shitty
for me, too.
You know...
guess we just can't do everything together
like we thought.
I'm just saying "hey"
to Heather really quick.
- Hey.
- Hi, Anna.
Hey.
- Hey, um...
- I'm sorry to interrupt.
No, it's not, it's fine.
I'm sorry about your parents' divorce.
- Oh, thanks.
- When my parents divorced,
it, like, sucked, but... you'll be fine.
- It's just hard to comprehend.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I know it feels
like the world's ending, right?
Yeah, it... it really does,
and I'm, like, kind of in shock.
Mm-hmm. On the bright side,
you'll get two of everything.
- So I gotta go.
- OK. Bye. Oh, thanks.
I'm OK.
Good Morning, Trailview Middle.
It's 55 and partly cloudy.
Bring your coats tonight for the dance.
Remember our clothing rules,
nothing short, nothing tight,
we gonna dance till the morning light.
Where's Anna?
I don't know.
She's over there.
The popular girls.
So she's sitting with them now?
It's really different.
Do you know that she told Heather
before she told me
that her parents are getting divorced?
- Can you believe that?
- OK.
I'm gonna tell you something, Maya.
- Just... don't freak out.
- Don't say anything to me right now.
What do you have to say? What? What?
All right. I heard a rumor that
Heather is taking Anna to the dance.
What? What did you say?
That was our plan
to go to the dance together.
We had a lot of plans tonight
so that's real...
Ho, ho, bitch. OK. OK.
Well, at least we're still going together.
I mean, together, as in like a group.
Hi, guys. Hey, Maya.
- Hey, Jenna.
Hey, Jeanine.
- It's Jenna.
- What?
- That's what I said. "Hey, Jenna".
- Wassup.
- The sun.
JK.
Oh, my God.
- Hey.
Hi.
Is something wrong with the toilet?
No. No, you don't have to look.
That's not...
Uh, you know... you can't flush pads.
No, I know. That's not a pa...
- That's not mine.
- Mm.
'Cause I don't, I don't have my periods,
so I think that's someone
that put in there...
Uh, you know, it's... it's natural.
It happens to everyone.
Good for them.
Ahem. Here. For whenever.
Well, I don't need it,
so I'll find someone who does.
- Maya.
- What?
- Get off the computer!
- OK.
- Now!
Hello. Ah!
It's your first shave before
your first dance. Are you two excited?
It's gonna be fun.
OK, this is a really big deal, girls.
Yeah. Once you start, you can never stop.
I just wanna make sure you know for sure
if you really want to start shaving.
- Mm-hmm.
- OK.
- OK. OK.
Yeah.
- Oh, you got me wet.
- I'm sorry.
Oh, it's OK.
You might bleed or cut,
so be careful.
Maya, don't shave over your knees.
- Mom...
- Always under and under your short pants.
Mom, they're called pedal pushers, like...
OK, whatever. Pedal pushers, OK?
Why are you looking at me
like that?
I'm not looking like you at anything.
What?
What time do you think
you're gonna be at Sam's?
Um, what time? I don't know.
I'm not that good at time.
Oh, really? 'Cause I feel,
like, you're usually,
like, always on time and good with time
and, like, keeping time.
- Why do you keep saying "time"?
- 'Cause, um...
I heard that you were invited to Heather's
to get ready at her house before.
Is that what you're gonna do?
No, I didn't say that.
I might take pictures
after this with Heather
and do half the time there
and half the time at Sam's.
- Yeah. So you lied.
- OK, Wait a second.
You're expecting me to drive you
to two places now
to have your picture taken?
Because we did not discuss this.
And... and who is Heather?
Heather... Heather Taylor?
Yeah, she's like the most popular girl
in school.
- Ooh.
- I guess, like,
Anna's best friends
with her right now so...
I'm actually not best friends with her.
She's just being really nice to me.
- OK.
- So...
- Whatever. It's fine.
- Can you stop?
I'm not doing anything.
Stop telling me to stop.
OK, everybody, time to get out.
Hey.
Hi. Sorry couldn't make it
to getting ready.
- Can you save me a dance?
- Oh, my God.
You look, like, super-different.
Um, can I...
Earth to Anna.
Circle back in 15.
You OK?
I just saw something. I wish I didn't.
Does it have something to do with me?
I can't say it, but, yeah.
Oh, my God, you keep looking at her.
Maya? No, I was looking at the, uh, wall.
Yeah. No, Yeah, yeah, yeah. Right.
OK, you know what?
If you're so obsessed with her,
why don't you go dance with her
instead of me.
What, Jenna? Come on.
Ew.
Alex is over there.
Yeah, I know. I'm so over him.
- Yeah, right?
- No, like, for real. This time I am done.
But, like, what if you saw him dancing
with another girl tonight?
- Like, would any part of you care?
- Not at all.
But speaking of boys, you should see...
What's the deal with Jenna?
- I don't know. She's a drama queen.
- Yeah.
- Oh, my God.
- I know.
I'm sorry, that must be really hard.
'Cause you like...
you like her or whatever.
Yeah, it is. A little bit.
Do you want to dance?
Come on, Sam.
I'm sorry. That probably hurt.
Ow!
- Just kidding.
- OK.
So, like, do you?
What?
- Do you wanna dance?
- Like, whatever. Yeah, I guess.
OK.
Alex, will you dance with me?
Oh, my God.
Holy Jesus.
Wassup.
I just wanted to ask you something. Um...
Just say it.
Alex, will you dance with me?
No.
- Let's get out of here.
- All right.
- What did you just say to Alex?
- Um, I just asked him to dance.
- But he said no, so...
- That's so messed up.
Thank you, guys. It's OK.
I'm OK, though, so...
No, what's fucked up
is that you would do that to Heather.
- She took you under her wing.
- And she didn't even want to.
Tell her, Heather.
My mom made me invite you,
because your parents were breaking up,
and we wanted to be nice
and that's... just so you know.
Flymiamibro22.
What?
It's me.
I'm flymiamibro22.
- What are you talking about?
- It's me.
What have you done?
- Oh, my God.
- Maya.
Excuse me.
Don't leave me.
Don't leave me, OK?
You feelin' this, Trailview?
This is your last freak song,
middle schoolers.
So get your grind on.
- Oh, my God. Who is it?
- Skyler.
- Skyler L or Skyler T?
- L.
- Who is that?
- Brendan.
Nice moves, UGIS.
I'm not UGIS, you fuck-butt.
Go fuck a dick till it comes, suck-face!
Jesus, I was just kidding.
You want me to finger you?
- Yeah.
- Just, uh... meet me back there.
Don't let anyone see you.
- Oh, my God.
- 'Na, come with me.
- It's all happening. It's all happening.
- No. No. Come with me.
OK.
Spooky in the dark.
Stop.
So, how do you wanna do this?
Wait, hold on. Sorry, sorry, sorry.
- I don't wanna do finger.
- What?
I don't wanna do finger.
OK, can... can you do it?
- Um... I'm like...
- Just, like, do it.
- I... I don't know. I'm not, um, ready.
- Yo?
- Um...
- Second base?
Both of you?
- Yeah.
- Cool.
- OK. Oh, my God.
Is that good... rotation pattern?
- You're both really hard-nipped.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
- Don't tell anyone.
- Yeah.
Wait at least a minute
before you come out.
OK.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
- Oh, my God!
Do you believe
that Sam is flymiamibro?
Oh, my God. It's so crazy.
But at least Alex didn't like
say no to you.
Yeah, I know, but then, like,
Brandt said that thing to me,
but then, like, I did the crazy thing,
and it felt, like, he was into it.
And then that's why he then asked, like...
Yeah.
- I know.
- Wait. Anna.
What?
- We both got felt up for the first time.
- I know. Second base.
- Together. Do you like him?
- I, like, love him.
- Wait, do you like him?
- No, he's kind of an asshole.
And he's best friends with Alex,
so it's just, like...
Something didn't happen today with Alex,
but it could tomorrow,
so I don't wanna complicate that.
- I feel, like, older.
- I know. Me, too.
I wonder when we'll get our periods.
Yeah, I know. Yeah.
Can I ask you a question?
- Uh-huh.
- But you promise not to get mad.
Yeah.
Why did you tell Heather
about your parents getting divorced
before me?
- I called you first.
- No, you didn't.
For your information, I did.
I called you first,
and you didn't pick up.
Then why didn't you leave a message?
- Maya...
- What?
That my parents are divorcing.
- Yeah.
- And you were so mad at me that night.
So I called Heather,
because she's the only person
in our grade with parents
that are divorced.
- Lie.
- What are you talking about?
Terra Newback.
- OK.
- Terra Newback's parents are divorced.
OK, I didn't think about that.
- I'm just saying, like...
- When you found out you were so weird
you didn't even care.
You didn't. You were, like...
'Cause it's a huge deal,
and I shouldn't have
found out that way. Like, are you serious?
It's not about you! Are you serious, Maya?
- It's not about you!
- OK, sorry!
It's about me,
because it's the saddest thing
that has ever happened to me.
No, it's fine, it's fine, it's fine. Stop!
Come here. I'm sorry.
I don't know what it's like.
I could never know, and I'm sorry.
- Parents are assholes.
- Yeah, they really are.
That's all really. It's fine.
Thanks.
Wait.
Oh, my God.
Do you wanna take a walk?
But, no, no, stop.
We're just gonna do it, like...
We're doing it.
Listen to that.
- Is that the wrong way?
- No, I think that's the right way.
Right?
I like it.
You have to inhale.
You're not inhaling.
Are you OK?
Do you wanna go inside?
No, let's just stay out here.