We haven't spent a lot
of time together.
It's just been moments here and there.
You know, if I'm alone with him,
I can tell him I'm not a slut,
and I'm sorry that
people know about us.
I just gotta get him alone.
I mean, obviously, he has trouble
expressing his emotions,
so if I'm alone with him,
he can really open up.
He doesn't like people
knowing his business.
‐ buh, buh, buh, buh,
buh, buh, buh, buh...
♪ Buh buh buh bubby dub dub dub dubby ♪
♪ buh buh buh bubby dub dub dub dubby ♪
If I was around, he'd notice me,
and I think the next stop
would be getting him
to ask me to be his girlfriend,
and then I get my first kiss.
And if I got my first kiss,
then he probably would ask me out.
I'd be his gf. Ha ha.
Oh, my god. Maybe we'd
go to the same college.
- We just need time alone.
- Hey, tj, come out.
But what if he forgets about me?
'Cause we haven't spent
a lot of time together.
It's just been moments here and there.
Mai.
‐ oh.
Hey.
Na...
I think I wanna join wrestling.
What?
‐ what?
‐ why do you keep looking over there?
‐ I'm not.
‐ you just‐‐why‐‐you only wanna join
wrestling 'cause Brandt's here.
‐ no, I‐‐stop saying his name so loud.
He's literally right there.
‐ I just said it‐‐like, not at all.
‐ I‐‐okay. Listen to me.
I didn't even know Brandt was in there.
‐ okay. ‐ I promise.
‐ okay.
You were staring right at him, but...
‐ yeah, 'cause I'm surprised
that I found him there.
I mean, like, honestly, I have
always wanted to wrestle.
‐ mai... ‐ what?
‐ girls wrote "desperate
slut" in my chorus folder.
‐ listen to me.
I hate girls right now, okay?
I'm over them.
I just like guys, you know?
'Cause guys don't gossip,
they don't talk about stuff
like that, they're not mean.
I just‐‐I just feel
like if we go in there,
we can just try it out.
And if you hate it, then we
don't ever have to go back.
Okay?
Just you, me...
And ten guys.
That's it.
‐ no.
No, mai. No.
‐ fine! Fine.
But I have an inner voice inside of me
that sounds a lot like my voice,
and it's telling me to
go in there and wrestle.
And I‐‐I can't ignore
it, so I have to go,
and I'd like you to join
or at least watch and be a good friend.
Stay low, Sam.
Lock your hands.
Slam him!
Hey, m‐‐mr. Brown.
I'd like to join wrestling, please.
Mm‐hmm.
Like, join the wrestling
team and stuff.
Your calves get any bigger,
you're gonna fall through the floor.
Thanks, coach.
‐ that's not something we do here.
Why, 'cause I'm a girl?
And I'm, like, stronger than
everyone here, probably.
Uh, yeah. You could get seriously hurt.
‐ well, um, I think it'd be
kind of messed up and illegal
if you didn't let me. ‐ levels, levels.
‐ and I could probably report it.
‐ okay. Fine.
You can shadow.
Go stand over there and watch.
‐ okay. Thanks, coach.
When you come in here, I
want you ready to wrestle.
‐ coach is making me shadow.
‐ dude, switch with me. ‐ sure.
‐ whenever Brandt touches his balls,
it means he wants a hand job.
‐ bro, shut up.
- Focus, focus, focus.
- Shut up.
So stupid.
‐ reach in and grab
all your rage inside
and let it out.
This is the place to do it,
not on your mom, not on your date.
Handle it like a man.
Destroy something privately,
or, better yet, on a team.
Nice!
Mr. - drive it! Drive it!
Drive it! Drive it! Drive it!
Nice, zablowski.
- Good job.
- ‐
‐ that was dope. ‐ thanks.
Sam cock‐block‐‐ so annoying.
Mr. brown, I'm, like, ready to wrestle.
I've learned a lot from shadowing.
‐ fine. Tj, partner up with Maya.
She says she's ready to wrestle.
‐ coach, I don't want to.
‐ come on, let's go.
‐ okay.
Now? Okay.
Stupid.
I wasn't ready. Like, what the hell?
Coach, can we stop?
I feel weird.
‐ fine, if he doesn't wanna wrestle,
I'll wrestle anybody else, honestly.
Anybody. Just raise your hand.
Like, I'm ready to frickin' go.
Brandt, whatever‐‐ if you want to.
Making her way to the ring,
Trish stratus!
‐ why don't you just,
like, talk to him, then?
‐ 'cause I don't wanna be like,
"hey, I'm terra newback.
"Let me just talk to
you for a long time
while you're bored as hell, Brandt."
Like... I'm not freakin' desperate.
I just want him to know I'm
hanging around and stuff.
‐ Maya, I don't wanna hear
about Brandt anymore.
‐ okay, well, that's fine
'cause I'm not talking to you.
I'm talking to Andy. ‐ who's that?
You serious?
You've never heard of Trish stratus?
‐ Trish stratus.
‐ her muscles are gross.
‐ yeah. No, she's slutty.
‐ yeah. ‐ yo, Trish is hot.
She's got my mad respect.
‐ hmm. Okay.
Oh, shit! ‐ okay, I can do that...
Easily.
‐ no, you can't, dummy. ‐ yes, I can!
Are you frickin' serious? Look at me.
‐ Maya, no offense but, like,
this b could take you.
‐ Doubt that.
‐ okay, that's what tj mulligan thought
before I freakin' kicked his ass.
- Did you see that?
- Oh, really?
Oh, what way am I gonna go, bitch?
Or, what, bitch? Come at me, bitch.
‐ your dad can't eat anything.
‐ guys, move. You're blocking the TV.
- ‐ he wants to destroy your ass.
- Oh, yeah?
Your dad eats soggy potatoes.
‐ and it makes him fart
on your face, Anna!
You're going down.
Put your money where your mouth is.
I'm putting my butt on your face.
You're cheating. You cannot do that.
‐ hey, yo, go, get her, Maya.
- Stop it.
- You're gonna die,
and I'm gonna be alive.
You're so frickin' weak, Maya.
No! Who's weak now, bitch?
I won.
Mom. The anna‐sthetizer
wants to put you to sleep.
Aah!
Oh, sorry.
But I just‐‐it's like that,
we were just wrestling,
and it was like, "I'm
the anna‐ihilator."
Anna.
I have a migraine from
doing energy work all day.
‐ well, I've been wrestling all day.
Like, don't make me flip you.
‐ could you take that
gross pillow to your dad?
He left it on my side of the house.
‐ yeah, that's fine, just
bring it to his room.
And quietly, please. ‐ okay.
‐ I can't take it.
Dad? ‐
dad? Mm‐hmm.
‐ um, do we have channel 151?
'Cause I want my Monday nights raw.
- ‐ what?
- Raw.
I want my Monday nights raw.
I‐‐I‐‐I think we get,
like, to channel one...
Hey, what's that pillow doing in here?
‐ mom just said to bring it to you
because you left it on
her side of the house.
‐ I told her already; She
can take it to the dump.
But you know your mother.
I mean, she does whatever she
wants, whenever she wants.
Don't leave the pillow.
I don't want it.
‐ okay.
I just never pictured
your mom and I's marriage going
quite this way, you know.
I've never been more in
love with anybody but her
my whole life.
‐ oh, yeah?
Yet you can still end up
sort of hating people anyway.
You know, if I'm the one that
ends up having to move out‐‐
even if I can only
afford an apartment‐‐
I'm not gonna resent it.
I just want you and
your mom to be happy.
Life can pummel you down, sweetie.
I hope you learn how to pummel back.
‐ take me now. The anna‐ihilator!
Get up... Get up!
Ooh! Ah!
You want some of this?
'Sup?
You're hot and strong.
You got my mad respect.
So my mom took me to kinko's...
Latest installment of weasels.
Which one do you think is better?
I think glossy really
makes it pop, you know?
‐ cool.
‐ hello? Hey, dude.
I was up until, like, 10:00 doing this.
Glossy or matte? ‐ no, either's great.
Okay? Yo, hey.
Ha.
What's up, zablowski?
Hey.
I'll see you later.
Yo, Brandt, wait up!
‐ glossy it is, then.
Mr. brown.
‐ Mr. brown.
‐ I just thought practice yesterday
was really inspiring. ‐ yeah.
‐ your team is well‐oiled,
and I was just honing in my skills
just about all night last night.
And... Do you wanna see them?
You don't have to.
But I'll just show you.
‐ Anna! ‐ and then you take it down
to brown town. ‐ stop.
‐ well, Maya, I guess you have someone
to fart around with at
practice, so that's something.
‐ well, um, I would love that,
except I already wrestled her a bunch.
I don't really feel like that's
challenging enough for me.
I was just thinking I could maybe
take on Brandt at the mock
meet on Friday or whatever.
‐ well, I already beat her
a bunch of times. Well‐‐
‐ Brandt's the... Best
wrestler in school.
Plus, you're different weight classes.
Oh, that's okay.
Maya and I can just partner up.
‐ Um...
Just out of curiosity;
how much weight do I have to gain
to be in Brandt's class?
‐ you'd have to gain at least
6 to 12 pounds in a week,
which is unhealthy at your
age and could mess you up.
So please don't try it.
‐ we won't.
We won't. ‐ we won't.
You're doing it for me,
but you're doing it for yourself too.
‐ clear, Maya, go! Clear, Maya, go!
Yeah, mai. You're bulking.
And you can't stop.
‐
‐ this is what it takes.
It's better with a little bit extra...
- ‐ no, little bitch.
‐ ha!
- ‐ sick.
You guys, I'm slamming
down the Mac and cheese.
Student can I have a bite of yours?
Um, here's the thing.
If you put peanut butter on the
hard‐boiled egg, that's the trick.
‐ what‐‐what trick?
How is that a trick?
‐ that is a trick. You get "yolked."
That's what, um, Trish stratus does.
She's hot. ‐ yeah, she is hot.
‐ and muscle weighs more than fat.
‐ Muscle weighs more than fat.
‐ that's what people don't realize.
‐ anyway, bro. Coach
brown got that new mat.
I'm gonna wrestle yo' ass.
So if you're gaining pounds‐‐lbs‐‐
that's not a bad thing.
‐ anyway, I'm gonna go hit the gym.
That was so funny
when you did that the other day.
You gonna eat all your peaches?
Oh, you don't say "bye" now?
Oh, my god, the protein's
going to her fat‐ass head.
I'm just kidding.
Take a picture. It'll
last longer, you guys.
Girls are so annoying, honestly.
Hammer fist!
Nailed him.
It's like I'm stalking you.
Just kidding.
Are you mad at me?
‐ why'd you join wrestling?
‐ 'cause I love ww.
‐
‐ I have for years, seriously.
I'm, like, sorry people
know about our three‐way.
‐ yeah.
‐ are you pissed?
‐ seriously, I'll do anything
I can to make it up to you.
Anything.
‐ yeah? Like what?
What?
If you take out the yolk of the egg...
You fill it with peanut butter,
it's truly like Reese's pieces.
How can you say "no"?
It tastes like my dog's ass.
Anna! You can't tell the difference.
I was gonna lift a tenner.
Be back soon.
Anna. Okay.
Come on, stop‐‐ Anna: I don't know why
- you keep doing this.
- Stop talking.
You want me to get jacked or not?
‐ literally, I was this close
to getting my first kiss with Brandt.
‐ how was I supposed to know that?
I didn't know that.
That's amazing, though.
Congratulations. ‐ no. Thank you.
It's fine, it's great. But
it doesn't keep happening
because you keep interrupting.
You keep walking in on us. Like...
‐ okay, well, I think that
you should learn to use
a lock on a door if you don't
want people to walk in.
‐ well, honestly, I don't
wanna creep him out.
So I'm just closing the door,
and I'm not locking it,
'cause I'm not crazy.
I know it's not personal,
but every time I'm alone
with him, you walk in.
And, honestly, like, Brandt and I‐‐
he doesn't really know
it yet, but, like,
we want time alone together.
'Cause if we don't have
time alone together,
then we're not gonna be
able to get to the point
- where I have my first kiss.
- Okay.
It's just like, you're
like, "Brandt..."
‐ shh.
‐ no, you're always like, "Brandt..."
‐ shh!
‐ it's just like, you're
like, "Brandt, Brandt,
"Brandt, Brandt, Brandt... ‐ stop.
Okay, okay, okay.
- ‐ "Brandt, Brandt, Brandt."
- Stop!
‐ and I'm like, "I
can't do it anymore."
‐ stop! ‐ Brandt!
- ‐ stop it, Anna!
- What?
‐ you're saying his name so lou‐‐
like, you're crazy, honestly.
- ‐ is that your hair?
- No.
- ‐ is that Brandt's locker?
- ‐ Maya.
- Stop saying his name.
‐ so, you and Maya in here, alone, huh?
So that‐‐that was like...
‐ she keeps following me around, man.
‐ well, you hooked up with
both her and kone, right?
Barely.
I mean, I don't wanna get
near their big‐ass bushes.
Their pussies smell like fish, dawg.
I mean, these fingers are clean.
Can't get that stank on me.
‐ big, smelly bush.
Oh, shit.
Anna and Maya are bsbs‐‐
big, smelly bushes.
Bro.
‐ tuna‐kone.
‐ yo, zablowski, you're funny, man.
Flyweight.
Middleweight. Middleweight.
Middleweight.
Jesus Christ, kone. Middleweight.
What did you do?
‐ Come on.
‐ another middleweight. ‐ really?
Does that mean I get to wrestle Brandt?
‐ you made weight, but the
pairs are set already.
First round is you versus blondie.
Whoever wins gets to wrestle
the winner of, uh, Brandt and Sam.
Who do you think's gonna win?
‐ I don't even know‐‐may‐‐
maybe‐‐maybe Sam.
Drive it! ‐ maybe.
Use your legs, Sam. Use your legs.
Nice, zablowski.
That was good.
That was great.
Get off.
Stop! No.
No.
Let me win, Anna.
‐ I need to get to Brandt. Stop.
‐ no.
Oh‐‐
I got you. Lookit...
You stay. You stay!
She's out.
‐ good match, bsb.
‐ where's Brandt?
‐ zablowski beat Brandt.
‐ you ready for this, bowl cut?
‐ don't call me that.
Fold him like a ham sandwich.
Is that all you got, bowl cut?
Stop calling me that!
I'm not calling you that.
I'm calling you "bowl cut."
Stop it!
- Freakin' asshole!
- Language.
Is that all you got?
Get off.
You're ruining everything right now.
I shouldn't even be wrestling you.
Well, at least I didn't
have a three‐way
in the closet with Brandt.
‐ yeah? You're just jealous
no one would go to the
frickin' closet with you.
Whoo‐whoo!
Whatever, bsb.
What?
At least I don't have a big, hairy bush
that smells like fish.
What?
‐ I didn't say that. Brandt
and the guys said that.
Come on, fight, let's go.
It's‐‐it's not a big deal.
It's just a‐‐it's just a joke.
Come on, let's go. ‐ no, stop!
‐ it's just a joke.
Match?
Here she is, star of the party.
There's my little athlete. ‐ ow.
‐ you win some, you lose some.
‐ ow, stop it.
‐ oh, no. I'm so sorry.
Did I hurt you? ‐ no.
‐ mai, sorry.
I just thought that's
what our buddies do.
You ok‐‐you okay?
‐ they're, um‐‐ ‐ what?
‐ they're calling us "big,
smelly bush" ‐‐bsb.
‐ wait. What?
Us?
Oh.
Oh, like, what is‐‐what is that?
Like‐‐ ‐ it's our pussies, na.
Our pussies.
That's what the guys
have been calling us.
They've been saying that our vaginas
are hairy and smell like fish.
‐ what? The guys?
Yeah. ‐ no, but they're my friends.
‐ yeah, well, they aren't anymore.
‐ you can't trust anyone! Ow!
‐ Anyone but you.
Our pussies!
It's okay.
Weasel‐shark.
Half‐weasel, half‐shark will
kill you and your family.
‐ yo, zablowski.
Yo, what up?
Yo, Sam.
What happened with
maya‐‐ you get a boner?
I said "bsb" to her,
and I probably shouldn't
have said that.
Hey, Sam, you coming?
Yeah, I'm coming. Hold up.
Ooh, ooh! Oh!
‐ wait. Did he just... Leave?
I thought we were gonna hang out.
‐ let's just go.
Wrestling's kind of gay.
One, two, three.
Oh, my god. Are you looking?
Yeah.
I don't know. It's kind of weird.
‐ I can't tell if it's,
like, big, but...
Can you smell anything?
‐ Yeah.
Do you?
‐ I think I smell something,
but it might not be that.
I don't know. 'Cause my
mom's cooking, so...
‐ I'm gonna try mixing
it with something.
‐ okay, yeah. Maybe I have something.
Ow!
‐ are you okay, Maya?
Oh, shit.
I think I burned it.
‐ be careful with it. Maybe
it doesn't like that.
‐
‐ I only have lip gloss.
‐ it feels like a little... Animal.
Hmm.
Meow. Meow!
Meow!
I need a little catnip.
Fly!
Are you still there?
- ‐ mm‐hmm.
- I'm gonna go.
‐ love you, bye.
Bye.
‐
Meow! Meow!
Fly!