ANNA: Last time on "Pen15"...
MAYA: Oh, my God,
Na, seventh grade!
It's gonna be so amazing.
‐ It's gonna be
really, really good.
‐ It's gonna be like
the best year of our lives.
‐ Maya, what the fuck
did you do to your hair?
‐ UGIS!
‐ Wait, what?
‐ It means ugliest girl
in school.
ANNA: Here comes Brandt.
MAYA: He's so cute.
‐ [whispering]
Is Alex looking at me?
MAYA: No.
‐ He'll probably
look at me later.
‐ I'm, uh, I'm Brendan.
I burned this for you.
ANNA: I guess he, like,
loves me or whatever.
‐ [whispering]
You have a boyfriend!
ANNA: He put his lips,
like,
all the way around mine
and sucked.
‐ Well, at least you've,
like, had your first kiss.
‐ But I wish that I hadn't.
MAYA: I feel, like, older.
ANNA: I know, me too.
MAYA: [crying] I don't
wanna do seventh grade.
ANNA: I'm not doing
seventh grade by myself.
‐ I don't know
how to say this.
Your dad and I,
we're getting a divorce.
ANNA: Everything's
just different,
and I just have
to break up with him.
[dial‐up connection beeps]
‐ Welcome.
MAYA: Oh, my God,
some random guy just
IM'd me again.
Flymiamibro22.
Hey, hottie.
What u look like.
I'm about to meet him
after school.
‐ You haven't met him
in person yet?
MAYA: Well, no,
we've talked on AIM.
JAFEER: He's probably
some warty old dude
and lives with his mother.
‐ It's me.
I'm Flymiamibro22.
‐ Oh, God.
[crying] Oh, my God.
SAM: Maya!
‐ Alex, will you dance
with me?
‐ No.
‐ What did you just
say to Alex?
GIRL: That's so messed up.
She took you
under her wing.
BRANDT: Nice moves, UGIS.
Want me to finger you?
‐ Yeah.
[Anna giggles]
‐ You have both
really hard nips.
I love you.
‐ And I love you too.
‐ Don't tell anyone.
‐ Yeah.
[pen scratching]
MAYA: Okay, and I'm adding
for you 2,000 kids.
ANNA: [chuckling] Oh, my God.
Maya, you're copying me.
MAYA: [scoffs] I'm doing it.
Okay, tell me when to stop.
ANNA: Stop.
‐ Okay.
12.
1, 2, 3, 4,
5, 6, 7, 8...
[whispering]
Okay, you're not with Brendan.
‐ Ugh. Oh, my God,
I don't want to be mean,
but he's like obsessed
with me, so...
MAYA: He's literally
obsessed with you.
‐ [laughs] I know.
‐ Okay, wait, okay, okay.
So you live in a mansion,
which is amazing.
‐ Yes!
‐ Ooh! A BMW 8 Series!
You have four kids.
You were literally one away
from getting Alex,
which is crazy.
‐ I just feel like I want him
a little bit less right now
'cause he dissed me
at the dance or whatever, so...
MAYA: Such an asshole.
Should we even, like,
go to Spencer's pool party?
Like, who's even
gonna be there?
Just gonna be Sam...
ANNA: Ugh.
‐ Gabe, Jafeer...I just‐‐
ANNA: Yeah.
Maybe we just stop in.
‐ Yeah, like for
literally a second.
Let's just, like, say hi,
be seen, and then like,
"Bye‐bye,
we got places to go."
‐ Just "bye‐bye."
MAYA: I don't know,
like, no offense,
but I think
we're too good for it.
Like, we're too good for it.
Mom, straight.
‐ Yeah, straight.
‐ Straight!
‐ It's straight.
KATHY: Okay, one, two,
three...
‐ [hisses]
[moans] Ohh...
ANNA: I just think
the real thing
is that we've changed.
MAYA: Yeah, it's so weird.
ANNA: Yeah.
MAYA: Yeah! Like,
after this weekend,
I think we are
on another level.
‐ Okay, my other ear.
‐ Okay.
ANNA: Yeah, I'm just keeping
my‐‐my options open.
MAYA: You should
keep your options open.
You're literally the hottest
I've ever seen you.
ANNA: [laughing] What?
MAYA: Anna, I swear!
ANNA: Yeah.
MAYA: You're at your hottest.
‐ Yeah.
MAYA: We, like, had Brandt J.
freaking like touch us up
at the same time.
Like, it's crazy.
‐ That's true.
‐ Aah!
[crying]
It burns, it burns!
Wait, you haven't told
anyone, though, right?
'Cause Brandt said not to.
‐ Oh, my God,
I swear to God, no.
‐ Wash it off now!
ANNA: Okay, so you have
a limo made of diamonds.
MAYA: Oh, my God, yes.
‐ And 2,000 babies.
‐ Wait‐‐what?
[laughing] No!
2,000?
That's crazy!
‐ You almost got Sam.
I just crossed out Sam.
‐ Oh, thank God.
He's a psycho.
ANNA: Oh...my...God.
‐ Stop!
Who?
‐ You got Brandt.
‐ No, I didn't!
No, I didn't!
Are you kidding?
Wait, are you kidding?
‐ No, you got Brandt.
‐ Aaah! I knew it!
ANNA: [laughing] Okay.
But you live in a shack
with 2,000 babies.
Do you wanna sign
for this life?
‐ Okay, I mean,
that's tough
because it's 2,000 babies
in a shack...
‐ Right.
MAYA: But, like, it just
means I get to kiss him
2,000 times so, yeah,
I sign for this life.
‐ Oh, you slut bag!
‐ Anna, shut up.
I'm gonna go, okay?
'Cause I wanna get ready.
ANNA: All right, love you.
MAYA: Okay, love you.
‐ Bye, bitch.
MAYA: Bye!
[phone bell dings]
THREE 6 MAFIA:
♪ Slob on my knob ♪
♪ Like corn on the cob ♪
[Maya rapping along]
♪ Juicy is my name ♪
♪ Sex is my game ♪
‐ ♪ Let's call the boys ♪
[Maya muttering]
BOTH: ♪ Let's run a train ♪
♪ Squeeze on my nuts,
lick on my butt ♪
‐ ♪ The natural curly hair ♪
‐ [muttering gibberish]
‐ ♪ Please don't touch ♪
‐ What's up, Brandt?
[chuckles]
Wait.
[laughs]
Stop.
You...
you've been thinking
about me?
I've‐‐I've been thinking
about you too.
Yeah.
[music continues
in background]
Sam, wait.
Literally back off!
Like, I'm in the middle
of something.
[softly] Sorry.
♪ ♪
That was really good.
Okay, now your turn.
Mm‐hmm.
Okay, now you both kiss.
[Will Smith's
Gettin' Jiggy wit It plays]
WILL: ♪ Whoo, uh, uh ♪
♪ Uh, uh ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Haha, haha ♪
♪ On your mark, ready,
set, let's go ♪
♪ Dance floor pro,
I know you know I go psycho ♪
♪ When my new joint hit ♪
♪ Just can't sit,
gotta get jiggy wit it ♪
♪ Ooh, that's it ♪
MAYA: Let's go.
‐ Maya, the door!
MAYA: Mom, get it.
‐ Hi, girls.
BOTH: Hi!
‐ They're all out back.
Hey, and no walking in the
house with wet suits on, okay?
BOTH: Kay.
‐ All right,
go have a good time.
BOTH: Thanks.
ISAAC: Yo, Mom.
Where's my hat?
ANNA: Do you have
the cigarettes?
MAYA: No. Damn it!
WILL: ♪ Make it feel
like foreplay ♪
♪ Yo, my cardio is infinite ♪
SPENCER:
Hey, what's up?
What are you guys doing?
[popping sounds]
‐ No, okay, don't‐‐
don't flick too hard, just‐‐
‐ The thing is, if I don't
flick too hard, then‐‐
‐ Okay‐‐
‐ It's not making any noise.
‐ Okay, so just find
the drum of your cheek
and just...
[popping]
Just flick casually.
‐ [snorting]
[popping continues]
SINGERS: ♪ Na, na, na, na, na,
na, na, na, na, na ♪
WILL: ♪ What? You want to ball
with the kid? ♪
[overlapping chatter]
♪ Watch your step,
you might fall ♪
♪ Trying to do what I did,
mama, uh, mama, uh,
come closer ♪
‐ So what I'm saying is,
weasels can technically kill
prey bigger than them.
Including rabbits
and squirrels.
‐ No, it's only a certain
species of weasels, though,
idiot.
‐ But it says here‐‐
‐ Don't look up.
Don't look up.
Maya just got here.
WILL: ♪ For the flavor
of a crowd‐pleaser ♪
KIMBERLY: Now, what did
I tell you?
No wet suits inside.
Now turn around and skedaddle.
WILL: ♪ Ride in my whips ♪
♪ South to the West
to the East to the North ♪
♪ Bought my hits and watch them
go off, a go off ♪
♪ In the winter or the ♪
SINGERS: ♪ Summertime ♪
WILL: ♪ I makes it hot,
gettin' jiggy wit 'em ♪
SINGERS: ♪ Na, na, na, na, na,
na, na ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
WILL: ♪ Gettin' jiggy wit it ♪
SINGERS: ♪ Na, na, na, na, na ♪
MAYA: I'm gonna
literally kill him‐‐
ANNA: Oh, sorry.
WILL: ♪ Getting jiggy wit it ♪
SINGERS: ♪ Na, na, na, na, na,
na, na ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
[song fades]
‐ Oh, my God, it's freezing.
‐ Do I look okay?
‐ Yeah.
You look so hot.
How 'bout me?
Does my bleach look okay?
‐ You look like a frickin'
hairless model.
‐ Okay.
MAYA: Oh...my God.
Na, Brendan
is staring at you.
Literally staring.
ANNA: Oh, my God.
I feel smothered by him.
MAYA: I know.
ANNA: Like, we are not a thing.
‐ Move on.
[sighs]
‐ There are, like,
no prospects here.
‐ No, I know.
Maybe we should just like stay
five minutes and then leave.
‐ That's all I thought
we were doing here.
‐ Okay, yeah.
Five minutes.
Just five minutes.
There's nobody here
that I wanna see.
‐ Yeah, for sure.
[indistinct chatter]
ANNA: Do you want me to go
say something to him?
‐ Who?
‐ Sam.
Oh, my God.
He keeps looking at you.
‐ No, he isn't. Stop.
ANNA: I'm gonna go
say something to him.
He needs to know...
‐ No.
‐ That you cannot be
someone else on AIM.
It's...illegal.
‐ Okay, fine, like
I don't want any drama,
but just like say
something to him and, like,
make it seem like
I don't care, 'cause I don't.
‐ Oh, I know you don't care.
‐ I don't care.
‐ [laughing] I know.
‐ So then just like
don't make any drama.
Just, like, do it.
Whatever.
‐ Okay.
‐ I think I should also
just go to Brendan, then.
It's time to move on.
‐ Okay.
‐ Like, honestly, it's time.
‐ Like, I'm‐‐I'm ready.
‐ Maya, no drama.
‐ Okay, no drama.
Sss...
ANNA: Hey.
What's up?
‐ What's up?
‐ Um, I just wanted to have
a mature conversation with you,
if you're all about it,
just address the
elephants in the basement.
‐ Sure.
ANNA: Um...
I just think
it's really messed up
that you pretended to be
somebody else on AIM.
Like...who does that?
And we just think
you're a tool.
So...[laughing]
just super weird because
you used to be our best friend.
‐ Well, there's two sides
to every story.
‐ Oh, yeah?
SAM: Yeah.
‐ So you're not
gonna apologize.
Are you seriously
not gonna apologize?
‐ Maybe I already did
apologize.
But she didn't
tell you that, though, right?
‐ Okay, maybe she did.
Maybe she did not.
All I know is that
she's my best friend
on God's green frickin' earth,
and I love her,
and she would never lie to me.
Ever.
‐ Well, we're kinda in
the middle of something here.
‐ Okay, what are you
in the middle of?
I'm sorry.
‐ Oh, it's‐‐it's weasels.
See, I made
this whole magazine.
JAFEER: Yeah.
GABE: See, uh, this is
one that I drew.
See, it's got buck teeth
and it's got‐‐
‐ You guys have to grow up.
Like, do you think that this is
gonna fly in eighth grade?
You have to be more mature.
[mockingly] Okay?
[hip‐hop music playing]
♪ ♪
‐ Sup?
‐ Hi.
‐ Um...[sighs]
basically, I'm here to tell you
that Anna's over you.
And she's just, like, done,
and she doesn't want
anything to do with you,
and you just gotta move on,
and I'm sorry.
‐ That's‐‐that's fine.
I'm dating Marissa H.
‐ Okay.
Cool.
So, what, you're like...
wait!
That's Icebox.
You're dating Icebox?
‐ [sighs]
She prefers Marissa H.
And just so you know,
she did not masturbate
with ice.
‐ Yeah, right.
BRENDAN: In fourth grade,
she was dared to put
an ice cube in her underwear.
[sighs] That rumor's
very heavily exaggerated.
‐ Whatever.
I've‐‐we can have different
opinions on what happened,
but, like, basically,
all you need to know
is you need to just, like,
end it with Anna.
‐ What?
‐ [mutters]
It's a good chat.
Sorry I...hurt your feelings.
Brendan's totally over you.
Completely.
‐ [laughs]
‐ He is, he's dating
Icebox now, I guess.
‐ What?
I didn't know that.
‐ Yeah.
‐ I didn't even know he was
into girls like that, so...
‐ But, like, she's a slut bag.
‐ Yeah, at least
I'm not like that.
‐ Anyway, it doesn't matter.
‐ Yeah, I don't care.
MAYA: It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter.
It's Icebox.
‐ I don't care!
‐ Like..."I put ice
in my vagina!"
[laughing]
‐ Wow.
‐ And she's a slut.
You have, like,
so many better options,
and it doesn't matter.
‐ Yeah, I do, I have a lot.
‐ You have so many options.
‐ So let's just leave.
‐ Yeah, let's go.
‐ Right?
‐ Let's go.
This place sucks.
‐ Blows.
‐ No‐‐stop, stop!
[dreamy orchestral music]
ANNA: Is that Brandt?
MAYA: No, no, no, no.
MAYA: Stop, stop, stop‐‐
ANNA: [whispering indistinctly]
BRANDT: Want me to finger you?
MAYA: Yeah.
BRANDT: You have both
really hard nips.
I love you.
MAYA: And I love you too.
Stop, stop, stop.
‐ Oh, my God, stop, stop!
‐ Stop, stop, Anna, stop it!
‐ [coughs]
Brandt‐‐
‐ Stop!
[wails]
ANNA: Go talk to him.
MAYA: No, you talk to him.
ANNA: Do you think
he's here for you?
‐ No!
‐ Go!
‐ Yes, I don't know!
Maybe.
ANNA: He is here for you.
MAYA: Okay, it's like, okay.
ANNA: Go now.
MAYA: Okay‐‐I don't know.
Okay, yeah.
BRANDT: Hey, what's up, man?
‐ What's up?
‐ He's here for Isaac.
‐ He's here for [murmurs].
ANNA: [whispering]
He's here for Isaac.
‐ He doesn't know you're here.
Ow.
Go.
MAYA: Oh, my God, okay.
‐ You're gonna get
your first frickin' kiss‐‐go.
‐ Okay, all right.
This is happening.
Let's just frickin' go.
‐ Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
Absolutely no coming
in the house while you're wet.
I told you guys that.
‐ We're not wet.
‐ Yes, you are.
I can still see a little
bit of water on you.
So dry off, okay?
‐ Sorry.
‐ We'll take care of it.
‐ There's a towel.
MAYA: Sorry!
‐ Thank you.
KIMBERLY: Thanks, girls.
‐ Sneak in, sneak in.
Come, come‐‐
‐ Nope.
Still too wet.
MAYA: Ow.
My God, she just like
[indistinct].
[indistinct background chatter]
Am I dry yet?
BRANDT: Cannonball!
‐ Cannonball!
[slow orchestral music]
♪ ♪
‐ Sup?
[sighs]
It's kinda funny
you're here right now.
‐ How?
‐ It's so lame here!
‐ It's my friend's party,
so...
it's kinda cool, actually.
‐ Yeah, it is pretty cool.
Haven't, like...
seen you since the dance
or like talked to you,
it seems like.
‐ We haven't, so...
that's probably why.
MAYA: Yeah.
Have you, um...
have you thought about
what happened on Friday?
‐ I don't‐‐what are you
talking about?
‐ [laughs]
You're being so funny
right now.
You know, like...
Brandt!
‐ The fuck.
MAYA: [giggles]
Sorry.
BRANDT: Jesus.
‐ Like when me, you, and‐‐
[whispering]
Anna, like, went
into the closet
and you, like, up and down,
in circles...
♪ ♪
Remember how hard‐nipped
I got‐‐
BRANDT: Nope.
That didn't happen.
‐ What‐‐
what do you mean,
it didn't happen?
That‐‐Brandt.
Are you f‐‐
‐ I'm so sorry.
[panting]
What's goin' on?
‐ He said it didn't happen.
‐ What didn't happen?
‐ Like I was just trying
to talk to Brandt
about how we did second base...
‐ Yeah.
‐ And he, like, didn't know
what I was talking about.
‐ [laughs] What?
‐ Like, he said
it didn't happen.
‐ That's a lie.
‐ I know, right?
Like, we did it.
‐ Yeah, he was freaking there.
That little freaking asshole.
‐ I mean, we did it, like,
we put the hands up and down
and we did the circle motions,
everything.
‐ All around.
‐ And like one hand
on your boob...
‐ It was.
‐ And one hand on my boob,
and he, like, didn't know
what I was talking about.
‐ And then there were
the circles.
Well, it happened.
Why would he lie about that?
‐ I don't know.
Do you think it's 'cause
he thinks I'm ugly
or something?
‐ No.
‐ Be honest.
‐ No!
If he does, he's a psychopath.
It happened, and I think
I know who saw.
Hey, Brendan.
Um, I just wanted
to touch base with you.
I know that...
little rude to you earlier.
And she can just be that way
sometimes.
But I heard that you're
going out with someone new,
and that's fine.
It doesn't change
what we had
or what we went through
together.
What?
‐ Say it.
‐ Um...
also, like, you know
how when, at the dance,
like when Brandt just
pulled us away from you?
We were‐‐we were, like,
grinding and then he was
like, "No! You come here."
Do you remember that?
'Cause he's saying
that that didn't happen.
I'm like, "It did."
It did, right, it did?
‐ I don't wanna get involved
with the drama, Anna.
I‐I've moved on.
I suggest you do too.
‐ Oh, yeah.
No, I know‐‐
[laughs]
To Marissa H.
I haven't heard one
bad thing about her, so...
‐ Me and her have a really
good rhythm with our kissing.
Peace.
[chair scraping lightly]
ANNA: Peace.
BRENDAN: Good‐bye.
‐ So somebody saw.
‐ No‐‐
‐ Someone here has seen,
so we need to go up
to people,
and we have to get proof.
‐ No, but Brandt said in
the closet not to tell anyone.
He's gonna get mad.
Please don't.
‐ Maya, who cares?
‐ Okay.
Okay, fine, okay.
We're gonna go up to people.
We're gonna get proof.
We're just not gonna
let them know everything
that happened.
We're not gonna
give it all away.
Me and Anna and Brandt
went into a closet.
Nothing happened.
Nothing happened, okay?
‐ I'll say a word,
and you tell me
the first thing that
comes to your mind‐‐loset.
Deposit.
‐ Do you know who Brandt is?
He was just showing up
a second ago.
He had a butt cut
and he was saying hello.
[attentive jazz music]
‐ Mafoset.
‐ And we basically
hooked up.
I'm not gonna say
what it rhymes with,
but it's second base.
‐ You ever seen
three people together?
‐ We touched each other,
but on the chest, nothing else.
And he said it didn't happen,
but it did.
‐ You ever been to a dance?
If you say no,
I don't believe you.
‐ You bitch‐‐I know
you're lying to me right now.
He went up and down,
and then he did circle motions.
And then he did circle motions.
Motion and a motion
on the boobies,
you know what I mean?
Maybe he does love me,
'cause he went up and down
a little bit more on me.
I knew it.
It's so weird.
But then he said "I love you,"
and then I said I love you back
and then now
he's taking it back,
and now I don't know what
it means,
and so I guess
I'm just asking you
[whispers]
'cause you're his best friend,
like what does that mean?
‐ You just told me, right?
You should go talk to Brandt.
‐ Ca‐can you tell me
where he is?
‐ He's in my room.
♪ ♪
ANNOUNCER: From the start,
clearly the aggressor
on Ziggo.
ANNOUNCER 2:
Ziggo spinning and spinning...
[continues indistinctly]
‐ ♪ On the back ♪
♪ Undercover ♪
♪ Got caught with the mother ♪
♪ Fuckin' with the rubber ♪
♪ Motherfu‐‐ ♪
Oh, hey.
[announcers continue
indistinctly]
ANNOUNCER:
There goes the ramp.
The wheel is off.
ANNOUNCER 2: Oh!
ANNOUNCER:
And now look at this.
[continues indistinctly]
‐ Sup?
Do you want me to leave?
Be honest.
It's like I'm stalking
you or something.
[laughing]
‐ Do not turn your back‐‐
Oh, he turned his back!
MAYA: Oh, whoa.
[announcers continue
shouting on TV]
[laughs]
‐ This is the final
slap of humiliation.
[announcers continue
indistinctly]
‐ Were you just joking
when you said that
the three‐way in the closet
didn't happen?
‐ What?
Yeah, whatever.
‐ So you're saying it happened.
‐ Yeah. Whatever.
‐ Okay.
ANNOUNCER: That is all Ziggo
just tearin' up that wood
like a beaver on speed.
‐ Wait, I'm, like, so sorry
I came up to you
in the pool like that.
I'm so lame.
BRANDT: Yeah.
Whatever.
It's cool.
I still think you're,
like, pretty or whatever.
So...could you move?
Cutie?
‐ Okay.
I'll sit down.
ANNOUNCER: I'm missing
a whole lot of examples.
But you fought hard
because you lost to this man
right here, Ziggo, Jonathan.
COMPETITOR: Yes, yes,
I know pretty well, so...
ANNOUNCER: It was impressive.
I want you guys, though,
to shake hands.
‐ Spencer saw it all,
motherfucker!
‐ Anna, he already said it.
Get out!
He just said it happened.
‐ Oh, you can get out.
He said it happened.
MAYA: Get out.
[door closes]
Sorry.
‐ Looks like it's just
the three of us again.
I'm really glad
that you guys have made up.
[girls giggling]
So you said that it
happened, hmm?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Yes, okay?
Just keep your mouth shut
about it.
I don't want that
getting out.
ANNA: Yeah.
‐ Okay.
‐ Nobody knows.
[both murmuring]
♪ But I didn't tell anybody ♪
♪ I didn't tell...♪
‐ Do you tell...
‐ ♪ But he just maybe
said I'm perfect ♪
‐ Guys, I'm trying to
watch this.
KIMBERLY: Who's in there?
MAYA: [whispering] Oh, my God.
‐ What are you doing
in Isaac's room
with the door closed?
And is that a wet bathing suit?
‐ Sorry.
KIMBERLY: Out.
ANNA: Sorry.
KIMBERLY: Yeah.
I'll just follow
the wet footprints, okay?
ANNOUNCER: And it's a wheel
of misfortune
spinning at 500 kilometers
an hour.
‐ [sniffles]
Nightmare is the most
aggressive BattleBot
in the competition and...
[whistle blows]
COACH: Around the cones,
people, around the cones!
MAYA: Wasn't Brandt
supposed to be in this class?
ANNA: You are, like,
so in love, it's crazy.
Why?
What's on that little mind?
‐ Nothing.
‐ ♪ What's on that
little mind? ♪
‐ Stop!
COACH: Kone, Ishii‐Peters!
You see everyone else
movin'?
What you doing?
‐ We are!
‐ We are.
‐ Keep it movin', let's go!
ANNA: Sorry.
‐ I was thinking
I would maybe put something
in Brandt's locker today
to, like, remind him of me,
but is that crazy?
‐ No, I love that.
‐ So desperate for
some water right now.
SINGER: ♪ La la la la la la ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ La la la la la la la
la la ♪
♪ La la la ♪
‐ Yeah, then go get some!
‐ I could get you some.
‐ Okay, he is like obsessed
with you‐‐I'm not kidding.
This is so crazy.
‐ ♪ Slutty‐dutty doo ♪
♪ Slutty‐dutty doo doo ♪
KID: Fucking slut.
‐ Slut?
JENNA: Anna, Maya.
Hey, can I talk to
you guys for a second?
Just...people have
been talking,
and I thought you should know.
‐ Okay, Jenna‐‐
‐ Okay, Maya, I'll get
to you in a second.
Anna, at the dance,
you were freaking
with everyone.
Uh, Maya, you too!
You were so desperate
trying to get Sam's attention
all night.
And then you had
a three‐some with Brandt,
and that's fucked up.
‐ [scoffs]
‐ What, uh...
a th‐‐
‐ That didn't happen.
Who did you hear that from?
ANNA: Yeah, where did you
hear that?
‐ 'Cause I didn't do that.
I didn't‐‐
‐ Yeah, I didn't do it either.
‐ We didn't do that.
‐ I mean, it's pretty obvious.
‐ That's absolutely nasty.
‐ Actually...
crazy, like crazy, crazy,
crazy!
You're crazy.
‐ Okay, yeah, whatever.
Just thought you should know
that everyone is saying
that you're desperate sluts.
And what makes me really sad
is that you've changed.
Like, a lot.
‐ Didn't happen.
‐ Yeah, Jenna, you don't
know what you're talking about!
ANNA: I don't like her.
‐ She's crazy.
Do you think I've changed?
‐ Who?
‐ Do you think I've changed.
‐ You?
‐ Yeah.
Do you?
‐ I think that we all
change all the time
and that that's just normal.
‐ So you do!
‐ I don't know how
to answer this.
‐ You think I've changed
like in a bad way.
‐ I don't know how
to answer this!
Mostly good, mostly good!
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ No, mostly good.
It's just when we were
at the dance, like...
you were, like, grinding
with just a few more
people than me,
and like when we were
having the fight,
I looked across the gym
and you were, like,
three‐waying kind of
with Gabe and Jafeer.
‐ But so you're saying I had
two three‐ways that night?
Did I have two threesomes
that night?
‐ You had two, but I had one.
Like, who am I?
‐ So then I'm more
of a slut than you!
That's what you're saying
right now!
‐ No, I'm saying if you are,
then I am too 'cause‐‐
‐ No, you haven't changed.
You just did one.
‐ No, I'm just saying
that we‐‐
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ I get why people
are saying this about us.
‐ So we're desperate sluts.
Great.
And now everyone knows
and Brandt's gonna be so mad.
He's gonna hate us.
‐ Brandt's a slut too.
Ha.
‐ No, he's just a player.
‐ Oh, yeah.
MAYA: He's just a player.
[soft, pensive music]
♪ ♪