Last time on "pen15"...
Oh, my god, na, seventh grade!
It's gonna be so amazing.
‐ it's gonna be really, really good.
‐ it's gonna be like the
best year of our lives.
‐ Maya, what the fuck did
you do to your hair?
‐ ugis! ‐ ugis!
‐ wait, what? ‐ it means
ugliest girl in school.
- Here comes Brandt.
- He's so cute.
‐ ls Alex looking at me?
No. ‐ he'll probably look at me later.
‐ I'm, uh, I'm Brendan.
I burned this for you.
I guess he, like, loves me or whatever.
‐ You have a boyfriend!
He put his lips, like,
all the way around mine and sucked.
‐ well, at least you've,
like, had your first kiss.
‐ but I wish that I hadn't.
- I feel, like, older.
- I know, me too.
I don't wanna do seventh grade.
I'm not doing seventh grade by myself.
‐ I don't know how to say this.
Your dad and I, we're
getting a divorce.
Everything's just different,
and I just have to break up with him.
‐ welcome.
Oh, my god, some random
guy just im'd me again.
Flymiamibro22.
Hey, hottie. What u look like.
I'm about to meet him after school.
‐ you haven't met him in person yet?
Well, no, we've talked on aim.
He's probably some warty old dude
and lives with his mother.
‐ it's me.
I'm flymiamibro22.
‐ oh, god. Oh, my god. Maya!
‐ Alex, will you dance with me?
‐ no.
‐ what did you just say to Alex?
That's so messed up.
She took you under her wing.
Nice moves, ugis.
Want me to finger you?
‐ yeah.
‐ you have both really hard nips.
I love you.
‐ and I love you too.
‐ don't tell anyone. ‐ yeah.
Okay, and I'm adding
for you 2,000 kids.
Oh, my god.
- Maya, you're copying me.
- I'm doing it.
Okay, tell me when to stop.
Stop.
‐ okay. 12.
1, 2, 3, 4,
5, 6, 7, 8...
Okay, you're not with Brendan.
‐ ugh. Oh, my god, I
don't want to be mean,
but he's like obsessed with me, so...
He's literally
- obsessed with you.
- ‐ I know.
‐ okay, wait, okay, okay.
So you live in a mansion,
which is amazing.
‐ yes! ‐ ooh! A BMW 8 series!
You have four kids.
You were literally one
away from getting Alex,
which is crazy.
‐ I just feel like I want him
a little bit less right now
'cause he dissed me at the
dance or whatever, so...
Such an asshole.
Should we even, like, go
to Spencer's pool party?
Like, who's even gonna be there?
- Just gonna be Sam...
- Ugh.
‐ Gabe, jafeer... I just‐‐ Anna: Yeah.
Maybe we just stop in.
‐ yeah, like for literally a second.
Let's just, like, say hi,
be seen, and then like,
"bye‐bye, we got places to go."
‐ just "bye‐bye." I don't
know, like, no offense,
but I think we're too good for it.
Like, we're too good for it.
Mom, straight. ‐ yeah, straight.
‐ straight! ‐ it's straight.
Okay, one, two, three...
‐ Ohh...
I just think the real thing
is that we've changed.
- Yeah, it's so weird.
- Yeah.
Yeah! Like, after this weekend,
I think we are on another level.
‐ okay, my other ear. ‐ okay.
Yeah, I'm just keeping
my‐‐my options open.
You should keep your options open.
You're literally the hottest
I've ever seen you. What?
- Anna, I swear!
- Yeah.
You're at your hottest. ‐ yeah.
We, like, had Brandt j.
Freaking like touch us
up at the same time.
Like, it's crazy. ‐ that's true.
‐ aah!
It burns, it burns!
Wait, you haven't told
anyone, though, right?
'Cause Brandt said not to.
‐ oh, my god, I swear to god, no.
‐ wash it off now!
Okay, so you have a
limo made of diamonds.
Oh, my god, yes. ‐ and 2,000 babies.
‐ wait‐‐what? No!
2,000?
That's crazy! ‐ you almost got Sam.
I just crossed out Sam.
‐ oh, thank god. He's a psycho.
Oh... My... God.
‐ stop! Who?
‐ you got Brandt.
‐ no, I didn't! No, I didn't!
Are you kidding?
Wait, are you kidding?
‐ no, you got Brandt.
‐ aaah! I knew it! Okay.
But you live in a shack
with 2,000 babies.
Do you wanna sign for this life?
‐ okay, I mean,
that's tough because it's
2,000 babies in a shack...
‐ right. But, like, it just
means I get to kiss him
2,000 times so, yeah,
I sign for this life.
‐ oh, you slut bag!
‐ Anna, shut up. I'm gonna go, okay?
- 'Cause I wanna get ready.
- All right, love you.
Okay, love you. ‐ bye, bitch.
Bye!
‐
‐ ‐
‐ what's up, Brandt?
Wait.
Stop. You...
You've been thinking about me?
I've‐‐I've been thinking about you too.
Yeah.
Sam, wait. Literally back off!
Like, I'm in the middle of something.
Sorry.
That was really good.
Okay, now your turn.
Mm‐hmm.
Okay, now you both kiss.
Let's go.
‐ Maya, the door!
Mom, get it.
- ‐ hi, girls.
- Hi!
‐ they're all out back.
Hey, and no walking in the
house with wet suits on, okay?
Kay. ‐ all right, go have a good time.
- Thanks.
- Yo, mom.
Where's my hat? Do you
have the cigarettes?
No. Damn it!
♪ Make it feel like foreplay ♪
- Hey, what's up?
- What are you guys doing?
‐ no, okay, don't‐‐ don't
flick too hard, just‐‐
‐ the thing is, if I don't
flick too hard, then‐‐
‐ okay‐‐ ‐ it's not making any noise.
‐ okay, so just find
the drum of your cheek
and just...
Just flick casually. ‐
♪ na, na, na, na, na,
na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ what? You want to
ball with the kid? ♪
♪ Watch your step, you might fall ♪
‐ so what I'm saying is, weasels can
technically kill prey bigger than them.
Including rabbits and squirrels.
‐ no, it's only a certain species
of weasels, though, idiot.
‐ but it says here‐‐ ‐ don't look up.
Don't look up.
Maya just got here.
♪ For the flavor of a crowd‐pleaser ♪
Now, what did I tell you?
No wet suits inside.
Now turn around and skedaddle.
♪ I makes it hot,
gettin' jiggy wit 'em ♪
♪ na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
I'm gonna literally kill him‐‐
- oh, sorry.
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
‐ oh, my god, it's freezing.
‐ do I look okay?
‐ yeah. You look so hot.
How 'bout me? Does my bleach look okay?
‐ you look like a frickin'
hairless model. ‐ okay.
Oh... My god.
Na, Brendan is staring at you.
Literally staring. Oh, my god.
I feel smothered by him.
- I know.
- Like, we are not a thing.
‐ move on.
‐ there are, like, no prospects here.
‐ no, I know.
Maybe we should just like stay
five minutes and then leave.
‐ that's all I thought
we were doing here.
‐ okay, yeah. Five minutes.
Just five minutes.
There's nobody here that I wanna see.
‐ yeah, for sure.
Do you want me to go
say something to him?
‐ who? ‐ Sam.
Oh, my god.
He keeps looking at you.
‐ no, he isn't. Stop.
I'm gonna go say something to him.
He needs to know... ‐ no.
‐ that you cannot be someone
else on aim. It's... Illegal.
‐ okay, fine, like I
don't want any drama,
but just like say something
to him and, like,
make it seem like I don't
care, 'cause I don't.
‐ oh, I know you don't care.
- ‐ I don't care.
- ‐ I know.
‐ so then just like
don't make any drama.
Just, like, do it. Whatever. ‐ okay.
‐ I think I should also
just go to Brendan, then.
It's time to move on.
‐ okay. ‐ like, honestly, it's time.
‐ okay. ‐ like, I'm‐‐I'm ready.
‐ Maya, no drama. ‐ okay, no drama.
Sss...
Hey.
What's up?
‐ what's up?
‐ um, I just wanted to have a
mature conversation with you,
if you're all about
it, just address the
elephants in the basement.
‐ sure.
Um...
I just think it's really messed up
that you pretended to be
somebody else on aim.
Like... Who does that?
And we just think you're a tool.
So... Just super weird because
you used to be our best friend.
‐ well, there's two
sides to every story.
‐ oh, yeah?
Yeah. ‐ so you're not gonna apologize.
Are you seriously not gonna apologize?
‐ maybe I already did apologize.
But she didn't tell you
that, though, right?
‐ okay, maybe she did.
Maybe she did not.
All I know is that she's my best friend
on god's green frickin' earth,
and I love her, and she
would never lie to me.
Ever.
‐ well, we're kinda in the
middle of something here.
‐ okay, what are you in the middle of?
I'm sorry.
‐ oh, it's‐‐it's weasels.
See, I made this whole magazine.
Yeah. See, uh, this is one that I drew.
See, it's got buck teeth and it's got‐‐
‐ you guys have to grow up.
Like, do you think that this
is gonna fly in eighth grade?
You have to be more mature.
Okay?
‐ sup?
‐ hi. ‐ um...
Basically, I'm here to tell
you that Anna's over you.
And she's just, like, done, and she
doesn't want anything to do with you,
and you just gotta move
on, and I'm sorry.
‐ that's‐‐that's fine.
I'm dating Marissa h.
‐ okay. Cool.
So, what, you're like... Wait!
That's icebox. You're dating icebox?
‐ She prefers Marissa h.
And just so you know, she did
not masturbate with ice.
- ‐ yeah, right.
- In fourth grade,
she was dared to put an ice
cube in her underwear.
That rumor's very heavily exaggerated.
‐ whatever. I've‐‐we can have
different opinions on what happened,
but, like, basically,
all you need to know
is you need to just,
like, end it with Anna.
‐ what?
‐ lt's a good chat.
Sorry I... Hurt your feelings.
Brendan's totally over you.
Completely. ‐
‐ he is, he's dating
icebox now, I guess.
‐ what?
I didn't know that. ‐ yeah.
‐ I didn't even know he was
into girls like that, so...
‐ but, like, she's a slut bag.
‐ yeah, at least I'm not like that.
‐ anyway, it doesn't matter.
- ‐ yeah, I don't care.
- It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter. It's icebox.
‐ I don't care!
‐ like..."I put ice in my vagina!"
‐ wow. ‐ and she's a slut.
You have, like, so many better
options, and it doesn't matter.
‐ yeah, I do, I have a lot.
‐ you have so many options.
‐ so let's just leave.
‐ yeah, let's go. ‐ right?
‐ let's go. This place sucks.
‐ blows.
‐ no‐‐stop, stop!
- Is that Brandt?
- No, no, no, no.
Stop, stop, stop‐‐ Anna:
- Want me to finger you?
- Yeah.
You have both really hard nips.
- I love you.
- And I love you too.
Stop, stop, stop.
‐ oh, my god, stop, stop! ‐
stop, stop, Anna, stop it!
‐ Brandt‐‐
‐ stop!
- Go talk to him.
- No, you talk to him.
Do you think he's here for you? ‐ no!
‐ go! ‐ yes, I don't know! Maybe.
- He is here for you.
- Okay, it's like, okay.
Go now. Okay‐‐I don't know. Okay, yeah.
Hey, what's up, man? ‐ what's up?
- ‐ he's here for Isaac.
- ‐ he's here for.
He's here for Isaac.
‐ he doesn't know you're here. Ow.
- Go.
- Oh, my god, okay.
‐ you're gonna get your
first frickin' kiss‐‐go.
‐ okay, all right. This is happening.
Let's just frickin' go.
‐ whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Absolutely no coming in the
house while you're wet.
I told you guys that.
‐ we're not wet. ‐ yes, you are.
I can still see a little
bit of water on you.
So dry off, okay?
‐ sorry. ‐ we'll take care of it.
‐ there's a towel.
Sorry! ‐ thank you.
Thanks, girls.
‐ sneak in, sneak in. Come, come‐‐
‐ nope.
Still too wet.
Ow.
My god, she just like.
- Am I dry yet?
- Cannonball!
‐ cannonball!
‐ sup?
It's kinda funny you're here right now.
‐ how?
‐ it's so lame here!
‐ it's my friend's party, so...
It's kinda cool, actually.
‐ yeah, it is pretty cool.
Haven't, like...
Seen you since the dance
or like talked to you, it seems like.
‐ we haven't, so...
That's probably why.
Yeah.
Have you, um...
Have you thought about
what happened on Friday?
‐ I don't‐‐what are you talking about?
‐
You're being so funny right now.
You know, like...
Brandt!
‐ the fuck.
- Sorry.
- Jesus.
‐ like when me, you, and‐‐
Anna, like, went
into the closet
and you, like, up and
down, in circles...
Remember how hard‐nipped I got‐‐
nope. That didn't happen.
‐ what‐‐
what do you mean, it didn't happen?
That‐‐brandt.
Are you f‐‐
‐ I'm so sorry.
What's goin' on?
‐ he said it didn't happen.
‐ what didn't happen?
‐ like I was just trying
to talk to Brandt
about how we did second base... ‐ yeah.
‐ and he, like, didn't know
what I was talking about.
‐ what?
‐ like, he said it didn't happen.
‐ that's a lie. ‐ I know, right?
Like, we did it. ‐ yeah,
he was freaking there.
That little freaking asshole. ‐ I mean, we
did it, like, we put the hands up and down
and we did the circle motions,
everything. ‐ all around.
‐ and like one hand on your boob...
‐ it was.
‐ and one hand on my boob,
and he, like, didn't know
what I was talking about. ‐ and
then there were the circles.
Well, it happened. Why
would he lie about that?
‐ I don't know.
Do you think it's 'cause he
thinks I'm ugly or something?
‐ no.
‐ be honest.
‐ no!
If he does, he's a psychopath.
It happened, and I
think I know who saw.
Hey, Brendan.
Um, I just wanted to
touch base with you.
I know that...
Little rude to you earlier.
And she can just be that way sometimes.
But I heard that you're
going out with someone
new, and that's fine.
It doesn't change what we had
or what we went through together.
What? ‐ say it.
‐ um...
Also, like, you know how
when, at the dance,
like when Brandt just
pulled us away from you?
We were‐‐we were, like, grinding and
then he was like, "no! You come here."
Do you remember that?
'Cause he's saying that that
didn't happen. I'm like, "it did."
It did, right, it did?
‐ I don't wanna get involved
with the drama, Anna.
I‐I've moved on. I suggest you do too.
‐ oh, yeah. No, I know‐‐
to Marissa h. I haven't heard
one bad thing about her, so...
‐ me and her have a really
good rhythm with our kissing.
Peace.
Good‐bye.
‐ so somebody saw. ‐ no‐‐
‐ someone here has seen, so
we need to go up to people,
and we have to get proof.
‐ no, but Brandt said in the
closet not to tell anyone.
He's gonna get mad. Please don't.
‐ Maya, who cares?
‐ okay. Okay, fine, okay.
We're gonna go up to people.
We're gonna get proof.
We're just not gonna let them
know everything that happened.
We're not gonna give it all away.
Me and Anna and Brandt
went into a closet.
Nothing happened.
Nothing happened, okay?
‐ I'll say a word, and you tell me
the first thing that comes
to your mind‐‐loset.
Deposit.
‐ do you know who Brandt is? He
was just showing up a second ago.
He had a butt cut and
he was saying hello.
‐ mafoset.
‐ and we basically hooked up.
I'm not gonna say what it rhymes with,
but it's second base.
‐ you ever seen three people together?
‐ we touched each other, but
on the chest, nothing else.
And he said it didn't
happen, but it did.
‐ you ever been to a dance? If
you say no, I don't believe you.
‐ you bitch‐‐I know you're
lying to me right now.
He went up and down, and
then he did circle motions.
And then he did circle motions.
Motion and a motion on the
boobies, you know what I mean?
Maybe he does love me, 'cause he went
up and down a little bit more on me.
I knew it. It's so weird.
But then he said "I love you,"
and then I said I love you back
and then now he's taking it back,
and now I don't know what it means,
and so I guess I'm just asking you
'cause you're his best friend,
like what does that mean?
‐ you just told me, right?
You should go talk to Brandt.
‐ ca‐can you tell me where he is?
‐ he's in my room.
From the start,
clearly the aggressor on ziggo.
Ziggo spinning and spinning...
‐
Oh, hey.
There goes the ramp. The wheel is off.
Oh! And now look at this.
‐ sup?
Do you want me to leave? Be honest.
It's like I'm stalking
you or something.
‐ do not turn your back‐‐
oh, he turned his back!
Oh, whoa.
‐ this is the final
slap of humiliation.
‐ were you just joking when you said
that the three‐way in the closet
didn't happen?
‐ what? Yeah, whatever.
‐ so you're saying it happened.
‐ yeah. Whatever.
- ‐ okay.
- That is all ziggo
just tearin' up that wood
like a beaver on speed.
‐ wait, I'm, like, so
sorry I came up to you
in the pool like that.
- I'm so lame.
- Yeah.
Whatever. It's cool.
I still think you're,
like, pretty or whatever.
So... Could you move? Cutie?
‐ okay.
I'll sit down.
I'm missing a whole lot of examples.
But you fought hard because you lost to
this man right here, ziggo, Jonathan.
Yes, yes, I know pretty well, so...
It was impressive. I want you
guys, though, to shake hands.
‐ Spencer saw it all, motherfucker!
‐ Anna, he already said it. Get out!
He just said it happened.
‐ oh, you can get out.
He said it happened.
Get out.
Sorry.
‐ looks like it's just
the three of us again.
I'm really glad that
you guys have made up.
So you said that it happened, hmm?
‐ yeah. ‐ yes, okay?
Just keep your mouth shut about it.
I don't want that getting out.
Yeah. ‐ okay.
‐ nobody knows.
‐ do you tell...
‐ ♪ but he just maybe
said I'm perfect ♪
‐ guys, I'm trying to watch this.
Who's in there?
Oh, my god.
‐ what are you doing in Isaac's
room with the door closed?
And is that a wet bathing suit?
‐ sorry. ‐ sorry.
Out.
- Sorry.
- Yeah.
I'll just follow the
wet footprints, okay?
And it's a wheel of misfortune
- spinning at 500 kilometers an hour.
-  ‐
nightmare is the most
aggressive battlebot
in the competition and...
Around the cones, people,
around the cones!
Wasn't Brandt supposed
to be in this class?
You are, like, so in love, it's crazy.
Why? What's on that little mind?
‐ nothing.
‐ ♪ what's on that little mind? ♪
- ‐ stop!
- Kone, ishii‐peters!
You see everyone else movin'?
What you doing?
‐ we are! ‐ we are.
- ‐ keep it movin', let's go!
- Sorry.
‐ I was thinking I would
maybe put something
in Brandt's locker today to, like,
remind him of me, but is that crazy?
‐ no, I love that. ‐ so desperate
for some water right now.
‐ yeah, then go get some!
‐ I could get you some.
‐ okay, he is like obsessed
with you‐‐I'm not kidding.
- This is so crazy.
- ‐
fucking slut.
- ‐ slut?
- Anna, Maya.
Hey, can I talk to you
guys for a second?
Just... People have been talking,
and I thought you should know.
‐ okay, jenna‐‐ ‐ okay, Maya,
I'll get to you in a second.
Anna, at the dance, you were
freaking with everyone.
Uh, Maya, you too!
You were so desperate trying to
get Sam's attention all night.
And then you had a
three‐some with Brandt,
and that's fucked up.
‐ ‐ what, uh...
A th‐‐ ‐ that didn't happen.
Who did you hear that from?
Yeah, where did you hear that?
‐ 'cause I didn't do that. I didn't‐‐
‐ yeah, I didn't do it either.
‐ we didn't do that.
‐ I mean, it's pretty obvious.
‐ that's absolutely nasty.
‐ actually...
Crazy, like crazy, crazy, crazy!
You're crazy. ‐ okay, yeah, whatever.
Just thought you should know
that everyone is saying
that you're desperate sluts.
And what makes me really sad
is that you've changed.
Like, a lot.
‐ didn't happen.
‐ yeah, Jenna, you don't know
what you're talking about!
I don't like her.
‐ she's crazy.
Do you think I've changed?
‐ who? ‐ do you think I've changed.
‐ you? ‐ yeah.
Do you?
‐ I think that we all
change all the time
and that that's just normal.
‐ so you do! ‐ I don't
know how to answer this.
‐ you think I've changed
like in a bad way.
‐ I don't know how to answer this!
Mostly good, mostly good!
‐ oh, my god. ‐ no, mostly good.
It's just when we were
at the dance, like...
You were, like, grinding with
just a few more people than me,
and like when we were having the
fight, I looked across the gym
and you were, like, three‐waying
kind of with Gabe and jafeer.
‐ but so you're saying I had
two three‐ways that night?
Did I have two threesomes that night?
‐ you had two, but I had one.
Like, who am I? ‐ so then I'm
more of a slut than you!
That's what you're saying right now!
‐ no, I'm saying if you
are, then I am too 'cause‐‐
‐ no, you haven't changed.
You just did one.
‐ no, I'm just saying
that we‐‐ ‐ oh, my god.
‐ I get why people are
saying this about us.
‐ so we're desperate sluts.
Great.
And now everyone knows and
Brandt's gonna be so mad.
He's gonna hate us.
‐ Brandt's a slut too. Ha.
‐ no, he's just a player.
‐ oh, yeah.
He's just a player.