Taking a nap!
No one bother me!
Boobs.
‐ Hi, Ume.
I
I am hiding
The you I show to you
Is just a lie
You take what you want
You get what you take
-  Lie
-  So high, high, high
‐ I didn't do that.
What'd sh‐‐what'd she say?
‐ She said she wants
to give you this pin.
It's from the plane.
‐ The pin?
‐ Mm‐hmm.
Oh, yeah, I get it.
Thought she was saying
something else.
Um, Shuji, can you ask her
if she wants to play with me?
‐ Why don't you ask her?
Ume‐‐
What?
What was that?
‐ Did you just say she's coming
to school with me?
I'm with you, Maya.
I‐‐most of this is goin' right
over my head.
‐ I'm following most
of everything they're saying.
‐ I do know, Ume,
that you look...
about the same as you were
when you were this big.
You're so cute.
‐ Me too, right, Dad?
I look the same
as that picture?
Yeah, you look the same.
Except you're, like, way bigger
and you have a mustache now.
‐ Shut up!
‐ Maya,
you are a beautiful woman.
‐ Dad, don't call me that.
‐ Well, you are.
‐ I'm not a woman, I'm a girl.
Like, I'm a kid.
I'm one year older than her.
‐ Well,
you're a little more mature.
‐ That's so gross and weird
for you to say, like,
I'm a little kid.
‐ Fuck!
‐ Dad.
‐ What?
‐ So good.
‐ The TV!
Come on‐‐
‐ Okay, well, let me try.
Give me‐‐
that's not the right one.
Did you try pressing the‐‐
‐ I bet the one that
your mother kept is working.
Just sayin'.
‐ Okay, well, we don't need
to watch something,
like, we can just...
chat.
Right? Really.
‐ Yeah, yeah.
‐ Um‐‐
oh, my God, congratulations
on your new place.
‐ Mm.
‐ Cheers.
‐ It's okay.
‐ It's really good.
‐ Yeah, I don't know how long
it's gonna take me to unpack.
‐ Well, I'll help you.
I'll help you make it feel
like your home.
‐ Does that mean that...
you know, you're gonna
pick my place full‐time?
'Cause that would
be really fun.
‐ I'm thinking about it.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Yeah,
I think it would be really fun.
‐ Oh, great.
‐ I really miss you.
Oh.
‐ I hoped that you would.
‐ You stay there.
I'll get it.
- Hello?
- Hey, Na, it's Mai.
‐ It's Maya.
‐ Na!
‐ Hi.
Are you at your dad's place?
‐ Yeah. It's great.
‐ Oh, my God. Amazing.
‐ No, I love it here.
It's so beautiful.
So you're never
gonna believe it,
but Ume is here from Japan.
‐ Are you serious?
‐ Yeah.
‐ "Oomi"‐‐Ume?
‐ Anna, it's Ume.
‐ No, that's what I meant.
Yeah, I can't wait to meet her.
Well, can you meet her now?
‐ I would love to, let me ask.
'Cause it's awkward
just the two of us.
‐ Hey, Dad.
Um, do you mind
if I go to Maya's?
‐ Uh, it's a school night.
‐ No, I know,
but it's a special occasion
'cause her friend's here
from Japan.
‐ Oh.
‐ Please?
‐ Yeah.
Yeah.
No, go ahead and go.
‐ Hi, he said I can go
and to have fun.
What? Okay, come right now!
- Okay, I'll see you soon.
- Bye.
‐ I've heard so much about you
from Maya,
and I'm glad that you're here.
‐ She doesn't speak English.
Like,
she can't understand that.
‐ Sayonara.
Na, that means bye.
‐ Oh, sorry.
‐ No.
‐ Okay‐‐oh, okay, okay.
I'm gonna translate for you.
‐ I always forget, like,
my best friend's fluent.
‐ Like, pretty fluent.
It's just 'cause
my mom's Japanese,
but, like, not fully.
‐ Don't downplay yourself.
‐ Isn't she, like, so cute?
I feel like we could pass
as twins, look.
Oh, yeah.
Or she's, like,
your baby sister.
‐ Mm.
Just 'cause her skin's
paler and she looks more, like,
innocent and, like,
she's shorter and, like‐‐
like, that stuff.
‐ Like me, like my‐‐
my skin and stuff.
‐ Yeah,
but hers is more porcelain‐y.
‐ Okay, thanks.
‐ No, not in a bad way.
Not in a bad way.
You both are beautiful.
She keeps staring at you.
‐ What?
‐ Nothing.
That's so mean, Ume.
That's not true, like‐‐
she said your nose is big.
Oh, that's okay.
I'm sorry. That‐‐ Ume‐‐
‐ I feel like ours
are the same size though.
Do you wanna just tell her
that really quick?
Uh‐‐yeah! Yeah!
It's the same, like‐‐ she gets it.
‐ Yeah, we don't...
‐ Sh‐‐
‐ Play‐‐it's a card game
we used to play.
- We don't wanna do that.
- Speedo?
You know, so I think‐‐
‐ What does "baba" mean?
‐ No to the cards.
Let's just, like,
play pretend or something.
Mm, got to get
my mash not lumpy,
'cause my angel doesn't
like lumpy mash.
‐ I know my angel,
and she likes a lumpy mash.
Yum, yum, yum!
It's a lumpy mash.
‐ Okay, well,
Steve likes a not lumpy mash,
just so you know.
‐ Oh, my God, Na.
You just said Steve.
‐ Oh, my God!
Wait.
‐ No, I didn't mean to do that.
I didn't even mean
to say Steve.
Like, that's my husband.
‐ Has he called you yet?
‐ Maybe, I don't know.
I gave him my mom's number,
and I'm at my dad's, so‐‐
‐ Well, wouldn't your mom tell
you if he called or something?
‐ Probably, yeah.
‐ Mama.
Okay, not now, Ume, like‐‐
Um, you guys have made out so
much, like, he's gonna call.
Hope so.
What's the guy
that likes me again,
what's his name?
- The high schooler?
- Derek.
School.
‐ Squirrel?
‐ No.
‐ Okay, squirrel.
‐ She's trying to‐‐
No, Anna,
she's trying to say school.
Like, sometimes words
come out differently
when you're not from here.
‐ Right.
‐ But she was just saying
"sker."
Anna, don't laugh!
That's mean!
That's, like,
how it's gonna
come out tomorrow.
She's gonna be like "sker."
They're gonna destroy her.
Oh, my God.
‐ They're gonna be,
like, so mean to her.
I mean, think about how people
barely like that I'm Asian.
She's full.
She's gonna get, like, roasted.
‐ Oh, my God.
Ume, at "sker"...
I know.
I protect you. You‐‐
- Can you just translate this?
- Okay.
We got your back.
She get‐‐she gets it now.
Uh, okay, class.
Maya's cousin is with us today.
‐ No, we're not related.
‐ Okay, friend then, whatever.
Uh, she wanted to see what
an American school was like,
so let's all be very welcoming
to her.
Why don't you come up front
so we can introduce you
to everyone.
Oh‐‐
‐ Do you want us
to go with you?
We should just go with‐‐
‐ I'm just gonna come up
with her, is that‐‐
‐ No,
you're fine where you are.
Ume means plum, right?
Everyone, this is Ume.
Let's give her a big
Trailview welcome, hm?
Yeah.
Thank you, school.
Oh, my God.
She's so cute.
I love her!
‐ What?
She actually loves
doing the peace sign so much.
She thinks it's so,
like, funny.
She'll put it in a photo.
‐ Mr. O,
can she please shadow me?
‐ Oh, she's shadowing us, so‐‐
‐ Yeah, she‐‐
I'm the only one
who speaks Japanese,
so she can't understand
without me.
Not the only one.
What's he saying?
‐ Shh, I'm trying to follow.
I'll explain later.
Have to be careful with Ume,
‐ Maya needs to translate,
you guys.
‐ You guys, stop!
Ah, you're touching her a lot.
Oh, my God!
‐ That's so cool‐looking!
‐ You guys,
you're gonna kill it.
She loves that thing.
I'll take care of it.
They really love Ume.
‐ Yeah.
Yeah.
‐ We were so worried.
‐ Unexpected, but wonderful.
‐ Hi, Ume.
Uh, my favorite fruit is plum.
‐ Don't look at us.
That's my ex.
He's, like, still not over me.
‐ He loves her.
‐ Ex‐eh.
Ai‐ai‐ai.
Get it?
‐ Hey, "Oomi."
Your hair's so pretty.
So black.
‐ My hair's always been black.
‐ Wait, Maya,
do you speak Japanese?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Ooh.
Can you ask "Oomi"
where she got her socks from?
‐ Yeah.
‐ I'm, like, totally obsessed.
‐ Yeah, I, like,
have the same socks.
They're just from Japan.
‐ What's up?
‐ Hector wanted me to tell you
that he thinks "Oomi"'s cute.
Ume! Come on, bro, go.
Ume!
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ They're so dumb.
‐ Hector‐‐the stripes,
thinks you're cute.
Just like the high schooler,
Steve, thinks I'm cute...
and wants to be with me.
‐ I don't care.
‐ Anna, she doesn't understand
English or gestures like‐‐
‐ That's why you're here
to translate.
‐ Okay, I know.
I just said it.
Okay.
‐ Yeah, Hector wants to play
Crashed Bandicoot: Warped
with her and hang out.
‐ Go tell her.
‐ Um...
I just told her.
What?
‐ Well, you guys,
maybe everyone should just
hang out at Maya's.
‐ Oh, yeah.
‐ If you want,
because that's
where Ume's staying.
‐ Yeah.
She, um, she has DDR and stuff.
It's this, like, cool,
like, Japanese dance game.
Um‐‐
If you guys want, like‐‐
Yeah, she'd love that.
So if you guys wanna just‐‐
you can invite Hector
or whatever,
and you all can come too.
‐ Yeah.
‐ What's DDR?
‐ Yeah, cool.
‐ It's the dance‐‐
‐ I'll go tell him right now.
‐ Cool, if I can.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Ume!
Ume.
‐ Hey, uh, "Hector."
Hector!
‐ What,
are you bored of me already?
Just like your mom?
Just kidding.
But you know, the more time
you spend with Maya, you know,
cuts into my time with ya.
‐ No, I know, but she just
needs my help, like,
with the party, you know?
‐ Okay, well,
when you get home,
I have a surprise for you.
‐ Oh, that's so nice.
Okay, cool.
Love you, Dad!
Thank you so much!
‐ I love you too.
Okay, so you have to press it
on the arrows‐‐
‐ I know.
‐ So where's Ume?
‐ No, you don't know
how to play.
No‐‐Anna.
- Please don't touch it.
- Sorry.
Just give me a second.
Dance Dance Revolution.
‐ Okay, it's set up.
Ready?
So you're gonna do these two,
and I'm gonna do these two.
‐ Okay.
‐ Okay, ready?
Anna, Anna, Anna.
Right, right‐‐no.
Oh, my God, Anna!
‐ It's not sensing me.
Okay, we failed.
That's 'cause Anna was
hitting it wrong.
‐ I don't think you guys need
to stomp so hard.
It only takes a light touch.
Anna was stomping really hard.
‐ Maya, I was doing the guy.
‐ You were supposed to‐‐
‐ Okay, head count on hot dogs.
‐ Dad, get out, please.
‐ I'll make the full pack.
‐ Go!
That's your dad?
He's not Japanese though.
‐ Yeah, he's white.
‐ Weird.
You look full.
No, I don't.
‐ Um, Hector, when will the
rest of your friends be here?
‐ Uh, they never said anything.
Also, my dad dropped me off.
‐ Sick.
‐ Hi!
Come here, come sit.
‐ My bro!
- What up?
- Get off!
Ow, don't move my arm
like that, you psycho.
‐ Whoa. "Sooji,"
your Japanese is really good.
‐ "Sooji,"
you and "Oomi" actually
look more related
than you and Maya.
‐ Yeah, that's because me
and Maya are half‐siblings.
Unfortunately,
she got the bad half.
‐ Oh, really?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Is white the bad half?
‐ Yeah!
‐ You wish you had more white
in you.
You'd look way better, bitch.
‐ I actually think, Shuji,
that you're very, very
attractive the way you are.
‐ Ew, Anna.
‐ Wait, hold on, so the hot dog
guy isn't your dad?
No, uh, my birth dad
lives in Japan.
‐ Yeah,
but that's still our dad.
‐ That's like‐‐
‐ Yeah.
‐ He's your dad.
‐ I know.
‐ That's why you and Ume have
such exotic names.
I've always wanted my name
to be Yolanda.
Yeah, and that's why
I can speak Japanese fluently,
and Maya can barely
say a sentence.
‐ That's‐‐you're lying.
I speak full Japanese.
Tell them.
Perfect, perfect, p‐‐perfect.
‐ Are you guys seeing this?
Perfect, perfect, perfect.
Holy shit.
"Oomi," can I play with you?
You're, like, perfect.
All right, that's enough.
My turn.
‐ Maya.
Don't move her arm like that.
‐ I didn't move her arm li‐‐
I, like, touched her
- like you touched my arm.
- Now she's crying.
Great job, idiot.
‐ Sorry!
She's crying
'cause everybody loves her?
‐ Okay, weird.
‐ Guess she's not into you.
I mean, honestly, like,
I love her,
but she's kind of a problem.
‐ No, and I hope that she's
okay, and I felt super bad,
but I'm also like, everybody's
complimenting you up the ass.
‐ We're sleeping
on the floor for you.
Like, can you stop
being such a crazy bitch?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Like, honestly.
‐ No, like, seriously.
‐ And I love her, but, like‐‐
‐ I love her,
but she is an attention whore.
‐ Truly, truly, truly.
‐ Because she's just like,
oh...
you know?
‐ Like‐‐
and then, like‐‐
Like, bitch.
‐ Hey.
‐ Hey, Ume.
I just‐‐
Anna, I just asked
if you're okay,
and she didn't answer.
Oh.
Guess it's time for bed.
‐ Get out!
Get out‐‐
What?
Pig Latin.
Smart.
‐ Hm?
‐ Like, she's kind of a liar.
Like, she'll say
she saw people doing things
that they weren't doing,
like, it's really weird.
Get out!
‐ I mean, I haven't
personally seen her do that,
but I also
don't speak Japanese,
so I could be wrong,
like, I trust you.
I trust you that you're right.
‐ Oh, my God.
What?
Ume, what?
Did you just see her glare
at me?
Like, that's crazy.
‐ Mm.
I'm just feeling really
stressed out, like‐‐
‐ She needs to go.
‐ Okay, get up.
We're gonna fix this.
Let's go.
Um, sorry.
‐ Mrs. Ishii‐Peters,
we'll be back.
‐ Okay.
‐ Got to fix this.
Maya, go.
Okay, you guys...
just hug.
Hug.
‐ See, she doesn't
even want to touch me.
She, like,
thinks I'm disgusting.
‐ Hug her.
‐ Like,
if you think I'm disgusting
and you don't like me,
you can leave.
Like, honestly...
What?
You're yelling at me. Like, s‐‐
Anna, she's yelling at me!
‐ You're yelling at me!
Like, stop, you're yelling!
‐ Did you just call me stupid?
She just called me stupid.
You think I'm stupid?
Fuck you.
Sorry, like, fuck you,
honestly!
Everyone thinks she's perfect.
You're so much better than me,
okay?
You win.
‐ Maya,
she's a year younger
than us, like, chill.
‐ Why is everyone
on Ume's side?
Why is being Japanese special
on her and bad on me?
Why?
‐ Oh, my God,
I'm getting your mom.
I'm getting your mom, Maya.
I hate you.
I really hate you.
Ume.
Oh, my God, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, I don't mean it.
Okay? I'm sorry.
‐ I love you.
What's going on?
‐ I think they're okay.
‐ Hey, Dad!
Dad?
‐ Hey.
‐ Hey, Dad.
Hey.
You know, there's nowhere
to lock up my bike
outside of this frickin' place.
‐ Oh, that sucks.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Hey, did anyone call for me?
‐ Uh...
no.
Um, not that I know of.
Oops.
Sorry.
Wow.
What have you been doing
in here?
‐ I just kind of unpacked
your kitchen stuff, so‐‐
Yeah, the kitchen looks great.
Thank you.
‐ You're welcome.
‐ Spending some time
at your dad's house, huh?
So does this mean
that you're gonna
make it full‐time?
‐ Um, maybe.
I got a surprise for ya.
You know, I think it's gonna
really move that meter
to, uh, I love my dad the most.
Nah, I'm just kidding.
‐ The cheese and corn's
not melted,
but I think it'll be fine.
Um...
Smells good.
‐ Ow.
Dad‐‐
Ta‐da!
Da‐da‐da.
What the fuck, Anna?
‐ I know, I just‐‐
I thought‐‐
‐ This is my new oven!
‐ I know, I'm sorry.
I thought it was glass‐‐
‐ You know, you don't
put plastic in an oven.
What are you doing?
‐ I thought it was glass‐‐
‐ God!
Ugh.
‐ I'm sorry‐‐
‐ That's why you don't do this
when I'm not here, okay?
‐ Okay.
‐ Here, come on, move.
Move, move, move.
‐ Okay.
‐ You're only‐‐
‐ Okay!
You're only 13.
‐ I thought it was glass.
I was just trying to help.
Ugh.
A hamster?
‐ I‐‐I wanted
to get you something so that
when you go back
to your mom's this week
and I'm not with you, you‐‐
you have someone
to keep you company.
Anna, the phone.
‐ Okay, okay!
Got it.
Hi, you've reached the Kones.
This is Anna speaking.
How can I help you?
Yo, how can I help you?
‐ Yo?
Oh, Steve?
Yo.
Things may come
to those who wait,
but only the things left
by those who hustle.
How you been?
‐ Busy.
Ah!
Nah!
Fell.
‐ Mm‐‐I don't know‐‐
I don't know what that means.
‐ No...
clothes.
Um... hot.
Yeah.
‐ Mm, me too.
Mm‐‐