‐ Driver.
Are we almost there?
Goal!
I
I am hiding
The you I show to you
Is just a lie
You take what you want
You get what you take
So high, high, high
‐ Right after that,
I snapped his headphones.
‐ Did your parents react?
‐ They stay out of it.
They don't really give a shit.
‐ Eager Anna.
‐ Thank you.
Um, I just wanted to say
that what you all
are going through
is intense but wonderful.
Kudos.
For me, I have a hamster,
and my Dad got it for me.
Its name is Daddy
'cause I named it that,
and I love it.
Couldn't help but feel like
maybe my Dad is just trying
to sweeten me up
by getting me the pet
because he wants me to live
with him, not with my mom.
‐ Yeah, wow,
y‐you don't have any problems
opening up and sharing, do you?
You remind me of my mailman.
‐ Thank you.
Um, and actually...
just going between
the two places‐‐
my mom's place
and my dad's place‐‐
it's hard,
and my mom is, like,
always late.
Always.
And my Dad is grumpier.
And he didn't get the house,
and I'm just like,
if he doesn't get me, too,
I don't know
what he's gonna do.
‐ You talk like you're 40,
kind of.
‐ Thank you.
And that's actually
a good thing,
because most people don't reach
their full potential
until they're at least 38.
‐ Oh, my goodness, it's time
for us to wrap it up.
Thank you for opening up
and sharing, everyone.
Get all your stuff.
Don't forget your shoes.
Oh, it's just my shoes.
Remember to breathe. Ciao!
‐ Thanks, Tina.
‐ See ya.
‐ What's up?
‐ Hey.
So, uh, you seeing the world
through
rose‐colored lenses now?
No, seriously, I don't get
what the point of it is
'cause, like, they just listen
and they, like, don't
give you advice, you know?
‐ Yeah. Yeah.
Basically, we
diagnose based on a spectrum,
and Maya happens to be
a little bit above average
on that spectrum.
Maya, do you have trouble
focusing?
‐ No, I'm actually
really smart.
‐ Oh, I know you're very smart.
That's not the issue.
Attention Deficit Disorder
is actually quite common,
and many of our patients
have found success
taking methylphenidate
hydrochloride.
‐ Medication for this?
‐ It is a stimulant,
but it actually
has the opposite effect
on kids who have ADD.
It helps them focus.
‐ Maya, then you just better
pay more attention.
‐ I do.
‐ That's all this is.
‐ Stop. Stop.
‐ No.
‐ You know,
Maya is jumping
off the walls like crazy.
And I love that about you,
darling, I do.
But not at school.
‐ And with every medication,
there are some side effects.
Most commonly,
increased heart rate.
But the benefits
do outweigh any discomfort.
‐ No, I don't wanna take
the medicine
if it's gonna
speed up my heart.
‐ Once you acknowledge
the problem,
she can have
extra time on tests
and other assistance that can
help Maya improve her scores.
‐ Extended time on testing?
‐ Yeah,
as much time as you need.
‐ We'll talk about it at home.
‐ I think I wanna take
the medicine.
‐ No.
‐ We'll talk about it.
‐ Mom, I wanna take it!
‐ Oh. Stop. Stop.
‐ Maya...
uh, how do you feel
about fluorescent lights?
‐ I don't feel good
about fluorescent lights.
‐ Anna.
Anna. Anna.
‐ Stop. What are you...
‐ Oh, just stare
at whatever you want.
Like, so stupid.
They're crazy.
‐ I know.
I like that, uh‐‐
I like when your mom's late.
‐ Oh, yeah?
‐ Which is, like, all the time.
I know.
‐ Ope.
‐ Hey.
‐ I know, I'm late.
Yeah.
‐ Who's that guy?
‐ Who are you talking about?
‐ Mr. Loser.
‐ There's no one there.
There's a guy
right there.
Doesn't even know
how to ride his bike.
‐ I don't know who that is.
He's in Teens in Need.
Okay.
Just get in the back.
‐ Irlen syndrome
is a light sensitivity
that can contribute
to reading difficulties,
headaches,
trouble concentrating.
But what can help...
Is wearing
these special glasses.
‐ Do I have to wear these
all day, like, every day?
‐ Well...
Look at Haley Joel Osment
on the red carpet.
He has Irlen syndrome.
He looks great. Very cool.
‐ I love it.
‐ And I know you want me
to do my own laundry.
‐ About that...
‐ But I'm just‐‐it's hard
with all the Teens in Need
and everything.
I can't have dirty underwear.
‐ Thank you.
‐ I got it.
But maybe, just maybe,
I've found someone
to help us with that.
‐ Maybe, just maybe, what?
Found someone to help.
‐ Found someone
to help us with that?
A maid?
Mom. A maid?
Surprise!
‐ Oh, you're late.
Huh.
‐ Grammy.
Oh, my. Oh, my.
Oh, and here I am
as a surprise.
I was going to help out
for the foreseeable future.
‐ How are you?
‐ Hello. Yeah.
You know, I keep telling you
this, and you don't listen.
You're slouching.
And if you continue to slouch,
you're going to get
one of those stomach pooches
just like your mother.
‐ Ha‐ha. Mom, stop.
‐ Oh, well.
I think I'm going to go
and make us some dinner.
Okay. Thanks, Grammy.
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ Love you.
‐ Well, yes, thank you.
‐ Bring the groceries.
Near the volcano,
it is distinguished
by a network of cracks.
Where were you?
My Grammy
just moved in with us.
‐ What?
‐ Yeah.
‐ That's crazy.
What? I love these.
‐ I have to wear them
'cause I have ADD
and Irlen syndrome.
And literally, like,
I have to take this medication
that can speed up
your heart rate and kill you.
‐ Wait, what?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Maya.
‐ I know.
‐ I can't lose you.
‐ Shh. Girls. Movie.
And Maya, no Oakleys
in the classroom.
I actually have Irlen syndrome.
Um...
and I need to wear these
'cause they're prescribed.
So...yeah.
And I'm also supposed
to be on medication right now,
but I'm not on it.
So I'm just having, like,
a really hard day.
‐ Hey, Bowl Cut.
"The Matrix" called.
‐ Neo wants his glasses back.
Haley Joel Osment wears them.
So did you hear
from Steve's friend Derrick?
Did he call you?
‐ You mean the high schooler
that's gonna be my boyfriend?
‐ Yeah.
‐ No, he hasn't.
But I'm just kind of,
like, waiting.
I feel like any day now.
‐ Yeah.
When he does,
we're gonna go on double dates.
‐ Um...
wait, if your Grammy
is living with you,
does that mean I can still
sleep over tonight or no?
‐ Oh, my mom's gonna
take us to Blockbuster.
Shh!
Sorry.
She's such a bitch.
Hi, Mr. Corlado‐‐
Anna, stop.
‐ Stop.
Oh, my God.
Why is my mom honking?
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ What is she doing?
‐ Why is she doing that?
‐ Come on, come on.
Get in, get in.
Oh, hi, honey.
Come on in.
No, not there.
I have my oxygen tank.
‐ Wait, is that your Grammy?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Get in the backseat.
That's good.
‐ I didn't know you were
picking us up.
- Well...
- Hi.
‐ Well, no, Mom is very busy
with her "rackas" clients.
‐ It's reiki, but...
Racka, reiki, ra‐‐
Did you know‐‐did you know
that your mother went through
a whole year of her RN,
and then she met your Dad.
And we all know
how that worked out.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Is she blind?
‐ Um, hi, Grammy. I'm Maya.
‐ It's Mrs. Ryan.
‐ Um, Grammy,
can we go to Blockbuster?
'Cause my mom
was gonna take us.
‐ No.
‐ Sorry, Grammy?
Yeah?
‐ Um, you don't have to honk,
'cause it'll move.
‐ Don't tell me what to do.
If you learned how to type,
it meant you wanted
to be a secretary.
So we took Home Economics
so we could get a good husband.
Mom?
‐ Where are we going?
‐ This way.
‐ Thank you.
‐ Mom?
‐ You don't have to yell
so much.
I mean, you're a tall girl
with a tall voice to match.
Let's go.
‐ Sorry.
‐ You know, I still wanna
have my hair done today.
‐ Where do I put my stuff?
‐ Just wherever.
Maya, you've been here before.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ Maya, don't...yeah.
‐ It's, like, stuck.
‐ Yeah, yeah.
You know, you gotta watch
these things.
They're lethal.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Okay. Okay.
It's stuck. Okay.
It's kinda hard to steer.
True.
‐ "Went out with Ramona.
Enjoy your movie."
‐ It's just us tonight.
‐ Well, let's take
a look at this.
Can we go to your room?
‐ Yeah. One sec.
‐ Oh, here it is.
Honey, would you please
call the salon for me?
I want to have
my hair done today‐‐
‐ Okay.
‐ With‐‐with Sheryl.
And do not let them
try to sell you on Theresa
because your mother tells me
she doesn't know one thing.
Yes.
Did Theresa do your hair?
‐ We're sorry,
La Moda Hair Salon
is currently closed.
‐ Uh, Grammy, they're closed.
‐ Well, call again.
Maybe you got the wrong number.
‐ I got the voicemail.
It's definitely them.
They're just closed,
but I can call again tomorrow.
‐ Well, if you hadn't been
lollywagging so much at school,
maybe we could have gotten here
and I could have gotten
my hair done.
You're just like your mother.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Sorry.
‐ Sorry, Grammy.
‐ Could you get me something
to drink with my pills dear?
‐ Okay.
‐ Okay, Grammy.
‐ Good.
No, no, no. Just you.
Come‐‐you come back, Maya.
Come back.
‐ Maya, she wants you.
‐ You can go alone.
You don't need Maya.
‐ Anna, wait.
‐ Oh, um, help.
‐ Do you need‐‐
‐ She's not gonna be gone
long, darling.
She's not gonna be‐‐
she'll be right back.
‐ Okay.
‐ I know that.
Yes.
‐ Sorry.
You know, I have ADD,
so I have to take pills too.
‐ You have ADD? Hmm.
Well, you know,
everyone only has
a certain amount of beats
in their lifetime.
‐ Really?
‐ That's why
I'm so very quiet and still.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ I got you water.
Two cubes, Grammy.
‐ Oh, darling, you know I don't
drink water with my pills.
I only take sherry.
‐ Oh, okay.
Oh, okay...
‐ You sit down.
‐ Gra‐‐grammy?
‐ Uh, Anna?
Anna?
‐ Are you okay?
‐ Where do you come from, dear?
Because you have
such Mongoloid features.
‐ Excuse me, ladies.
I'm Anna Kone.
I'll be your server.
‐ Honey, no.
You know I don't take water
with my pills.
I take sherry.
‐ She has sherry, Grammy.
‐ Oh, good.
‐ Um, I brought you some
stacked crackers and cheese
because I love you.
‐ Did you wash your hands
before making me
the cheese and crackers?
‐ Um...
‐ Just do it. Just do it.
‐ Sorry, Grammy.
‐ Please‐‐that's right.
‐ Do I need to wash
my hands too?
‐ Yesterday.
Did you wash your hands
really well?
‐ Yes. Wait, Anna, wait.
Do we have to hang out
with her the whole time?
‐ I mean, I know I'm exhausted.
The funny thing is that
she was actually here to help.
‐ I feel like she hates me.
‐ She hates me so much more.
‐ Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ Oh, my God, this is gonna
be my entire childhood.
Okay, we should go.
‐ No, let's play. Please.
Maya, I wish I could.
‐ Grammy.
‐ This sucks.
‐ Are you okay, Grammy?
‐ I wanted
to have my hair done.
‐ Do you like your nails,
Grammy?
Well, you kinda shake a lot.
‐ Okay. Are you ready to look?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Okay, Grammy.
‐ Anna, you're good at this.
Very good.
Oh.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
‐ Welcome, Grammy.
‐ Pretty.
‐ Sorry today was kinda boring.
Thanks for doing
my Grammy's nails.
It's okay.
‐ Sorry you have ADD.
‐ And Irlen syndrome.
‐ Are you gonna sleep
with your glasses on?
‐ Oh, no.
Can't do that.
Goodnight.
‐ Goodnight.
‐ Anna.
‐ Mom?
Oh, my God.
‐ What? Stop. Stop.
Stop.
Mom?
‐ Wait.
Anna, wait.
‐ Mom?
She's gone.
‐ Oh.
‐ Such a psycho.
‐ Side, side, side!
‐ You're about to go
to a funeral.
What's your problem?
You're acting like
Looney Tunes.
Take this pill.
‐ No, I don't wanna
take the pill.
I don't wanna die!
‐ Dame.
‐ There's only so many
heartbeats in a lifetime.
I don't wanna die.
‐ Just take it.
Am I gonna die?
‐ No.
‐ Thank you.
Fine, you keep them.
‐ Oh, thank you.
‐ Thank you.
Thank you for coming.
‐ Thank you for coming.
It means a lot.
‐ I took my medicine,
but I don't feel it yet.
‐ Okay.
‐ Say something nice to Anna.
‐ Yeah.
Sorry about your G‐ma.
Should I go now? Okay.
‐ You better go now.
‐ Right now?
‐ With Anna.
‐ She still has
my nail polish on.
‐ Oh, yeah.
She kinda looks weird.
‐ Yeah.
Do you feel sad?
‐ Right now?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Oh, um...
Sort of.
I will later, I think.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Okay.
Bye, Grammy.
‐ Bye, Grammy.
That was weird.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Um, if everyone wouldn't mind
taking a seat,
I'd like to say a few words
about my mother.
Oh, before I forget,
lunch will be served upstairs.
It's nothing elaborate,
but we hope you'll stay
and share your memories.
‐ Oh, my God. Is that Derrick?
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ They're here.
My God, Derrick is so fine.
Okay.
All right.
‐ Geraldine Olay Ryan.
‐ Olay is her middle name?
I didn't‐‐
‐ Stop.
My mom.
Geraldine Olay Ryan.
She was a character.
She didn't smile a lot.
No, she didn't.
‐ Geraldine Olay Ryan
was a mother
that I loved very much.
‐ Yame nasai.
When I found her
facedown,
sprawled out...
It's an image that
I won't get out of my head.
‐ That's quite enough,
young lady.
‐ With the oxygen tank
blowing air to no one.
Where was I?
She was the first to graduate
college in her family.
And I'm really grateful
that my daughter and I
got to spend her last days...
with her.
‐ I want cheese with that.
Ow!
‐ That was so inappropriate.
‐ Stop. It's not my fault.
That was Anna.
She started it.
‐ Do you need to take
more medicine?
‐ No. I don't even feel it yet.
‐ I don't even feel it.
Oh, wait. Mama?
Mom?
I think I'm feeling it now.
Anna.
Excuse me.
‐ Thank you.
‐ Sorry, um, for what I did.
Like, my reaction
wasn't, like, normal.
‐ It's okay.
‐ Really?
‐ Yeah.
I think maybe it is normal.
It's okay.
‐ Pretty freaky, huh?
‐ I'm on methylphenidate
hydrochloride right now.
‐ I tried that once.
It was fun.
I'm Derrick. Wassup?
‐ I'm Maya.
‐ I know.
‐ Thank you.
Who is that?
I don't know.
‐ Hey.
Hey, Dad.
‐ How you guys doing?
‐ Great.
‐ Yeah.
Again, Kath, I'm sorry.
She was unique.
‐ I loved her too.
‐ No, you didn't.
‐ Yes, I did.
I mean, I know‐‐I know
she was hard on you
and she messed up a bit,
you know,
here and there.
But I know
how proud of you she is.
‐ Was.
‐ Yeah, maybe, I don't‐‐
Thank you.
‐ I'm gonna go, okay?
‐ Okay.
‐ That laughing, not funny.
‐ Dad.
‐ I'm serious.
‐ I'm sorry.
‐ You have a little bit
of growing up to do, all right?
‐ Okay. Stop. Not now.
It's too much.
‐ Take care of your mom,
all right?
She needs you.
Okay.
Bye. Love you.
‐ Sweet of him to come.
‐ Curtis. Sometimes Curt.
Steven. Sometimes Steve.
‐ Yeah, it is.
‐ Most of the time Steve.
‐ So I brought my fried Maya.
‐ No, I don't wanna
speak right now.
‐ Hi, Maya.
‐ Sorry, she doesn't wanna
speak right now.
So...
um, but for me,
I'll just say that, um,
I'm afraid that...
my Dad is really mad at me
right now.
And that's because I...
told him that I wanted
to live with my mom.
And I told him over the phone.
And I could tell
by just the tone of his voice
that he was really, really sad.
I don't want to disappoint him,
but I told him
that my mom needs me right now
'cause my Grammy just passed.
I'm just really worried
about him.
‐ Oh, I'm so sorry
for your loss.
I'm so sorry
Sorry for your loss.
‐ Thanks, Sasha.
I'm good, actually.
I'm not good, but I'm okay.
‐ She's okay, 'cause...
you, like, laughed
during the eulogy,
so it's not, like, that sad.
‐ Well, it's just that a word
struck me funny,
but I'm not‐‐
‐ No, I know.
‐ You laughed, too, so I
don't know why you'd say that.
‐ Yeah, well, it's not
my Grammy, though.
Like...
‐ I'm so sorry.
‐ It's okay.
‐ I have ADD
and Irlen syndrome.
‐ Oh.
Well, thank you so much
for sharing, Maya.
‐ You're welcome.
Lost on a island
Catch me drinking
pee‐pee water
Lost in the forest
While I'm drinking
pee‐pee water
Got no fluids
Catch me drinking
pee‐pee water
Drinking pee‐pee water
‐ Oh.
Nice, nice.
‐ Stop.
Hey.
- Sup?
- What's up?
What's up?
Hey.
‐ Do you wanna be
my girlfriend?
‐ No.
On Opposite Day.
‐ Sick.
‐ Yeah, of course.
Good afternoon.
‐ Good afternoon.
‐ Do you have your meds?
‐ Like, no, on opposite day.
‐ So is that yeah?
‐ Yeah.
You can have tomorrow's
if you want.
‐ Cool.
‐ 'Cause I'm not gonna
take that one. Here.
‐ Yeah. Oh.
‐ Oh, sorry.
It's all good.
It's still good.
I've taken worse.
‐ So, um,
do you wanna be my boyfriend?
Your glasses are weird.
‐ Okay.
‐ Kay.
‐ Oh.
‐ Okay.
‐ That's gonna hit nice.
I'm getting dizzy.
Me too.
‐ Mom, did you do my laundry?
No, it's your
responsibility.
‐ Are you kidding?
Ugh.
I already used both sides!
Look on your bed,
sweetie.
‐ My bed?
Grammy's hand‐me‐downs.
She'd want you to have them.
Enjoy.
‐ Ew.
They're from Grammy!
Thanks, Grammy.
Ew.
Anna?
I'm coming!