Hey, get out of the way!
- Oh, my god, wait.
- Ow!
You're stepping on my toe. Jesus.
Let me see! Yeah, I mean,
you don't really know‐‐
‐ Oh, my god!
Oh, my god, oh, my god. I
got it, I got it, I got it.
‐ congratulations! That's amazing.
- I think you go it.
- Oh, my god! Yes!
- I think you got it.
- You do?
- I do, I do, I do.
- Sorry, you guys.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Wait.
Oh, my god.
Oh, my god. ‐ that is not real.
That's not real. That's not real.
‐ that's the lead.
‐ oh, my god!
‐ wait. ‐ that is incredible.
Wait.
‐ is there another list, though?
Okay. ‐ oh, my god, no, I'm sorry.
- ‐ no, it's fine.
- No, no.
It's so fucked up you didn't get
a role and I did.
‐ no, it's fine. ‐ no,
it doesn't make sense.
You're literally the best
actress in our school.
Like, you're so much better than me.
I don't want to do it without you.
Oh, my god, Maya!
‐ hi. Oh, my god.
Thank you. ‐ I know! It's amazing.
You're gonna be so good.
‐ oh, my god. You're gonna be so good!
‐ hi. No, no.
No, you guys. You don't even know.
I've, like, never done this before.
I've never acted. You're
gonna be so good.
Stop saying that!
‐ I'm not going in. ‐
you're incredible.
‐ no, I'm not. I'm not. I suck.
‐ you have to go in, Maya. ‐ I quit.
I'm not going in.
No, please. I want you to go in.
- You're better than me.
- First rehearsal!
‐ I know! I'm so excited.
No, I can't do it. Please.
Just come in for a little.
‐ I don't know. ‐
please, please, please!
‐ no, it's embarrassing.
Maya. ‐ no, I can't go in. Please.
Please. Please. ‐ Maya. Maya.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
You want some milk? ‐ yeah.
‐ all right.
Shh.
Latch.
Maya, latch, latch.
‐ Anna: That's better.
‐ ‐ Maya, no.
No. Ma‐‐ow! Maya!
Ow! ‐ Maya?
Yeah. ‐ are you coming in now?
We're about to start.
‐ yeah. ‐ hello.
I'm sorry, who are you?
- ‐ Anna.
- I just wanted to say that
I know that you "cast" your
play already... Uh‐huh.
But if you have an
understudy role, I'm free.
‐ she's actually, like,
a really good singer
and actor and stuff.
She had this "ave Maria" solo
a while back that was really good.
- Here, sing it.
- ‐
it's whatever.
‐ wow.
You have a really great range.
But we're about to have our
first rehearsal now, Maya,
so we're ready whenever you are.
Great to meet you. Keep‐‐keep going.
You're really some‐‐great.
‐ sure thing.
Thank you.
‐ okay. So it's just you.
‐ okay.
I'm sorry.
No. Have an amazing time.
You got it. ‐ no, I don't
want to go without you.
You've got it.
‐ I love you. ‐ I love you.
‐ so, here we are. Congratulations.
I'll give you a little backstory.
The play is an original piece,
which means I wrote it.
And for you guys as the actors,
my whole thing, my mantra,
it's gonna be real and honest.
If you're not real and honest with me,
if you're not real and
honest with yourselves,
and if you're not real and
honest with each other,
then this whole thing is bullshit.
Now, there are four of
you in this ensemble
and by the end of this rehearsal,
there will be three.
So who here doesn't belong?
Come on.
Ian, who doesn't belong?
‐ um, I'm, um‐‐
come on. ‐ sorry, it's just hard.
Real and honest.
‐ um, I think I would pick...
Maya.
It's just, in every drama
class since third grade,
you haven't, um, showed
anything that I've noticed.
I don't think you have,
like, "it" charisma.
You're just kind of wild
and out of control.
Thank you, Ian.
Well...
That was just an exercise.
Relax. You guys all belong.
Relax.
You're here. You're in.
‐ ‐ good.
Very real, very honest.
Now we can start.
Good job, guys. Really good job.
Relax. Take a deep breath.
How'd you guys feel?
Trailview middle school's
performing arts showcase.
Oh, my god.
Hey, Anna. ‐ hey.
‐ want some duct tape?
‐ what?
‐ we're making wallets.
- ‐ oh.
- Here.
‐ oh. Ow.
What are you guys doing here?
We're techies. I'm the
lighting designer.
Marissa's props.
‐ ‐ sorry, babe.
Master of props.
We handle all the technical
elements of the play
and build sets.
‐ wow. Talented couple.
Do you have, like, a
teacher or anything?
- Supervisors?
- Kind of.
Steve's a freshman
and he's supposed to supervise us,
but lets us do whatever till tech week.
You mean hell week, peasants.
'Sup, Steve?
‐
You two watch final destination yet?
It's on my list.
Horror's an easy genre to fuck up.
Watch it, kone?
Is it James wong's sonata?
Obliviously not, but
you should watch it
if you think films are worth watching.
‐ okay, people. Very exciting moment.
Getting our official show scripts.
You only get one of these, so
take very good care of it.
Go ahead.
Highlight your character's parts
and your dialogue.
There are four highlighters there.
‐ wow, Maya. You get
to highlight a lot.
‐ whoa. Maya and Gabe kiss.
‐ okay, Jessica.
‐ no, Jessica's right.
There is a kiss in the first scene.
Which we are gonna have to make
as real and honest as possible.
Anybody have any questions yet?
Do you want to give it a rest?
I'm trying to read.
I'm just prepping
in case the judge decides
that I don't get the house.
Okay?
Anna, look.
I found your old Nintendo.
‐ that's a broken game boy.
We're trying to read.
I'm the one that should
be worried, all right?
It's not like that female judge
is gonna rule in my favor.
All the more reason to help me.
Anna, look!
Your "most improved" trophy.
Keep it? ‐ no.
I don't know why I'd need that, so‐‐
how 'bout your glitter? Keep that?
You still love crafts, don't you?
‐ mom!
I don't want any of that stuff.
Like, I don't do that anymore.
Glitter's for kids, Kat.
You keep talking to us
while we're reading.
Like, stop.
‐
Sheila was backing away from you.
Don't you dare make another drink.
Don't you dare!
I'm warning you, don't do it.
Were you doing your
business with Sheila?
Were you doing your business?
Were you‐‐were‐‐
were you doing your business
with Sheila, you rat bastard?
You rat bastard!
Were you doing it with
Sheila, you rat bastard?
Get away from me!
Yeah.
You get your hands off me, you pig.
You know,
I could call you mommy
and you wouldn't know the difference.
Mommy.
Mommy, get me water. Get me turnips.
Yeah.
You're not a man.
You know, a real man,
he grabs a woman,
he takes her by the neck, and says,
"everything's gonna be all right."
Oh, what?
What, you gonna hit me?
Yeah, that's what I thought.
You don't even know what it takes
to put your flesh
against someone else's.
You just sit. That's all you do.
You sit, you sit, and you sit,
and you wait for someone to come by
and tell you what to do.
Well, you know what? I
ain't gonna do it no more.
I'm not gonna sit.
I'm not gonna wait around for anything.
I'm gonna swim! I'm gonna fly!
I'm gonna be the best goddamn person
that ever fucking existed!
You hear me?
I'm it, baby.
I am it!
‐ a real man grabs a woman...
Grabs a woman by the neck
and‐‐ya hear‐‐
it takes flesh...
Takes flesh to g‐‐ ‐
against someone's.
Sorry.
Can I start again?
‐ mm‐hmm.
‐ um...
It's the flesh that takes
against someone else's‐‐
what it feels against someone else's.
‐
‐ if it‐‐ ‐
‐ when you feel the flesh against‐‐
‐ sorry.
Gabe, can you, like, stop
eating your sandwich right now?
'Cause you're taking
me out of the scene.
I'm, like, trying to‐‐
Greg: This is good.
See, if you were really in the scene,
then you wouldn't have been
distracted by Gabe's eating.
You see that? ‐ yeah, I agree.
I feel like I was in the scene
and I was, like, really‐‐
‐ imagine you're in a theater
of 300 people, okay?
- ‐ uh‐huh?
- Do you think they're all
just gonna sit quietly and watch?
People are gonna get up
to go to the bathroom,
they're gonna be
whispering to each other,
they're gonna be coughing, there's‐‐
papers are gonna be crinkling
all over the place,
but you can't stop.
You gotta keep going.
‐ I promise you, like,
I did this last night.
I was really good.
‐ if you're in the moment,
then you're not distracted
with what's going on around you.
‐ I was in the moment
'cause that's happening in the moment.
Right, where you were in that moment.
- ‐ yeah.
- Not that one.
‐ right.
So...
‐ okay.
I'm telling you, one screw, man.
- Two.
- Babe, listen to her.
She's a carpenter.
‐ freaking hot. Is the air on?
No, they only put it
on during hell week
for the actors.
‐ you guys know I can make
myself cold on demand?
It's 85 degrees in here
and I'm fucking freezing.
Steve, you've gotta show
me how you do that.
Yeah, but like I was
saying, one screw‐‐
here. You'll need this.
- Two.
- What's two gonna do?
‐ oh, I'm not really
sure I'm gonna stay
'cause I don't know if
I'm really, like, built
for this kind of thing.
‐ "adapt what is useful,
"reject what is useless,
and add what is specifically your own."
Bruce Lee.
‐ hmm. Okay.
‐ build yourself to build a set.
‐ cool.
‐ you don't know what it takes.
I don't even know.
Ya hear‐‐
- ‐ okay.
- Sorry.
‐ it's all right.
We're gonna try something different.
Put the script down. Script down.
Plant your feet.
Bend your knees.
Slight bend so you can
have a little bounce.
Now shake it out. Ha, ha, ha.
‐ that's stupid.
‐ shake it. Be stupid.
Let those hands go.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
Good.
Now what are you scared about?
‐ What?
‐ what are you scared about?
‐ nothing. ‐ what are you scared about?
‐ dying. ‐ what are you scared about?
‐ my dad!
- ‐ good. Gabe, now.
- ‐
take it from the end of that scene.
Don't worry about the lines.
You gonna hit me?
‐ you gonna hit me? ‐ yeah.
‐ all right, come and hit me.
Hit me real good, right in the jaw.
‐ you shut your goddamn face or
I'll give you a real shiner!
‐ yeah, you think you're tough?
Come at me, baby! I'm ready.
I'm ready to feel something.
I haven't felt something in years.
‐ you say one more word, I swear‐‐
‐ yeah, you swear what?
You gonna cry home to your mommy?
Mommy, mommy, mommy, mommy!
‐ you shut your mouth. ‐ yeah, or what?
‐ no clapping during rehearsal.
Maya, Gabe...
There it is.
That was it! There it is!
‐ wow, Maya, I was wrong.
You have "it."
‐
I don't even know what happened.
I was, like‐‐ I, like, blacked out.
That was so weird.
I felt‐‐like, I spit on you. I'm sorry.
‐ oh, no. I loved that.
Like, I didn't even feel it.
It made me so angry, like‐‐
‐ ‐ like, in the scene, yeah.
‐ I know. I'm, like‐‐look.
I'm literally shaking right now.
‐ oh, my god, me too. Look.
Let's take ten.
After the break, we're gonna
get into the kissing scene
because I think we're ready.
Just be honest and honesty will follow.
Ooh!
Shut up, dude.
‐ yeah, stop.
‐ Spielberg used two screws
in every beam in jaws.
Look it up. ‐ no, one screw.
You put in two screws and
you risk splintering it.
‐ two screws ensure it doesn't break.
‐ sorry. Oh, no, keep going.
Be right back. Whoopsie‐daisy.
‐ if we put two screws and we break it,
it's all gonna be your fault.
- It won't break.
- Yes, it will.
No, it won't!
‐ hey, sorry.
Um, I was just thinking that,
like, maybe they could
just stop arguing.
It would be a little bit more efficient
if they just tried,
like, the two screws
'cause I already finished,
like, six beams
and we can't really move
on till that one's done.
So maybe you could just
say something or...
‐ why don't you say it to them?
‐ okay, sorry.
We're not gonna get in trouble
if we just do it my way,
and you know what? ‐ yeah.
If it doesn't work, we can
just put in two screws.
Fine, but I already know it's
going to work with one screw.
‐ hey, so‐‐ Brendan: It won't work.
‐ Sorry for interrupting.
Not to be bossy, but I
was just gonna say,
like, what's the point
of all the talking?
‐ we're trying to build
this beam correctly.
‐ right.
But I'm just saying, like,
hell week's coming up,
and, um‐‐
‐ look, why won't you
guys just listen to me?
‐ trust me, okay? ‐
there's a bunch of...
Stuff that has to get done.
We have to do it quickly
and, like, I think you
should just make a decision
and if you make a decision,
then we can just get it done
and move on, and if you don't,
then you're just wasting your own time.
I'm sorry.
It's just a thought I was having
and I just wanted to share it,
but it's probably stupid.
‐ guys, I think she's right.
‐ I know. I just wanted to‐‐
"knowing is not enough.
"We must apply.
"Willing is not enough.
We must do."
Bruce.
Okay, obi‐wan kone‐obi.
What do we do next?
Your scene work with Maya
was really inspiring.
‐ oh, uh, thanks.
Yo, Gabe!
‐ heard you guys had a crazy sleepover.
What a ridic‐‐
like you weren't doing the same thing?
Come on.
‐ at least I wasn't
tag‐teaming like you homos.
Okay.
‐ yeah, well, this homo
gets to kiss Maya,
so who's the homo now, faggots?
‐ well, yeah, you know it's
not a real kiss, though.
'Cause it's in a play.
‐ yeah, well, she's hot,
so I don't care if it's real or not.
‐ okay.
Okay.
- ‐ later.
‐ half beam, go.
Faster. Go.
Yes. Move.
Sorry to say that.
Bring it in. Faster. Yes.
Yes, you guys. Yes. Support.
Support is my middle name.
Oh, my god.
We're good.
All right, gang. Welcome back.
So let's take it from the end
of the first scene
at the line, "get away."
‐ get away from me.
‐ isn't this what you want?
‐ you don't know the first thing
about what I want.
You get your hands off me, you pig!
Oh!
Or what?
Uh, sorry, uh... Hold.
Um, Greg, uh, can I have a
little aside with Maya?
‐ whatever you need.
Okay.
I'm sorry. ‐ no, it's okay.
Was it my breath?
‐ oh, uh, no. It's just, um...
Like, I just wanted to
make this official,
you know, before we... Uh...
Do it, so, like...
Um...
Do you want to be my girlfriend?
You don't have to answer now. ‐ yes.
‐ okay. ‐ okay.
‐ sick. ‐ oh, my god.
‐ so, like, in rehearsal‐‐ ‐ yeah.
‐ whenever we kiss, um‐‐
in rehearsal, whenever we kiss,
it's gonna be, like, Joe
and Debra, you know?
‐ yeah.
‐ and I want to kiss as Gabe and Maya.
‐
That's literally the
most romantic thing
I've ever heard.
‐ okay.
So let's save it then.
Let's save our first kiss.
‐ okay. So when?
‐ for, uh, let's‐‐ first date.
We'll do it on our first date.
‐ so when?
‐ the last night of hell week.
‐ okay. ‐ okay.
‐ wait, what's hell week?
Oh, you'll see.
‐ Oh, my god, they heard us.
‐ they heard us.
Guys, are we ready yet?
- Sorry, yeah. Yeah.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like, just, like, the shading here
and then it kind of has,
like, a vibe with it.
The kind of feel of the night.
‐ going into hell week, gang.
It's gonna be intense.
Sure, a play needs actors
and writing, blah, blah.
Actors suck!
But it really is about
the behind the scenes
that makes it all happen.
And kone, you fucking led us there.
I'm making you stage manager.
‐ oh, my god.
‐ hey. ‐ hey.
‐ hmm.
‐
‐ oh.
You looking for these?
It's 4:00. Actors are called at 4:10.
Oh.
Let's go.
‐ yeah, that's on me, guys. I
got the time all messed up.
You're in the driver's seat, kone.
Here's what's gonna happen. ‐ okay.
‐ the actors are gonna
be so fucking excited
to step onto stage,
they're gonna walk around barefoot,
but there are nails, there is sawdust,
this is not a playground.
You own the space.
Don't let them‐‐ Maya:
Oh, my god, you guys!
This is so big!
This is crazy!
This is, like, so big.
Hey! Ha! Ha!
Ha! Ha!
Okay.
Places for the‐‐
it's not‐‐it's not, uh‐‐
‐
‐ turn it up.
‐ Places for the top of act one.
Please?
‐ hey, Anna. ‐ hey, Maya.
Please, can you do that?
And put your shoes on.
‐ we usually rehearse
without shoes, but‐‐
‐ and then we'll do places
for the top of act one.
‐ okay.
‐ guys. ‐ shoes are over there.
‐ oh, god.
‐ we have our shoes over here.
I‐‐they're not back here. ‐ oh, my god.
Tech week, people.
Take it from the top.
‐ I saw you!
I saw you with my own two eyes!
Hold.
Yeah, stay right there. Hold.
‐ I didn't even finish my line.
‐ kay, it's more important
that we mark this cue.
It's a lighting thing.
You wouldn't understand.
Okay, we got it. Act.
You‐‐
‐ oh, is it your line? ‐ yeah.
I saw you with my own‐‐
hold. ‐ oh, my god.
‐ why do you keep going like this?
If you're not gonna do that on the day,
don't do that, okay?
‐ seriously? ‐ did you get it?
‐ yeah. ‐ okay, we got it. Act.
‐ for ten years, you've told me‐‐
hold.
You're not in your light.
Still not in your light.
‐ I'd rather go to jail‐‐
mai, that's you. ‐ line.
‐ "I'd rather go to jail
than spend one more minute with you."
‐ I have it. Thank you.
‐ to your left. Your left.
The other left. ‐ Anna,
let me finish the line.
Hold. Go 132.
Hold. Hold, I said.
Hold. Hold!
Hold.
- ‐ we're just getting up.
- Hold.
Walk it through slowly
so we can get the marks.
‐ Saw you with my own two eyes.
‐ slower physical.
‐ Rat bastard.
‐ faster vocal.
‐ I saw you backing away from Sheila.
Sheila was a rat bastard. I saw
you backing away from Sheila.
‐ what are you gonna do, Debra?
You gonna divorce me?
‐ I don't even know what
we're doing anymore.
I'm really confused. ‐
can you do it full‐out?
‐ I don't wanna do it
full‐out right now.
I don't want to go at 100.
I'm gonna go at‐‐
‐ if you are doing something different
than what you're doing on the day,
we're not gonna know our cue.
‐ oh, my god.
Please let us do our work.
‐ uh, can you say it again?
‐ you keep forgetting your lines.
‐ okay, sorry!
Find your light. ‐ is that it?
Colder. ‐ is that it?
‐ colder. ‐ is that it?
Ice cold. ‐ is that it?
‐ oh, my god. ‐ is that fucking it?
Line? ‐ damn it, Maya!
‐ I cannot act
when you're yelling technical cues.
I cannot do it.
I don't know where the light is!
‐ whose fucking beeper is that?
‐ Did I find it?
‐ this is our time in the tech world
to make sure that you
guys don't mess it up.
No offense. ‐ I can't feel it.
‐ feel the warmth! ‐ give us space‐‐
‐ take a‐‐take a‐‐ ‐ to
breathe and say our lines!
If I can't say the
lines, then I can't act!
‐ I‐I can't‐‐
we're fucked.
So it's really simple.
I'm in my light.
Not in my light.
‐ can I just interject?
‐ yeah. ‐ it's called warmth.
You feel the warmth when
you're in the light.
‐ can I interject on his interjection?
I'm not feeling warmth.
Like, when I stand in the lights,
I don't know about you guys,
I don't feel it on my skin or anything.
‐ these are grade a lights.
‐ okay, we don't have a lot of time,
so props.
You guys need to put your props
back down on the props table.
I cannot emphasize it enough.
‐ sorry, but every time
Marissa places my prop
on stage left,
it's actually meant to be on
stage right where I exit.
‐ actually, you're using the bottle
at the top of act two
when you should be using the broom.
‐ okay, you guys, we don't
have time to talk about this.
So basically, the thing is,
is you just put your prop
back on the prop table.
Maya, got a note for you.
You gotta remember your lines.
That's the only way
that we know our cues
and you need to memorize them.
‐ I did memorize them.
If we had enough time to go
over them, I'd be able‐‐
‐ Maya, we can't do the work for you.
‐ I'm not asking you
to do the work for me.
I was doing the work.
'Cause you guys are doing tech
and we're, like, doing art, so‐‐
kay, tech is art, so‐‐
‐ fuck the semantics.
Just fucking remember your lines!
‐ all right, all right, okay.
- Very good.
- ‐
‐ was that a cough, Gabe?
‐ oh. Yeah, it's‐‐ I'm fine, though.
‐ all right. Everybody freeze.
We're done.
I am not gonna have my
actors get sick, okay?
Gabe, I'm not messing around, okay?
Go home, steam your sinuses,
and you gargle three times
with salt water, okay?
Everybody else, techies included,
go home, get some sleep,
at least eight hours,
and please, please wash your hands!
Thank you. ‐ I'm still‐‐
we're done. ‐ okay. Memorize‐‐
‐ good night. ‐ and
memorize your lines.
Thank you, Anna.
I'm sorry I'm yelling.
‐ are we still on for
our date tonight or no?
‐ I mean, I might be sick.
‐ okay, well, I can take care of you.
Sick boy.
See you tonight, boyfriend.
‐ yeah. That's me.
‐ actually, that's the cue 32.
Like, I'm just so‐‐ fucking hell.
I can't handle these actors.
Like, I can't.
We didn't even have a dress rehearsal
'cause they're so fucking incompetent!
‐ shh.
‐ sorry.
‐ I was sweating bullets
2.6 seconds ago.
Look at me now.
‐ mm‐hmm.
‐ this play's a pile of dog shit.
But you can change it with your mind.
You get me?
‐ okay.
‐ Gabe, you girlfriend's here.
And she's so cute,
I won't even leave the door open.
‐ ‐
‐ mom.
‐ hi, boyfriend.
‐ hi.
‐ I brought masks and soup.
‐ I don't think I'm sick.
‐ well, just in case.
‐ I love this song.
‐ it's my favorite.
‐ me too.
‐ oh, my god.
Rehearsal was, like, complete shitake.
Literally.
‐ literally?
So it was a mushroom?
‐ yeah.
‐ what?
‐ do you want me to feed you the soup?
‐ nah, I'm good.
‐ okay.
‐
♪ It's only a tiny space ♪
‐ whoa, whoa, whoa.
‐ hold on. ‐ sorry.
‐ I just, uh...
‐ Sorry.
‐ I just, uh, didn't want
you to get sick, you know?
Here we go. ‐ kay.
‐ get a good hold on it.
Good? ‐ yeah.
I don't want you to get sick either.
Care to dance?
It feels like...
There's a bunch of butterflies
fluttering around in my chest.
‐ yeah.
‐ can we do a real kiss
now, without the masks on?
‐ um... L‐let's wait
until opening night
to do our first kiss.
‐ but I thought you
said not to do the kiss
as our characters, but
as Gabe and Maya?
‐ well, it's too late, you know?
We‐‐we already are our characters.
We are Joe and Debra, Maya,
so...
When we kiss, it'll still be us.
♪ Just the way you look ♪
‐ that's romantic.
Okay.
So tomorrow?
Opening night.
♪ Just the way you look ♪
‐